I've found my reason to become stronger
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So let's go and press on 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
Hung up on memories of a life of suffering
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
My heart barely stirs
kowabaru kokoro
My trembling hands are still
furueru te wa
Looking for the thing they long to grasp
tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
Even glaring up at the sky
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
Through the fragrance of the night
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
The only thing I can change is myself
kawatte ikeru no wa jibun jishin dake
And nothing else
sore dakesa
I've found my reason to become stronger
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So let's go and press on 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
No matter what!
doushitatte
My dreams can't be erased
kesenai yume mo
And time is keeping up its pace
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as there's someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
I learnt what it meant to lose
sekai ni uchinomesarete
As the world brought me down
makeru imi wo shitta
May the blood-soaked lotuses bloom bright
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Illuminating our path ahead
unmei wo terashite