This is the fate I’ve been entrusted with
ware ni kasu itaku wo
I’ve made up my mind, so I have to follow through
unmei to kakugo suru
I might struggle as it tries to tear me down
doro wo name agaitemo
But I can’t ignore this tiny invisible thread
me ni mienu hosoi ito
It connects me to a gentle smile
nakitaku naru you na
Bringing me to tears
yasashii oto
In the midst of this frustrating journey, it says
donna ni kuyashikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
A song in my heart
utae
Carries me past the despair
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how much it may hurt
kizutsuitemo kizutsuitemo
I have no choice but to get back on my feet
tachiagaru shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
There’s something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru