Nezuko!
Don't chase him!
Get back here!
Come back.
Nezuko!
Master Urokodaki did tell me
that since Nezuko's a demon now,
she doesn't need me to protect her anymore.
Can I let her handle this?
If she watches over these two,
I can focus on the offensive.
Nezuko!
I'm diving in!
Please protect these two!
I can count on you, right?
This is the inside of a swamp.
And these are...
Are these the belongings of
the people who were kidnapped?
Just look at how many innocent people
they've killed and eaten!
They can't get away with this.
Absolutely not!
Having trouble breathing, brat?
There's hardly any air inside this swamp.
On top of that, the darkness coiling around
your body must be feeling pretty heavy.
You can't move about freely like you would
above ground! Serves you right!
You should've looked before you leaped in, imbecile!
Don't underestimate me!
Where do you think I got my training, anyway?
Compared to the hell that was Mt. Sagiri,
this is nothing!
Not to mention
some techniques reach
their full potential underwater!
They can move around like that down here?
But it doesn't matter!
I just need to wait for them to close in, then attack!
There's a form that can be utilised
even without stable footing.
A forceful twist of the upper and lower body
that creates a powerful vortex!
I can smell it!
The opening thread!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Sixth Form!
Maelström!
I can't breathe!
I've gotta get out of here, fast!
Nezuko!
This girl's so damn strong!
It looks like she doesn't know how to morph yet,
but look at how strong she is anyway!
He must’ve given her a stupid amount of blood!
She moves so fast! I can't dive back into the swamp!
But...
I'm starting to get used to her simple attacks!
Even if she kicks my head off...
Even if she smashes my guts...
Demons regenerate in a flash!
Gotcha!
Now I'm gonna drill a hole
straight through your face!
Hands off my sister!
Is this really it?
He already took out my other selves!
You smell like rancid oil.
What a terrible stench!
Just how many people have you guys killed?!
Now listen here!
If you let girls age past their prime,
they'll start to look and taste like shit!
We ate them for their own good!
You should be thanking u—
Never mind.
Tell me everything you know about Kibutsuji Muzan.
Start talking!
Now!
I-I can't tell you...
I can't tell you!
Don't utter a single word.
You mustn't tell anyone about me.
If you do, I will know immediately.
I'm always watching you.
I can't tell you!
I can't tell you! I can't tell you! I can't tell you!
The smell of fear is strong.
He's absolutely terrified.
I can't tell you!
Yet again, I couldn't get any answers.
Nezuko!
She's sound asleep.
The bleeding's stopped, too.
She's trying to recover, huh?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Wait just a little longer, okay?
I promise your big brother
will make you human again!
Kazumi?
Are you all right?
My fiancée is dead.
How could I be all right?
Kazumi...
No matter how many people
you hold dear pass away,
you have no choice but to move on.
No matter how devastating the blows may be.
What the hell do you know?
You're just a kid!
I'll be on my way now.
Take this.
I hope you'll find one of Satoko's accessories
among these to hold on to as a memento.
Did you go through something like this, too?
Is that why?
I...
I'm sorry!
That was an awful thing to say!
Please, forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
Seeing his hand, hardened by relentless training
and covered in calluses, was heart-wrenching.
Those weren't the hands of a boy.
I'm leaving that girl in your hands!
Got it!
Got it...
It's not just me.
How many people have you killed,
tortured, and tormented?
Kibutsuji Muzan,
I will make you pay
for the misery you've caused!
Next on the list: Asakusa, Tokyo!
Rumours speak of a demon lurking there!
It's time for my next mission already?
Yes indeed!
Give me a second to breathe...
Second given!
Come on, just one minute! Hold on! What?
Just shut up and get going!
Are cities this advanced nowadays?
It doesn't feel like night-time at all!
The buildings are so tall!
What the—?!
The city...
I'm getting dizzy...
L-Let's go this way, Nezuko!
I-I beg your pardon!
Excuse me.
One bowl of Yamakake udon, please.
S-Sure thing!
I've never been to a place like this.
It's way too crowded.
One bowl of Yamakake udon.
Thank you kindly.
That scent!
Why would I catch it here?
It's the same scent that was at my house!
Kibutsuji Muzan!
Is that his scent?
It's him!
Daddy!
Who's that?
He's...
It's all right.
Don't worry.
He's...
He's pretending to be human!
Is there anything I could do for you?
You appear to be quite flustered.
Oh, my. What’s going on here?
Mommy!
They're human!
The baby girl and the woman...
They smell human!
Don't you know?
Can't you tell?
That he's a demon?
That he eats people?
An acquaintance of yours?
No, I don't know him.
Much to my consternation,
I've never met this youth before.
He may have mistaken me for another, perchance.
Oh, is that so?
What's the matter, honey?
Honey?
Stop!
I've finally tracked down Kibutsuji Muzan!
If I take him down,
I can make Nezuko human again!
But wow, everyone in Asakusa sure is stylish, huh?
I bet you'd look great in an outfit like that!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
The owner of the udon shop
was born and raised in Asakusa.
And I heard he makes udon in Asakusa
because he loves the place so much.
A suit, huh?
Now I feel kind of mature!
I'd better get back to my mission!
Next, Episode 8,
"The Fragrance of Bewitching Blood"!