Here goes...
I'm comin' through!
Infuriating!
Teruko!
Hold onto the furniture!
That's a demon with supernatural abilities!
Stop launching those reckless assaults!
Infuriating!
You damn insects running amok in my house!
The room freakin' spun around!
This is fun! I'm havin' a blast!
Don't stomp all over her!
Who the hell are you?
What do you think you're doing,
stepping on a little kid like that?
I like it!
No human's ever sent me flying like that before!
Why is he coming after me?
Isn't he a Demon Slayer?
My swords will hurt you.
Because they're not the kind of swords
you little gentlemen use!
The way they shred through flesh...
I pride myself on that!
Knock it off! There's a demon
right there, you know!
Like I care!
Damn insects!
Get out of my sight! Die!
The floor ripped apart all of a sudden!
At the same speed as the sound of the drum!
In the shape of a beast's claws!
Spinning right!
Spinning left!
Damn insects!
You damn miserable insects!
I'm starting to get the hang of it now!
We're in yet another room?
But what does this mean?
That demon didn't strike his drum just now.
I'm picking up the scent of
multiple demons in this house.
Is there another demon with a drum?
Is that why...
I can smell blood.
You'll be fine, okay?
Just stay behind me.
Okay.
Another human ripped to shreds and devoured!
Wh-What's the matter?
It's all right. There are no demons around.
Come on, let's head over there.
Without so much as a backward glance.
Look straight ahead, okay?
There's another scent.
A unique scent of blood I've never smelled before.
Looks like there wasn't that much bleeding.
Excuse me, Zenitsu.
G-G-G-Give me a signal first!
If you have something to say,
don't do it out loud suddenly!
It feels like my heart missed a beat!
I'm sorry.
If that had come to pass,
you would've become a murderer for sure!
You get it?
It's just that... Well, you see...
You've been sweating, gasping,
and shivering so horribly.
What about it? Aren't I doing the best I can here?
Well, forgive me for saying so,
but you're making me nervous, too, so...
Oh, no! Sorry about that!
But even so!
If we talk too much, those demons and all will...
They might find us, right?
That's why...
I think it would be best
to be as quiet as possible! Right?
A couple of kids.
Probably most agreeable to the tongue.
What did I tell you?
A demon showed up! You got it?
A demon showed up!
Go away! Stay away from us!
Stop that!
W-W-We don't taste good! I'm sure I taste awful!
I'm serious, okay? This kid's all skin and bones,
so he's all dry and tastes ghastly!
How will I know until I have a taste?
No!
What was that? He's quick-tongued!
Even able to split a vase in two!
This can't be real!
Zenitsu! Get up!
It's in my knees now!
Eighty percent of my fear is in my knees!
This isn't the time to whine!
Just leave me behind, okay?
Make a run for it!
I couldn't possibly do that!
He's such a good kid!
Staying here even though all I do is whimper!
I've got to find a way somehow!
If I don't protect him, what will become of him?
Dying before he reaches double digits
would be way too tragic!
But I'm so horribly weak!
Get up!
I don't have the ability to protect him!
But if I don't protect him...
I'm gonna guzzle your brains through your ears!
Zenitsu!
Zenit—
He's fast asleep.
What's up with him?
Die!
Zenitsu!
Please wake up!
Wh-What's this sound?
This guy...
He's giving off a different vibe!
Zenitsu...
Thunder Breathing First Form!
Thunderclap and Flash!
He's dead!
He died all of a sudden!
What the hell? I can't take this anymore!
What is this? What the? Yuck!
Shouichi...
Don't tell me...
Thank you! You saved my life!
I shall be eternally grateful to you for this!
Why didn't you tell me sooner
that you were so powerful?
What are you going on about?
Did you say something?
No.
Uh, no. Forget it.
Let's get going, okay?
Okay.
Damn! He sent me flying again!
It's been like this for the last three days, dammit!
Making my way through a cramped building like this...
It's just not my thing for crying out loud!
You dodged me, huh?
You seem to be a pretty fresh human.
Your flesh will be well worth gouging out!
Self-taught! Beast Breathing!
It's gonna be so worth it to shred such a huge target!
You've got guts to charge me head-on like that!
Owie!
Flaunt your corpse
and serve as my springboard!
Third Fang!
Tear and Gorge!
Comin' through!
Rareblood...
If I can just consume some...
Fifty...
No—A hundred humans' worth...
I have to find more rareblood humans
and consume them.
That way...
I can reclaim my place among
the Twelve Blood Moons!
Kyougai.
You can't eat any more?
Is that all you've got?
No.
No, I'm not done!
P-Please give me more time!
J-Just a little!
I've had enough.
I'm stripping you of your number.
That's your limit, and you've reached it.
The more humans you consume,
the stronger you can become.
And once he saw my potential,
Lord Kibutsuji was willing to share his blood with me.
The power of that man's blood was mind-boggling.
I was sure that I'd grow
infinitely stronger than ever before,
be welcomed into the ranks of the Twelve Blood Moons,
continue to gorge myself on humans,
and become even more powerful! Or so I believed!
Or so I believed.
Kiyoshi!
Teruko!
Wh-Who's he?
I'm Kamado Tanjirou.
I've come to defeat the evil demons.
Now then, show me your wounds.
Good job for hanging in there on your own.
Kiyoshi...
Now this ointment here is amazing!
My master gave it to me!
My master always wears a tengu mask.
Tengu?
Really?
Yes, it's true.
My master's ointment is so amazing,
it kicks in within mere seconds.
Okay, you're all set!
Well? The pain's gone, isn't it?
Yes!
Do you think you can you tell me what happened here?
A monster dragged me away,
a-and I nearly got eaten.
But just then,
another monster showed up out of nowhere,
a-and they started fighting to the death
over who was gonna get to e-eat me.
A-And then,
the one with the drum growing out of him...
When the other monster defeated him,
he dropped a drum!
And when I picked it up and struck it,
this room suddenly changed.
And I somehow held on until now!
A demon with drums growing out of him...
So that was him?
He mentioned "rareblood" or something like that.
That's right!
He kept calling me "rareblood"!
Rareblood!
That's what they call those who carry delicate blood!
You little brats!
I'm going to peck you now.
Cut it out!
What do you mean by "delicate blood"?
The blood of all living species
can be categorized into types, moron!
And the ultimate rareblood...
The less common the blood is...
For a demon!
A single rareblood human has
the same nutritional value as eating fifty!
One hundred humans!
For demons, rarebloods are a feast!
Rareblood is their favorite food!
Rareblood...
I'm leaving this room now.
Keep calm.
It's all right.
I'm just going to take down that demon.
Listen to me, Teruko.
Your brother is terribly exhausted right now.
Make sure to look after him, okay?
As soon as I leave the room,
strike that drum and move out.
Just like Kiyoshi's been doing until now,
whenever someone tries to open
the door or you hear something,
strike that drum right away and make a run for it.
I promise to come pick you up.
I'll follow your scent.
I'll call out your names when I open the door.
You just have to hold out a little longer.
You can do it, right?
Good!
You're so strong!
I'm heading out.
Strike it!
Damn insects!
So infuriating!
The drum on his right shoulder
flips the room to the right!
The left one flips it to the left!
Right leg, forward spin!
Left leg, backward spin!
And the drum on his belly launches that claw attack!
So fast!
The speed of the rotations and attacks is devastating!
Miss Tamayo may have treated my wounds,
but I haven't fully recovered from my injuries yet!
Can I beat him?
These injuries hurt so badly
that I can hardly stand it!
All this time, I've just been enduring it!
When I pulled Zenitsu off that girl,
when I shouted out, I was enduring
this horrendous pain!
I was able to withstand it because I'm the eldest son!
But I couldn't have if I were the second!
Whenever I dig in, the broken parts creak,
and I can't muster any strength.
That demon's attack is leaving scars
that look like claw marks.
It scares me so much that I can't move in closer!
Since I'm not at full strength,
if I charge forward to get within striking distance,
a flash of pain makes me stumble!
I'll get sliced into rings!
My injuries are making me
imagine the most awful things!
Master Urokodaki!
Water can change into any form.
Pour it into a container, and it's a square.
Pour it into a bottle, and it's round.
Sometimes, it can even smash boulders
and flow away as far as the eye can see.
That's right! That's it!
There are ten Water Breathing forms!
I can battle any kind of opponent!
If you're hurt, use a move
that will compensate for that!
I can take on any form!
And this flow will never be stopped!
Right now, it's not just my bones!
My heart's also been broken!
A broken Tanjirou's not gonna do any good!
All right! If you could please quiet down!
Look straight ahead!
Fire yourself up!
Give it all you've got, Tanjirou!
You've got this!
I've been doing great so far!
I have what it takes!
And neither today
nor any other time in the future!
Even if I'm broken...
I won't ever give up, no matter what!
Give it all you've got, Tanjirou!
You've got this!
I'm the eldest son, so I can endure it!
You'll be cheering me on too, right?
Thanks, Nezuko!
Okay, to show you my gratitude,
I'm gonna cheer you on, too!
Give it all you've got, Nezuko!
You've got this!
You won't ever give up, no matter what!
You're the eldest daughter, but if anything
bad happens to you, don't endure it.
Just tell me, okay?
Next, Episode 13,
"Something More Important Than Life"!
Looks like we've run out of time for the Taisho secret!