Excuse me.
Could I have that basket, straw, and some bamboo?
Sure, I don't mind. But that basket's full o' holes.
That's fine, thanks. How much is it?
Nah, that's all right.
I mean, 'tis a basket o' holes.
Please, I insist.
Nah, don't worry 'bout it.
Ya can take the bamboo and straw, too.
Well, I insist!
'Tis fine, really!
You're one stubborn lad!
Please accept this, even if it may not be much!
Thank you very much!
Yeowch!
Nezuko?
Huh? Nezuko?
She's gone!
Oh, there she is.
Nezuko...
Did she dig herself a hole?
I can't believe my little sister turned into a mole.
And she's got a giant frown on her face.
She really doesn't like sunlight, huh?
Give me a bit.
Nezuko?
Can you fit in here?
I'd like to keep moving during the day.
I can carry you in here.
Come.
Inside.
The basket.
A bit small, huh?
Nezuko sure has grown into a big girl.
It feels like yesterday that she was just a little kid.
Say, Nezuko.
Remember how you made your body bigger before?
Could you do the opposite and shrink instead?
Shrink, Nezuko!
Shrink more!
Nicely done!
Attagirl!
I'm impressed!
Mt. Sagiri?
If you want to get to Mt. Sagiri,
you'll have to cross that mountain, but...
The sun's already setting.
Will you be okay with all that luggage?
It's dangerous.
Don't worry, I'll keep an eye out.
Thank you kindly.
People have been going missing recently!
Make sure you don't get lost!
There's a temple here.
Looks like the lights are on.
We can probably find someone there.
Let's check it out.
I can smell blood.
This mountain path is pretty rough.
Someone might be hurt!
Is everything okay?
The hell's this?
This is my turf.
Set foot in my territory
and I'll make you regret it!
A man-eating demon!
Something's off here.
Are you two human?
An axe, huh? Not bad.
But a scratch like this
will heal in no time.
See, what'd I tell you?
The bleeding's stopped already.
He's fast! And incredibly strong!
The same trick ain't gonna work twice.
Say goodbye to your neck!
Sh-She killed him!
But hold on, he's a demon!
It should be fine, r-right?
N-Nezuko...
You've gotta be kidding me.
Did his body just move without a head?
You assholes!
So one of you was a demon!
No wonder you seemed off.
Why the fuck's a demon in cahoots with a human?
His head's still talking!
Stop!
Nezuko!
What's wrong with this guy?
Why the hell is he growing arms from his head?
I've got to save Nezuko!
Get outta my way!
This guy's head is hard...
His head is
crazy hard!
All right!
My hair got all tangled up on the haft!
Shit!
Nezuko! Where are you?
Nezuko!
Don't you touch her!
I wonder if there are lots of demons out there.
This isn't the scent I picked up back home.
He's unrelated.
But...
If I don't finish him off, he'll continue killing people.
So...
I have to do this.
Do it!
You won't be able to kill him with that.
A tengu mask!
I couldn't hear his footsteps!
H-How do I finish him off?
Don't rely on others!
Can't you use your own head?
If stabbing won't work...
Crushing is my last resort.
If I want to crush his head completely,
I'll have to hit him multiple times.
It'll be a painful death.
Isn't there something, anything,
I can use to finish him in one go?
This kid isn't gonna cut it.
His compassion is clouding his judgment.
He's facing a demon,
yet the scent of kindness remains.
His empathy extends even to demons.
Giyuu...
This kid won't make it.
I blacked out.
Did my body die, then?
I feel sick!
You bastard, I'll kill you!
I'll eat your fucking guts.
Get over here! Dammit!
I can't get to you, so come over here!
I've wasted too much time.
Hey, are you listening, brat?
Hey! Come here, you!
The sun's already rising.
Are you listening, you fucking brat?
All it took was that little sunlight?!
No wonder Nezuko shrinks away from it!
Nezuko?
Nezuko...
Oh, r-right.
What about that man?
He buried the victims.
Excuse me.
My name is Urokodaki Sakonji.
You must be the one
Tomioka Giyuu sent my way.
Yes! My name is Kamado Tanjirou!
My sister's name is Nezuko, and...
Tanjirou.
What will you do when your sister devours a human?
You're too indecisive!
You're too slow at making tough decisions.
You failed to kill that demon before daybreak.
Do you know why you couldn't
answer my question straight away?
It's because you lack resolve!
There are only two things left to do
when your sister devours a human.
First, you kill your sister!
Second, you cut your own stomach and die!
That's what it means to continue
staying by your demon sister's side.
Commit to memory that such a thing
should never occur, no matter the circumstance.
Make sure that your sister never
takes the life of an innocent person!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes!
I will test you to see if you're fit
to become a Demon Slayer.
Get your sister ready and follow me.
He's fast! Just how old is this man?
And I still can't hear his footsteps!
Nezuko, I know you're uncomfortable
in there, but please bear with it.
You've always had to bear with everything.
Nezuko...
You...
You're fixing your kimono again?
I guess we've gotta buy you a new one.
No, no, it's fine!
This kimono's my favourite!
Besides, I'd rather the little ones
got more food to fill them up instead!
I swear I'll make you human again!
I swear I'll buy you a beautiful kimono someday!
Everything I couldn't do for the others...
I'll do it all for you!
N-N-Now have I... p-passed the t-test?
The test begins now.
We're climbing up the mountain.
I'll take care of your sister in the meantime.
I'll leave her in your care, then.
I'm exhausted.
I can't feel my legs anymore.
I feel like I'm about to pass out.
Now find your way back to that house
at the bottom of the mountain.
I won't wait until daybreak this time.
That's it?
Oh, I get it.
He thinks I'll get lost in this thick fog.
I just have to get back by dawn, right?
That's a piece of cake!
I've got a sharp nose!
I've already memorised Urokodaki's scent!
Pebbles?!
A pitfall?
I see.
This place is rigged with traps.
So that's the challenge.
Oh, crap!
Crap, crap, crap!
If I keep getting caught in traps,
I won't make it back by dawn!
And besides, on this mountain...
On this mountain...
The air's really thin here!
It's way thinner than back home.
So that's why I've been feeling so light-headed!
Will I make it back in time?
I might pass out.
No!
I will make it back.
Get your breathing under control
and sniff out each and every trap!
Got it! I can smell them!
Traps set by humans will have
their scent lingering around them!
But knowing that
doesn't magically make me
athletic enough to dodge them all!
I'll make it back to you no matter what...
Nezuko!
I've... made... it back...
Dear Urokodaki Sakonji.
Please forgive my briskness.
I'm sending a boy your way
who wants to become a Demon Slayer.
He was brazen enough to challenge me unarmed.
A demon slaughtered his family,
and the surviving younger sister has become one.
However, I have determined
that she will not harm humans.
I can sense something special about these two.
Like yourself, the boy appears to
have a keen sense of smell.
Perhaps he'll find a way to break through
and become your successor.
Please take him on as your apprentice.
I realise that this is a selfish request,
but please bear with me.
I hope that you will take
good care in your endeavours.
Yours sincerely,
Tomioka Giyuu.
I accept you as my student, Kamado Tanjirou.
The demon in that temple
sure took us by surprise, huh?
I never expected to see arms grow from his head!
Now that Master Urokodaki
has accepted me, I'll do my utmost best!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
Believe it or not, the masked
Urokodaki's age is actually—
Tanjirou!
Yes?!
What do you want for dinner?
Meat and potato stew or oden?
Huh? Well...
You're too indecisive!
I want oden!
Next, Episode 3, "Sabito and Makomo"!