The reason I won
was because I learned how to
detect an opening to strike.
While fighting somebody,
I can sometimes pick up the scent of a thread.
That thread connects my blade
to an opening in my opponent's stance,
becoming taut the moment I sense it.
It guides my blade,
and I strike through the opening.
Master Urokodaki...
I had no intentions of allowing you to
take part in the Final Selection.
I no longer wanted to see any children die.
I was confident you'd be unable to
split this boulder in half, and yet...
Well done, my boy!
Tanjirou, you're a remarkable child!
Make sure you come back alive
from the Final Selection.
Your sister and I will both be waiting for you.
What's the occasion? There's so much!
You've completed your training.
It's a cause for celebration.
Don't be shy. Eat up.
Thank you very much!
Tanjirou,
there's nothing more I can do for you.
From here on out, you will face
much hardship and strife.
Your training will pale in comparison.
So, at least for now,
rest well without a care in the world.
Hey, Tanjirou...
Yes?
Did you enjoy the hot pot?
Yeah! It's been a long time since I've had such a feast!
A callow lad with a hearty appetite
will grow both bigger and stronger.
But the same rings true of demons.
Remember this.
A demon is as strong as the
number of humans it has consumed.
So the more they eat, the stronger they get?
That's right.
Some demons even morph and gain special powers.
You never know what strange
abilities you might run into.
When your sense of smell grows keener,
you'll be able to tell how many
humans a demon has devoured.
What's this?
It's a warding mask.
I've imbued it with magic that
protects the wearer from harm.
A warding mask...
Nezuko.
I swear I'll make it back.
Don't worry about your sister.
I'll take care of her.
Thanks, I appreciate it!
See you, Master Urokodaki!
Give my regards to Sabito and Makomo!
Tanjirou...
Where did you learn of
the names of those deceased children?
Wow.
Look at all these wisteria.
I thought they were out of season.
It's packed here.
Greetings, everyone.
Thank you for attending the Demon Slayers'
Final Selection this fine evening.
Here on Mt. Fujikasane,
the Demon Slayers keep
several captured demons alive.
They cannot leave this mountain.
That is because wisteria, which demons hate so much,
blooms year-round from halfway down the mountain.
However, they don't grow from this point onward,
thus there will be demons about.
To pass the Final Selection process,
you must survive there for seven days.
And now, be on your way.
Surviving should be the only thing
on my mind for the next seven days.
First things first, I need to get through the night.
Once the sun comes up,
the demons won't be able to do anything.
I can rest up then.
With that in mind, I'll head eastward!
I'll make my way to where the sunlight hits first!
This scent...
It's a demon!
And it's nearby!
Where is it?
Where's it coming from?
I can't pinpoint the direction of the scent!
From above?
A demon...
Damn you!
Don't try'n steal my prey, asshole!
Get off my turf before I make you!
To hell with you! Beat it!
Don't gimme that turf bullshit!
Two of them right from the get-go?
Shut up before I fucking kill you!
I wonder if I can take them.
He's my prey!
Oh shut it, princess!
It's first come, first served!
You can do it!
Calm down and watch their movements!
Remember your training!
It's been ages since I got to enjoy human flesh!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
I can smell the thread!
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide!
I did it!
I beat two demons!
I've grown stronger!
All that training wasn't for nothing!
I can do it after all!
If I kill a demon with the sword
Master Urokodaki gave me,
not even its bones remain, huh?
A demon's weak spot is its neck!
But even then, a normal sword
won't be enough to kill it.
Then, how do you kill a demon?
The swords the Demon Slayers wield
were forged with a special type of steel.
That's the only way to kill a demon.
We call them "Sun Blades".
Rest in peace.
What's that rotten smell?
No way...
I didn't sign up for this!
What the—
What the hell is that?
Hey, Sabito...
Do you think Tanjirou can beat him?
I don't know.
No matter how hard you try, it's never enough.
You know that well yourself, don't you?
What's this deformed demon doing here?
They didn't tell us about this!
He ate him!
Don't be afraid!
Help him!
You're not powerless anymore!
Go!
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Another sweet little cub has come my way!
"Another"?
Tell me, little fox cub. What Meiji year is it now?
We're in the Taisho Period!
Taisho?
What the hell?!
We've already changed dynasties?!
Again! I've been stuck on this goddamn
mountain for yet another dynasty!
Unforgivable! He'll pay for this!
Damn you, Urokodaki! Damn you, Urokodaki!
You know Master Urokodaki?
Oh, I know him, all right!
That bastard was the one who captured me!
It's been forty-seven long, torturous years!
He was still a demon hunter back then!
It was the Edo Period during the Keio Era.
Demon hunter? Edo Period?
You're lying!
No demon has ever lived that long!
The only demons in here should be those
who've eaten just two or three humans!
They get killed during the Final Selection,
and even cannibalise each other!
But I've survived all this time.
I've feasted on at least fifty of you
brats inside this wisteria prison.
Fifty?!
Eleven, twelve...
Thirteen.
That makes you number fourteen!
What are you talking about?
That's how many of his disciples I've eaten.
I promised myself I'd kill every single one of them.
Let's see...
There were two in particular I'll never forget.
Those two...
The stronger one was a brat
with an unusual hair colour.
It was like the colour of meat.
He had a huge scar across his cheek.
The other brat was a girl that wore a floral kimono.
She was small and frail, but quite nimble.
This demon has already killed them?!
But I was with them earlier!
Those fox masks!
All of his disciples wear them.
I'm familiar with the designs Urokodaki carves.
They're the same style as his tengu mask!
Warding masks, right?
I ate them because of the masks they wore.
They're all here inside my belly.
It's like Urokodaki fed them to me himself!
When the girl heard that,
she started crying and fell into a rage.
Her deftness turned into recklessness,
making her much easier to deal with.
I ripped her apart, limb by limb, and then...
Calm down, Tanjirou.
Your breathing's uneven.
It's all right. Don't worry about us!
I've gotta get the hell out of here while
the demon's focused on that guy!
Another one of Urokodaki's brats is dead.
I wonder how he'll feel when
another kid doesn't come home.
What kind of look will he have on his face?
Oh man, I wish I could see it.
I really do.
Tanjirou!
He dodged it?!
He's still got some life in him?
Great! I get to have some more fun!
Damn it! No matter how many arms I cut,
they grow back in mere seconds!
You're gonna need to do more than just
slash off my arms if you wanna win.
But then again, not even that
pink-haired brat could chop off my head!
I can't just let this go!
I've gotta bring him down now,
before any more lives are lost!
I can smell a demon underground?
Wh-What a leap! Dammit, I missed him!
Sure, but there's no way he can
dodge this attack in mid-air!
Do you think Tanjirou will lose, too?
His neck is so tough, after all.
He may lose, and yet, he may win.
Either way, there's one irrefutable fact.
Tanjirou is
the man who split the largest,
toughest boulder of all in half.
He deflected it!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
He's gotten too close!
But I have nothing to fear.
My neck is impenetrable! He can't cut through it!
First Form!
As soon as he fails to cut my neck,
I will crush his puny little head!
Just like the other one!
Surface Water Slash!
How was that Nezuko? Aren't I pretty cool?
What? Sabito was cooler than me?
C-Come on, Nezuko!
R-Right!
I saw beautiful wisteria blooming
around the exam grounds.
Let's go see them when you're human again.
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
There's this blond boy named Zenitsu.
I hear his master slapped him around for refusing to
take the exam and had to drag him here.
Next, Episode 5, "My Own Steel"!