Let's go.
The Demon Slayers.
They number in the hundreds.
The organisation isn't officially
recognised by the government,
but it has existed since ancient times,
and they continue to hunt demons to this day.
However, their leader's identity
remains shrouded in mystery.
Demons.
Their staple food is man.
They kill humans and feed on them.
The time and place of their origin is unknown.
Their bodies carry immense strength,
and their wounds mend in no time.
Their mangled flesh regenerates,
and their limbs can be regrown.
Some have special abilities.
A few can even shapeshift.
They can only be killed by exposing them to sunlight
or by beheading them with a special sword.
The Demon Slayers battle the demons
with their mortal bodies.
Since they're human,
their wounds are slow to heal,
and, once lost, their limbs don't grow back.
And yet, they continue to fight the demons
to protect their fellow humans.
I'm a mentor.
I teach people in swordsmanship.
There are as many mentors
as there are stars in the sky,
and each one teaches their disciples
in their own respective place and style.
In order to become a Demon Slayer,
you must survive the Final Selection
process held on Mt. Fujikasane.
Whether you may take part or not
is up to my discretion.
Starting today, I'll be keeping a journal for Nezuko.
I descended the mountain again today.
I'll train my hardest so I don't die
during the Final Selection process.
After descending the mountain day after day,
I've grown adept at avoiding the traps
thanks to my strength and endurance training,
as well as my sense of smell vastly improving.
That said...
The traps keep getting more and more extreme.
I swear he's trying to kill me here!
Today, I did the usual while carrying a sword.
It was genuinely awful!
No longer empty-handed,
I kept getting caught in traps.
Nine-hundred-ninety-one!
Nine-hundred-ninety-two!
Today, I practised sword swings.
Nine-hundred-ninety-three!
Nine-hundred-ninety-four!
Well, I say "today", but I've been doing
this pretty much every day as of recently.
Nine-hundred-ninety-five!
Nine-hundred-ninety-six!
Nine-hundred-ninety-seven!
After my daily routine, I'd practise swinging
until my arms were about to fall off.
Nine-hundred-ninety-eight!
Nine-hundred-ninety-nine!
One thousand!
Do five hundred more!
Swords are very brittle.
That was his first lesson.
Vertically, a sword is powerful,
but horizontally, it's fragile.
You must apply the force straight along the blade.
The blade's orientation must be in perfect alignment
with the force of your swing.
He also made it crystal clear
that if I ever break or damage a sword,
my bones would be soon to follow.
Real scary stuff.
Nezuko...
I'll keep doing my best, okay?
Today, I did nothing but fall.
That is, I trained to break my fall properly
and get back up quickly, no matter the situation.
I would wield my sword
and charge at Master Urokodaki with full intent to kill.
In contrast,
Master Urokodaki would await me bare-handed.
But he's ridiculously strong!
Every time he flung me away,
I'd struggle to break my fall.
I'm back, Nezuko.
Today, I learned about breathing
techniques and a few stances.
Total Concentration Breathing?
That's right.
I will teach you all ten Water Breathing forms.
Take a deep, lengthy breath and feel the oxygen
flowing into every cell in your body.
This will enhance your body's
natural healing power,
as well as stabilise and energise your spirit.
Relax your upper body
while bracing your lower half.
All right. Breathe!
Wrong!
Next! Take your stance.
Right! Like this?
Wrong!
Like this?
This?
Wrong!
He yelled at me for not bracing my stomach,
and kept punching me in the gut.
Next, he told me to "become one with water".
Get in there!
Nezuko!
Nezuko! I am water!
Before I knew it, six months had passed
since Nezuko entered her deep slumber.
Master Urokodaki summoned a doctor
and had her examined straight away,
but he found nothing wrong.
It's abnormal for her to stay asleep for so long.
I'm scared.
I worry that one day,
I'll wake up to find her dead.
Not a day goes by that I don't worry.
My descents keep getting more dangerous,
and the air's even thinner where I train now.
Time and time again,
I worry that today will be my last.
I have nothing left to teach you.
Out of nowhere, about a year after
I arrived at Mt. Sagiri, he broke the news.
The rest is up to you!
Will you be able to obtain a deeper
understanding of what I've taught you?
Follow me.
If you can split this boulder,
I will allow you to participate in the Final Selection.
Is a boulder something
a sword can split?
Can a sword really cut through it?
I don't think I can do it.
My sword would snap in half!
Please wait, Master Urokodaki!
Master Urokodaki!
From that day onward,
Master Urokodaki would no longer teach me.
I would practise what I had been taught
over and over every single day.
Holding my breath, flexibility...
I'm glad I wrote down every little detail in my journal.
However...
Six months went by,
and I still couldn't split that boulder.
I was frustrated.
Not enough!
I haven't trained hard enough yet!
I've gotta train more!
Even more!
Am I a lost cause?
Will Nezuko never wake up again?
I can't go on! I've hit my limit!
Don't give up, Tanjirou! You've got this!
Shut up!
A man shouldn't whine.
It's unseemly.
Where did he come from?
I can't pick up his scent!
Is that a fox mask?
No matter what hardship you face, bear it in silence.
Like a real man.
If you can even call yourself a man.
You're slow.
Weak.
Immature.
You're a far cry from a real man.
What do you think you're doing?!
Do tell me, what do you think you're doing?
What do you mean?
I'm training.
How long does it take you to get your ass
off the ground and assume a proper stance?
Now. Come at me.
But your sword's made of wood and mine's real!
Well, would you look at that!
Why, thank you for worrying about me.
So you think you can so much as graze me?
You have absolutely nothing to be concerned about!
I'm stronger than you!
Strong enough to cut through boulders!
Hang on, cut through boulders?
You've gained nothing.
You haven't mastered a single thing!
Not even the breathing technique
taught by Master Urokodaki:
Total Concentration Breathing.
He knows Master Urokodaki?
And even the breathing technique?
All you did was memorise it.
You learned it as knowledge.
Your body has no idea
what it's supposed to do.
What the hell have you been doing
for the past year and a half?
Carve it into your flesh!
More!
Even more!
Never forget the secrets Master Urokodaki taught you!
Pound it into the marrow of your bones!
I'm trying!
I've been trying my best every single day!
But I'm just not making any headway!
I just can't advance any further!
Advance!
If you're a man!
If you call yourself a man!
Your only choice is to advance!
Come at me!
Show me what you're truly capable of!
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Are you okay?
Did you see that?
What an amazing strike!
Not a single bit of wasted motion.
It was truly beautiful!
I want to be just like him!
You think I could become just like him?
I'm sure you can, since I'll be watching over you.
She's so cute.
Excuse me, but who are you?
That girl's name was Makomo.
She told me the boy's name was Sabito.
She started by pointing out my shortcomings.
She also corrected any unnecessary
movements and bad habits I had picked up.
But she refused to tell me anything about
why she's helping me or where she came from.
We really love Master Urokodaki.
That was her pet phrase.
Sabito and Makomo weren't siblings.
They were orphans before
Master Urokodaki took them in.
There are other children besides us.
They're always watching over you, Tanjirou.
Makomo is a bit of a strange girl.
She speaks in such a fluffy, dreamy way.
Total Concentration Breathing
accelerates your blood flow,
which makes your heart race.
Your body becomes boiling hot
and you become as strong as a demon.
The important thing is to expand your lung capacity.
When you bring lots and lots of air into your blood,
your blood gets excited.
This makes your bones and muscles, like,
heat up and make you a lot stronger.
I don't think I caught any of that.
How do I do that?
Train to death.
At the end of the day, I don't think
there's much else you can do.
Until my arms and legs were ready to fall off...
Until my lungs and heart were ready to burst...
I would swing my sword.
But even then...
I still couldn't beat Sabito.
Not until six months later.
When I challenged him that day,
he was wielding a real sword.
It took you half a year,
but you're finally starting to look like a real man.
Today's the day I win!
Head-on battles are simple.
Victory goes to whomever's stronger and faster.
The battle was over in an instant.
It was this day. For the first time,
right at this very moment,
my blade reached Sabito first.
When I had finally beaten him,
Sabito was smiling.
A smile that carried a hint of delight and melancholy.
An expression full of relief.
Tanjirou.
You did great.
Hold this memory close to your heart.
Make sure you win, okay?
Beat him, too.
The next thing I knew,
Sabito was gone.
And my sword, which I was sure
had cut through Sabito's mask,
had split the boulder.
Yeah, that shocked me too!
I can't believe I split that boulder!
I couldn't have done it without those two.
I can't thank them enough.
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
Why does Master Urokodaki wear a mask?
I heard it's because demons used to
make fun of his face for looking too kind.
Sabito, Makomo, and Master Urokodaki!
I'll keep doing my best
to make Nezuko human again!
Next, Episode 4, "The Final Selection"!