Rise and shine, demon!
Stop it!
Look, it's the human blood you love so much!
What's the matter, demon?
Come have a taste!
You know you want it.
Iguro, you're digging into him too hard.
Ease up a bit, please.
I'm only pinning him down
because he's trying to break free.
Kamado,
if you use any breathing techniques while
your lungs are being squeezed, your veins will burst.
His veins will burst!
I like it! Sounds bombastic!
Come on! Start bursting!
Poor soul.
Such a weak, pitiful child.
Praise to Amida Buddha.
Kamado?
Nezuko!
She's my sister!
She's my little sister!
It wasn't Nezuko!
I don't know what's wrong with her now, but...
All humans are your family.
Protect humans.
Humans are to be helped and protected.
I must help them.
I must never hurt them.
What just happened?
The demon girl turned away in disgust.
Shinazugawa stabbed her three times
and is flaunting his bloody arm in her face,
but she restrained herself and did not bite.
And with that, it's been proven that
Nezuko won't harm any humans, right?
What do you think you're doing, Tomioka?
Tanjirou.
I'm sure that, even after all's said and done,
there will be some who still can't accept Nezuko.
You must prove yourselves from this point onward.
Prove that both of you can serve as Demon Slayers,
and that you have something to offer.
What is this feeling?
It's like I'm floating.
His voice...
Is it because of this man's voice
that my head is feeling so mellow?
Go out and defeat one of the Twelve Blood Moons.
With that, you will be accepted by all.
And it will give more weight to your words.
I...
Nezuko and I will defeat Kibutsuji Muzan!
We will not fail!
We'll take him down and put an end
to this endless cycle of grief!
As you're ill-equipped to do so right now,
let's keep it at taking down
a Blood Moon for now, all right?
Yes, sir.
You mustn't laugh!
You mustn't, mustn't, mustn't!
It goes without saying that the Hashira of
the Demon Slayers are phenomenally skilled.
They have trained to the point of coughing up
blood and stared in the face of death,
and also claimed the lives of many a Blood Moon.
A good attitude to have!
That is why the Hashira are respected
and welcomed by many.
So Tanjirou, mind your manners when you speak.
Y-Yes, sir!
And one more thing. Sanemi.
Obanai.
Don't be so harsh on the younglings.
As you wish.
Tanjirou, we have concluded our business with you.
You may step back.
In that case, allow me to take Kamado into my house.
All right, then! Take them away, please!
Pardon me for cutting in front of you!
Now then, let us begin the Hashira Meet—
Hold on! I'm not done yet!
Come back here!
Please allow me to give that man
covered in scars a good headbuttin'!
I've gotta—
Shut it! Keep your mouth shut!
I must trade a headbutt for
every time he stabbed Nezuko!
Surely headbutting doesn't violate the code!
Shut up! Settle down right this instant!
Let me go!
Cut it out!
You're not allowed to interrupt the Master.
We beg your pardon!
We beg your pardon, Master!
Master Tokito!
We beg your pardon.
We beg your pardon!
We assure you that this boy
will be severely reprimanded, so—
Muichiro!
What a fine boy!
So please! Please!
So cool!
Just get out of our sight.
Yes, sir!
Tanjirou.
Give Tamayo my regards.
Hold up a second!
I just heard him mention Miss Tamayo's name!
Not another word from you!
You got us in big trouble back there!
I was about to piss my pants!
You have no clue how terrifying the Hashira are!
Try to read the room! Please!
Don't think I'll ever forget this!
Me either!
Apologise!
Apologise! Right now!
I-I'm sorry.
Hello! Is anyone home?
Hello...
Geez, no one's answering the door.
Let's check the yard.
Hey, use your own two feet.
I'm sorry.
But my body is aching like crazy.
The headquarters was huge too,
but this mansion's something else, huh?
Come to think of it, wasn't this place
called the Butterfly Mansion?
Ah, there's someone here.
Right there, see?
That would be, um...
Oh, right! The Tsuguko...
Her name was...
Tsuguko?
It's Master Tsuyuri Kanao.
It's the girl from the Final Selection.
Seems like someone forgot the lady who
stomped him over the head the other night, huh?
A Tsuguko is a swordsman trained by a Hashira.
Only those who stand out with
their skills and talent get chosen.
She may be a girl, but she's plenty awesome.
Please forgive us, Master Tsuyuri.
We come here on orders of Lady Kochou.
Permission to enter the mansion?
Uh, do you mind?
You don't mind, do you?
And who might you be?
Well, you see...
We have orders from Lady Kochou!
Are you a Kakushi?
You've brought a patient, then?
Please come this way.
Uh, right!
She's fast!
Five times?
I've gotta take this medicine five times a day?
And for three whole months, you say?!
If I take this, I'll feel too bloated to eat!
It's super bitter!
It's such an ordeal!
So wait, are you seriously saying
this medicine will heal my limbs?
Listen, are they really gonna heal?
Give me answers! How will they heal?
Please stop shouting!
Somebody give me a thorough explanation!
He's still making a commotion?
What'll happen if I forget one day? Spill it!
My arms and legs!
What's gonna happen to my arms and legs?
What'll happen if I forget to take it?
Zenitsu!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Please quiet down!
Didn't we already explain it to you multiple times?
If you don't stop this nonsense
right now, we'll tie you up!
Really now!
Zenitsu!
Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?
So you did come up the mountain after all!
T-Tanjirou...
Tanjirou! Listen to me, will ya?
I got bit by this stinky spider
and the venom hurt like crazy, y'hear?
And that girl's been yelling at me all this time!
I hate my life!
Hey, get away from me.
I've got nothing to do with this.
Zenitsu, did you get smaller or something?
I almost got turned into a spiderling.
I've got stumps for limbs now.
Is that right?
Where's Inosuke?
Have you seen Murata?
I don't know this Murata bloke,
but Inosuke's right next to me.
Hey, you're right!
He's been here all this time!
I didn't notice!
Inosuke! I'm so glad you're okay!
I'm so glad you're all right!
I'm so sorry! I couldn't come rescue you!
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Paper! Paper! Do something about this!
Your voice...
Is that you, Inosuke?
Wipe it! Hey!
I heard he lost his voice or something.
Do you hear me? Hey!
I don't know all the fine details,
but I heard he, like, got whooped in the neck.
So when he yelled at the top of his lungs afterwards,
it did a number on his throat.
He's all depressed now, so he's all meek.
That seriously cracks me up!
Why are you cackling in such
a creepy way all of a sudden?
What's going on?
I'm sorry for being so weak.
Hang in there, Inosuke!
It's not like you to get depressed!
Come on, you did well! You're awesome!
I'm just so happy that you're alive!
Did I take my morning meds?
Did you see me take them?
Someone? Did anyone see?
Somebody? Did anyone?!
Zenitsu...
Inosuke...
Thank goodness.
You made it out alive.
It's all right now.
They said you could use this room, Nezuko.
Ow, ow, ow!
I really got roughed up on Mt. Natagumo.
It hurts a lot.
To be honest, it hurts like crazy.
Nezuko...
Thanks for protecting me on the mountain.
Who would've guessed that not only you,
but Master Urokodaki and Mr. Tomioka, as well...
They're all risking their lives for us.
They're all taking care of us.
I...
need to get stronger.
Even today,
the Master more or less saved both of us.
That man's voice...
It was soothing in a mysterious way.
Just listening to him speak made my head feel mellow.
I wonder what kind of person he is.
Oh, right.
You're sleep-deprived, aren't you?
I'm hurting, and this is tough,
but I've gotta keep on fighting.
Because...
I'll be a grown man one day.
And then,
I'll become old and die.
you, as a demon, will end up all alone.
That would be too lonely, wouldn't it, Nezuko?
I promise I'll make you human again, okay?
Just as you've all reported,
the demons' carnage has increased more than ever.
Meaning that the threat to human life
is greater than it's ever been.
We'll have to bolster the ranks of the Demon Slayers.
What do you all think?
The incident on Mt. Natagumo made it crystal clear.
The calibre of Demon Slayers has
nose-dived to unbelievable levels.
Most of them are useless.
The trainers must be blind.
You'd think they could at least tell
if someone's competent or not.
Well, that kid today sure seemed competent.
He did land that grandiose blow on you,
Shinazugawa. He's got potential.
The more the human population increases,
the harder it becomes to control and unify them.
Not to mention that the times have changed
considerably since the previous era.
Other than those who've had their loved ones
brutally massacred and joined the Slayers,
or those of distinguished pedigree
who have hunted demons for generations,
to ask anyone to harness such resolve and
drive to produce results would be cruel.
Still, considering that boy ran into a
Blood Moon so soon after becoming a Demon Slayer,
he may have the power to draw them!
Even we rarely get the chance to confront one!
It makes me envious!
Agreed.
But the fact that a Waning Blood Moon
took such drastic action
probably means that Muzan is
nowhere near Mt. Natagumo.
After all, as in the case of Asakusa,
whenever Muzan wishes to hide something,
he creates a clever diversion to throw us off.
It's really quite frustrating.
But those demons are still freely devouring humans,
gaining strength and living on as they do.
For the sake of those who have perished,
there is only one thing left for us to do.
I believe that among you Hashiras
who are present today,
I've assembled the finest unit since the
First Breathing swordsmen of the feudal era.
Uzui Tengen.
Rengoku Kyoujurou.
Kochou Shinobu.
Kanroji Mitsuri.
Tokitou Muichirou.
Himejima Gyoumei.
Shinazugawa Sanemi.
Iguro Obanai.
Tomioka Giyuu.
My children,
I look forward to your success.
Kibutsuji Muzan,
I swear I'll defeat you if it's the last thing I do.
We will bring you down without fail.
I still find it hard to believe that
some demons don't attack humans.
It must be a miracle or something.
If you're gonna go there, then us trying
to find a clue about Kibutsuji is...
Well, what you call a "millennial miracle"!
That's a typical grandiose idea if ever I heard one!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I hear that the Master is
the 97th leader of the Demon Slayers!
To ensure we don't squander this opportunity,
us Hashira need to be the glue
that holds the Demon Slayers together!
Are you mentally prepared for that, Sound Hashira?
You don't have to remind me, Fire Hashira!
Next, Episode 24, "Rehabilitation Training"!