No way...
My sword!
Holy shit!
This guy's on a whole 'nother level!
He's head and shoulders above the rest!
He sliced through that
tough-as-nails monster like tofu!
Amazing! Amazing! Simply amazing!
Who is this guy?
Damn, I still have goosebumps!
Hey, you!
Fight me, Mismatched Haori!
You beat that Blood Moon!
And now I'm gonna beat you!
That's how it works!
And once I've done that...
That'll make me the strongest!
Get back to training, you buffoon.
The f—
That thing didn't even compare
to an actual Blood Moon.
You couldn't even figure that out?
Sure I could!
I never thought that dumbass
was a Blood Moon, either!
Tanjirou was the one that said he was a Blood Moon!
All I did was repeat what he said, got it?
What the hell? He tied me up?
Whoa, he's quick...
What a speed demon.
Hey, wait! Get back 'ere!
If you can't even realise the state you're in,
you have no business on the battlefield.
I can't hear you!
Stop mumbling and walking so fast!
I told you to get back 'ere, punk!
Let me go right now!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Yoo-hoo!
Are you all right?
Gramps...
Whoever might you be calling "Gramps"?
I saw Gramps just now.
He told me not to give up.
That would've been your life
flashing before your eyes.
There's a theory that suggests that you
see such images right before dying
because your brain is searching through
your memories for a way to avoid death.
Well, it's not like I can confirm that,
since I've never experienced it myself.
You did an outstanding job slowing down
the venom with your breathing.
You would've become a spiderling
ages ago if you didn't hang in there.
I'll administer an antidote now, okay?
Hurry up! Over here!
Can we get them down?
Be careful, okay?
Great news! They're still alive!
My sword was cut in half!
I can't believe it!
The webs this boy controls are even tougher
than the body of that other demon!
Master Urokodaki, Mr. Haganezuka,
please forgive me!
Due to my inexperience,
my sword has now broken!
This isn't the time to worry about that!
Think! Think!
If I can't cut through the webs,
I'll have to go for his body instead!
It's hopeless!
I can't break through.
It's like those webs have a life of their own!
He's obviously toying with me,
but I'm still getting overwhelmed!
Well?
Do you still refuse to take back those words?
Fine.
In that case, I'll slash you to ribbons.
I can't dodge them!
Nezuko!
I'm sorry you had to protect me!
That girl was hidden in his box,
but she has the aura of a demon!
You...
Is that...
That girl...
Is she your sibling?
What's it to you?
These wounds are so deep!
Her left hand's about to fall off!
Hurry up and heal!
Siblings...
Siblings.
The sister has become a demon.
R-Rui?
And yet, she still stays by his side.
The sister protected her brother.
She risked her own life!
That's a genuine bond!
I want it!
W-Wait!
Please, wait!
I'm your elder sister!
Please don't desert me!
Shut your mouth!
None of you ever managed to
fulfil the roles bestowed upon you.
Not even a single time.
W-Wait...
I was the elder sister you wanted, wasn't I?
Please let me redeem myself!
If you want to atone, kill the people
wandering over the mountain.
Once you've done that,
I'll forgive you for what just transpired.
I-I understand.
I'll kill them.
Boy...
Boy, let's have a chat.
Come on out.
Boy?
Chat?
You see, I was really moved.
Seeing the bond you two share gave me chills.
I doubt there are any words in the world
that can describe how I felt.
And yet, the only fate left for you is to die by my hand.
It'd be sad if that came to pass, right?
But there's an option left for you.
A single option that lets you escape that outcome.
That sister of yours...
Hand her over to me.
If you hand her over without a struggle,
I will at least spare your life.
What the hell are you saying?
From today onward, that sister
of yours shall be my little sister.
You didn't actually think I'd agree to that, right?
Nezuko isn't some item you trade around.
She's a living being with her own will.
She will never become your sister!
It's fine. You have nothing to worry about.
I'll forge a bond between us.
I'm stronger than her,
so I will forge a bond using terror.
I'll teach her what happens if she defies me.
I've had enough of this crazy talk!
Using terror to shackle someone hand and foot
isn't what a true family bond is like!
You'll never get what you want
if you don't fix up that misunderstanding!
You're so irritating.
Could you keep your voice down, please?
We just can't see eye to eye, can we?
I'll never hand over Nezuko to the likes of you!
That's fine, I suppose.
I'll just have to kill you.
Not if I take your head first!
Now that's the spirit!
I'd love to see you try.
Let's see if you can even lay a scratch on a Blood Moon!
In a family,
the father holds a certain degree of responsibility.
The mother has her own responsibilities as well.
The parents care for their offspring,
and the elder siblings protect the younger ones.
No matter what.
Even at the cost of their own lives.
The way I see it, if you can't fulfil your role,
there's no reason for you to live.
What about you?
Do you understand your role?
Your role is to relinquish your sister to me
and remove yourself from the picture.
If you can't do that, you have no reason to live.
Since you can't defeat me.
Waning Five.
I already had a feeling since he was so strong.
This kid is a genuine Blood Moon!
Cutting through those webs won't be easy.
What do I do?
If his neck is as tough as those webs,
I won't stand a chance with my broken sword!
I don't like that fiery look in your eyes.
It's borderline foolish.
You don't really think you can defeat me, do you?
Nezuko!
There you go. She's in my custody now.
Do you finally understand your role?
Let her go!
Had you only done as you were told,
I would've at least spared your life.
She's gone!
Nezuko!
Stop that hollering.
She's a demon. A little scratch won't kill her.
But it looks like I'll have to teach her a lesson after all.
I'm going to let her bleed for a while.
If she still doesn't learn to be docile,
I'll just leave her like that until daybreak
and let her roast a bit.
Let go of Nezuko!
Look,
I may be mistaken, but...
You didn't think you could lop off my head
simply by getting close to me, did you?
Fine by me. Here.
Give it your best shot.
The blade won't go through!
See?
Didn't I tell you?
You don't stand a chance against me.
My body's sturdier than any of my webs.
If you can't even cut through those,
there's no way in hell you'll chop off my head.
H-He's strong...
His power's on a completely different level
from any demon I've faced so far!
So this is a Blood Moon's power.
The power of a demon with a
high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood.
You're so loud.
Could you shut up for a bit?
Stop that!
I'm your brother now.
Enough of that infernal wailing.
Calm down! Don't let your anger get the best of you!
You'll play right into his hands!
Did she pass out?
She's asleep?
Something feels off about her.
She's different from other demons somehow.
Interesting.
Concentrate!
Get your breathing under control!
Unleash your strongest and most decisive form!
Total Concentration!
You still don't realise it's futile?
Water Breathing!
Tenth Form!
οὐροβόρος
The Wheel of Life!
I did it! I cut through the webs!
He's gaining more and more force with each rotation.
This could spell trouble.
I can do it!
If I close the distance between us, I can beat him!
You didn't think that I've been
going all-out this whole time, did you?
Blood Arts!
Cutting Gossamer Cage!
I've had enough of you.
Farewell.
No way!
I can't cut through these!
I haven't gotten enough spin yet!
These webs give off an entirely different scent!
But I can't afford to lose here!
I'm gonna die!
I'll lose!
I...
Dad...
Tanjirou.
Breathe.
Get your breathing under control
and become the Fire God.
Tanjirou.
Look.
It's your father's dance.
Our family works with fire,
so to ward off injuries and disasters,
we offer this dance to the Fire God,
along with our prayers, on New Year's Day.
Hey, Mom.
How can Dad dance in the snow
for so long when he's so frail?
I bet my lungs would freeze.
I use a special way of breathing.
It invigorates you, no matter how much you move.
Breathing?
That's right.
If you can master the correct way to breathe,
you'll be able to dance forever, too.
The cold won't bother you, either.
Tanjirou.
If nothing else, make sure at least that dance
and these earrings get passed down to you.
Promise me.
Dance for the Fire God!
Waltz!
My webs!
Don't stop!
Keep going!
If you stop now,
the whiplash from forcibly switching
between breathing forms will kick in!
Once that happens,
you won't be able to move for a while!
That's why you have to finish it now!
Run!
You have to protect Nezuko!
This guy!
There it is! The opening thread!
You've gotta take him down now!
Even if
it means getting cut down alongside him!
Nezuko.
Wake up, Nezuko.
You have to save your brother.
I know you can do it, Nezuko.
Do your best.
Please, Nezuko.
Or your brother will be killed!
Blood Arts!
Blood Burst!
No way!
My webs were incinerated?!
No one will ever sever
the bond
between us!
I wonder why I suddenly remembered
the Dance for the Fire God right then.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks to that, I was able to
cut through that demon's neck!
Thank you, too, Nezuko!
This week, I have a Taisho secret
about the Kamado family!
After every festival, Mom and Dad
would always toast rice crackers for us.
Those were the good times,
making loud cracking noises while we ate them!
Thanks, Nezuko. This isn't the time
to bask in memories, huh?
Next, Episode 20, "Pretend Family"!
Did I actually defeat a Blood Moon?