When I close my eyes, I can still see it
me wo tojite omoidasu
Those times long gone which I held so dear
sugisarishi ano koro wo
But I can’t go back, can’t rewind time
modorenai kaerenai
And now the darkness keeps spreading around me
hirogatta fukai yami
I can’t go back, can’t rewind time
modorenai kaerenai
Now only darkness remains around me
ima wa tada fukai yami
But then I hear a gentle laugh
nakitakunaru you na
Bringing tears to my eyes
yasashii oto
In the midst of this painful journey it says
donna ni kurushikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Don’t give up!"
susume
"Keep living on!"
Carrying me past the despair
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how much I might still lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
I have no choice but to continue living on
ikiteiku shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
There’s something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
No matter how much I might still lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
I have no choice but to continue living on
ikiteiku shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
There’s something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
This is the fate I’ve been entrusted with
ware ni kasu itaku wo
I’ve made up my mind, so I have to follow through
unmei to kakugo suru
I might struggle as it tries to tear me down
doro wo name agaitemo
But I can’t ignore this tiny invisible thread
me ni mienu hosoi ito
It connects me to a gentle smile
nakitaku naru you na
Bringing tears to my eyes
yasashii oto
In the midst of this frustrating journey it says
donna ni kuyashikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
A song in my heart
utae
Carries me past the despair
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how painful it might be
kizutsuitemo kizutsuitemo
I have no choice but to get back on my feet
tachiagaru shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
There’s something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru