When I close my eyes, it's like I'm right there
me wo tojite omoidasu
All the times long gone that I held so dear
sugisarishi ano koro wo
But I can’t turn back the hands of time
modorenai kaerenai
As the darkness spreads all around me
hirogatta fukai yami
I can’t turn back the hands of time
modorenai kaerenai
As the darkness spreads all around me
hirogatta fukai yami
I find myself reduced to tears
nakitakunaru you na
As I hear a gentle voice
yasashii oto
It cuts through all my pain just to say:
donna ni kurushikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Don’t give up!"
susume
"Live on!"
Leave your despair behind
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how much I still have to lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
Living on is still my only choice
ikiteiku shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
I have somebody to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
No matter how much I still have to lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
Living on is still my only choice
ikiteiku shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
I have somebody to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
This is the fate I’ve been entrusted with
ware ni kasu itaku wo
I’ve made up my mind, so I have to follow through
unmei to kakugo suru
I might struggle as it tries to tear me down
doro wo name agaitemo
But I can’t lose sight of the thread of fate
me ni mienu hosoi ito
I find myself reduced to tears
nakitaku naru you na
As I hear a gentle voice
yasashii oto
It cuts through my frustration to say:
donna ni kuyashikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Stand up!"
mukae
"Don't back down!"
Despair can't stop you now
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how much it may hurt
kizutsuitemo kizutsuitemo
Getting up is still my only choice
tachiagaru shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
I have somebody to protect
mamoru mono ga aru