Rui!
What are you doing?
You know you're not supposed to be outside!
I've always been very frail,
ever since I was a child.
I was never able to run.
Even walking was a struggle.
That was, until Lord Muzan appeared.
You pitiful thing. Let me save you.
My parents weren't happy about it.
Because at the cost of a strong body,
I could never see the sun again.
I also had to start devouring humans.
What have you done?!
What on earth have you done?
Rui!
Long ago, I heard a wonderful story.
About a father who died saving his drowning child.
I was deeply moved.
Such astounding parental love.
And such a powerful bond, too.
The father who drowned in the river
had fulfilled his role as a parent.
And yet,
for some reason, my parents...
My own parents tried to
kill me.
All my mother did was sob,
not even lifting a finger to protect me.
They must've been imposters.
The bond between us wasn't real.
I'm sorry...
She's saying something.
She's still alive?
...for not giving you a strong, healthy body.
I'm so sorry.
Those were my mother's last words as she passed away.
She's dead.
It's all right, Rui!
We'll be following you soon.
I was so enraged that my father had tried
to kill me that his words went over my head.
But in that moment,
I realised that he meant to die with me
to atone for my sin of having murdered another.
It was a genuine bond.
And that night,
I severed it with my own two hands.
Even so,
Lord Muzan gave me words of encouragement.
This was your parents' fault for refusing to accept you.
Take pride in your strength.
I had no choice but to look at it that way.
I couldn't bear the weight of what I'd done.
Even knowing that I had only myself to blame...
Day after day, I missed my parents
so much that I could barely stand it.
Even after creating a fake family,
that feeling of emptiness wouldn't go away.
Since I was always the most powerful,
there was no one who could protect me...
No one who could shield me...
The stronger I became,
the less I remembered from the time I was human.
I was losing sight of what it was I wanted to do.
Seeking a bond that I could never have.
It was simply out of my reach,
no matter how I strained to get my hands on it.
That small body
gives off the scent of overwhelming grief.
So warm.
Hands as warm and gentle as sunlight.
Now I remember as clear as day.
What I wanted to do was apologize.
I'm sorry.
I was... Everything was my fault.
I hope you can forgive me.
But since I've killed so many people,
I'm going to Hell, aren't I?
Father...
Mother...
I can't go to the same place as you, can I?
That's not true.
Even if it's to Hell, we'll be going together.
Rui...
Father...
Mother...
Rui...
No matter where you go, we'll be with you.
It was all...
Everything was my fault!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Don't waste your sympathy on
a demon that has devoured humans.
It doesn't matter if it looks like a child.
It's still a hideous monster that's lived for decades.
To avenge the people who were killed,
to make sure there are no more victims,
I'll bring my blade down on any
demon's neck without mercy!
But as for those for whom
being a demon meant despair,
those who regretted their actions,
I will never trample over them!
Because even demons used to
be human at some point!
They were once human, like you and I!
Please step off of him!
They're not hideous monsters at all!
Demons are hopeless creatures!
They're tragic creatures!
You're...
Oh my?
For whatever reason could you
be getting my way, Tomioka?
Weren't you the one who told me man
and demon could never become friends?
How should I put this?
This is exactly why
nobody likes you, y'know.
Man, Lady Kochou's antidote is really effective!
Yeah. And all it took was one look
at the situation to finish preparing it!
She's truly amazing.
That goes for him, too.
Oh, that guy?
Since he defeated the demon,
the poison's circulation slowed a bit.
All right! This should do it!
Looking good!
Chances are, they'll all pull through.
Still, I'd like to wrap things up quickly
and leave this place as soon as possible, wouldn't you?
Yeah, same here.
I mean, this place really, really stinks!
Now, now, Tomioka,
please move out of the way.
I'm not...
I'm not disliked by people.
Ah, I apologize. You have yet to realise
what people think of you, huh?
That was uncalled for. Please forgive me.
Little boy!
Yes?!
You're protecting a demon there.
I don't want to hurt you,
so please get out of the way.
Y-You're mistaken!
Well, you're not, but...
She's my little sister!
She's my little sister, so... You see...
Is that right? Poor thing.
In that case,
I shall use a gentle toxin to kill her,
so she won't suffer, all right?
Can you move?
If you can't, force yourself to.
Take your sister and make a run for it.
Tomioka...
Sorry for the trouble!
Thank you very much!
Isn't that against the Demon Slayers' rules?
My whole body is aching! It's so painful!
I want to scream from the pain!
Deal with it!
Deal with it! Deal with it!
Does this mean I'll have to quit the Demon Slayers?
Even if she's my sister,
there's no way they'd let a
Demon Slayer travel with a demon!
I see you're taking this seriously, Tomioka.
Who would've thought a Hashira
would ever defend a demon?
Unfortunately for you, I have no intention
of joining you in stalling for time.
And with that, adieu.
Is that your attempt at catching up with me?
I don't mind if you want to try stopping me,
but don't forget about the other one!
Don't stop!
Keep moving!
I've got to get as far away as I can!
Not good!
What happened?
It took all I had to keep running!
Nezuko!
A Demon Slayer!
Run, Nezuko!
Run! Make a run for it!
Don't get caught no matter what!
Hurry—
She shrunk and turned into a child?
All she does is run away. She's not even attacking me.
But why?
No need to ponder it.
My only job is to slay this demon.
Tomioka?
Earth to Tomioka.
Since the purpose of my attack was to
slay a demon, and therefore justified,
I don't believe it could be construed
as a violation of the rules.
But we can't say the same about your actions, can we?
You're actively interfering with my duties.
Just what might your intentions be here?
Don't you have anything to say for yourself?
This is your final warning.
Give me a reason at least.
If I'm remembering this right, it was two years ago...
Please spare me the long, rambly backstory.
Are you doing this out of spite?
Are you perhaps still angry at me for
pointing out why nobody likes you?
Message! Message!
I bring a message from headquarters!
Tanjirou and Nezuko are to be
taken back to headquarters alive!
Tanjirou and the demon, Nezuko,
are to be taken back to headquarters alive!
Tanjirou, dressed in a checkered haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a female demon with a bamboo muzzle!
Bring them back! Bring them back!
Are you Nezuko?
Tanjirou, dressed in a checkered haori,
with a scar on his forehead!
Nezuko, a female demon with a bamboo muzzle!
Bring them back! Bring them back!
He has a scar on his forehead.
All right, take him into custody.
Look. His jawbone seems to be broken, doesn't it?
I feel bad about tying him up.
Wh-Who the hell is this?
I don't know.
A demon? Couldn't be, right?
Is it a human?
He's wearing our uniform's trousers.
Oh hey, this is a mask! He's a human!
All right, let's bring him in.
This guy's really banged up!
Why's he strung up like this?
There was nothing I could do...
I couldn't even kill a single demon on my own!
Y'know what?
Maybe I'm not that strong...
They wrapped us up like mummies.
Who are these people?
They seem to be cleaning the place up really efficiently.
And that girl over there...
Isn't she the girl from the Final Selection?
She has the same kind of hair ornament
as the lady who wrapped us up.
Should we bring them
to the Butterfly Mansion?
Yes, bring all of the wounded to our place.
I'll be hunting down the demons in the area
so you can work uninterrupted.
Actually, I've heard of them.
The cleanup crew, the Kakushi.
They're the unit that cleans up after
the Demon Slayers battle demons.
They say that most of its members are people
who have no swordsmanship skills.
The sun's coming up.
Wake up.
Hey, I told you to wake up!
Wake...
Hey! Hey, you!
Come on, dude! C'mon!
Are you gonna nap all day?!
Rise and shine already, will ya?
You're in the presence of the Hashira!
We've been teaming up on missions
quite frequently as of late, haven't we?
Could you at least answer me, please?
Are you perhaps still angry at me for
pointing out why nobody likes you?
Don't you have anything to say?
Time for a Taisho secret.
Apparently, Kochou can't stand cats,
dogs, or any kind of furry creature.
You finally open your mouth,
and that's the first thing you say?
You didn't deny it, so does that mean it's true?
That lack of tact is exactly why nobody likes you!
People...
"...do like me?"
Any answer but that one please.
Next, Episode 22, "The Master of the Mansion".