South-south-east!
Your next location is south-south-east!
I heard you the first time!
I know already. Give me a break and pipe down!
I'm begging you!
I got the message, so please!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
I could meet my demise at any time, y'know!
That's why I want you to marry me!
Please! I'm begging you!
Wh-What's going on over there?
What on earth?
Huh?
I beg you!
There's nobody else!
You're all I have!
I see! Gotcha!
I'll see what I can do!
Please help me! Please marry me!
I beg—
What do you think you're doing
in the middle of the road?
Can't you see that she wants no part of you?
And stop causing trouble for your sparrow, too!
That uniform!
You're that guy from the Final Selection!
I don't know anyone even remotely like you! No one!
But we met! Don't you remember?
You're the one with issues! Like your memory!
All right, I've dealt with this issue.
You have nothing to worry about anymore.
Yes, thank you so much!
Hey!
Stay out of my way!
That girl is going to marry me!
Because she's in love w—
Hey! Ouch! That hurts! Stop it!
Stop it! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
P-Please, calm down!
When did I ever say I'm in love with you?
You were crumpled up on
the side of the road and looked ill!
All I did was call out to you!
You mean you didn't reach out to me
out of love because you were worried?
I already have a fiancé, so not on your life!
Since you're so full of energy,
you must be fine now, right?
Have a very nice day!
W-Wait, come back!
Come...
Look, cut it out already!
Wh-Why'd you get in my way?
This has nothing to do with you!
What's with that look on your face?!
Stop it!
Why are you staring at me like I'm
some inhuman creature or something?!
Hey, you! Take some responsibility!
It's your fault I missed out on getting married!
Geez, say something!
Listen up! I'm gonna die soon!
My next job will be the death of me!
Thing is, I'm a complete and utter pansy, 'kay?
Don't underestimate me!
You've gotta protect me until I get married, y'hear me?
My name is Kamado Tanjirou!
Is that so? My apologies!
I'm Agatsuma Zenitsu!
Please save me, Tanjirou!
What do you mean, save you?
What was your reason for
picking up the blade, Zenitsu?
Why are you acting so blatantly shameless?
Sure are a harsh one, aren't you?!
I got swindled by some woman
and racked up all this debt!
The old geezer who took it over
for me was a cultivator!
I went through hellish training day after day!
It was so bad that I thought I'd be better off dead!
I was hoping I'd die during the Final Selection,
but since I was "fortunate" enough to survive,
I'm still going through hell every day!
I'm so scared! Scared! Scared! Beyond scared!
I just know I'm gonna get gobbled up
by some demon sooner or later!
My brains are gonna get sucked out
through my ears while I'm still alive!
No! God, no!
Somebody, save me!
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
You feeling better?
Yeah.
Now that I've calmed down, I'm getting hungry.
Don't you have any food on you?
Nope.
Here, I've got this.
Want it?
Ah, thank you.
You're not eating, Tanjirou?
No. That's all I had.
Here.
At least take half.
You sure?
Thanks!
I get what you mean when you say
you're scared of demons,
but you can't stir up trouble for your sparrow.
Was it upset?
How could you tell?
Well, he says you're always whining
about not wanting to work,
always hitting on girls, and that you snore loudly.
He's had it up to here with you!
That's what he told me.
He did?
You can understand what he's saying?
You're lying, right? You're just trying to trick me!
Hurry! Hurry!
Tanjirou, Zenitsu, get going!
Both of you are to head over to your next destination!
Run! Run, Tanjirou, Zenitsu!
Why is that crow talking?!
Hey, Tanjirou,
on second thought, there's no way I'll make it.
Even if I tag along, it's not like I'll be useful.
The demon scent is gradually getting stronger.
There's something up ahead.
What's that?
I can smell blood.
But this particular scent...
You smell something?
Something I've never smelled before.
I don't know about that,
but do you hear that sound?
Also, are we gonna work together after all?
Sound?
K-Kids...
I wonder what's wrong.
Hey, what are you doing all the way out here?
They seem really spooked.
Okay, you wanna see something cool?
Ta-dah!
It's a tame sparrow!
See? Isn't he cute?
Please tell me.
Did something happen?
Is this your house?
No. No, it isn't.
This...
This is...
A-A monster's...
house!
Our big brother got taken away.
While we were walking down the road late at night,
a monster came up out of nowhere.
It didn't even look at us, just our brother.
And they went inside that house, right?
Yeah.
And you two followed them here?
You did well!
Great job!
We followed his blood trail.
Since he got hurt!
Hurt...
Don't worry!
We're going to defeat the bad guy
and rescue your brother!
Really? You will?
Yeah.
I promise!
Tanjirou...
What's this drumming sound?
This creepy sound hasn't stopped at all.
Is it some kind of drum?
Sound?
I don't hear anything.
Don't look!
Are you all right?
Stay with me!
The wound is so deep.
Is this...
Even though... I got out...
Even though I made it out...
Made it outside.
Still...
Am I gonna die?
Am I still gonna die?
He's gone...
He must've been in a lot of pain.
He must've suffered a lot.
Tanjirou, by any chance, is that guy these kids'...
We couldn't save him.
If only we'd gotten here a little sooner,
we might've been able to do something.
Sorry, but...
Is this man your...
H-He isn't our brother.
He was wearing a persimmon-coloured kimono.
I see.
It captured more than one person.
I promise I'll give you a proper
resting place when I return.
Forgive me, please!
All right.
Zenitsu, we're going in!
We're the only ones who can help them now.
That so?
Okay.
Hey, c'mon! What are you scowling at me for?!
Fine, fine, I'll go with you!
I'm not trying to force you.
I said I'll go!
In case of emergency, I'm leaving this box with you.
Even if something happens, you two will be safe.
We'll be back soon.
Tanjirou!
Hey, Tanjirou!
You'll protect me, right?
You will protect me, right?
Zenitsu, I hate to put you on the spot, but...
I've got a broken rib and leg from my previous battle.
And neither are fully healed yet.
So—
The hell you mean, "broken"?
Don't go breaking any bones on me, y'hear?!
There's no way you can protect me
if you've got fractures!
I-I-I'm gonna die!
What am I gonna do?
I'm screwed!
Screwed! Screwed! Screwed!
Broken bones? How could you?
I'm a dead man now!
The odds of me dying have
increased to ninety percent!
I'm as good as dead! Dead! Dead!
Zenitsu, quiet down!
You'll be fine!
Don't sugarcoat it!
I'm not! I can tell. Zenitsu, you're—
Oh, no!
You shouldn't be here!
M-Mister, we heard scratching from inside that box!
E-Even then, it pains me that you left it behind!
I mean, it's more precious to me than my own life!
Sorry! My butt...
The room changed.
No.
Were we moved instead?
To the beat of that drum, perhaps?
Sorry you got separated from your brother.
But I'll make sure to protect you.
And Zenitsu is gonna protect your brother.
Don't worry!
What's your name?
Teruko.
Is that right? Teruko?
That's a fine name you h—
Of all the scents enveloping this house,
this one is the most intense!
This demon has devoured a whole slew of humans!
He's clearly the master of this mansion!
I'm gonna die!
I'm as good as dead, I'm telling you!
I got split up from Tanjirou!
Teruko!
No, no, no!
Don't make any loud sounds!
If you yell and the bad guy hears you,
it won't end pretty!
Come on, let's go outside!
Wha—
Why outside?
Are you trying to run away?
All this constant yammering about dying...
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Clinging onto a younger person...
Don't you feel pathetic?
What are you carrying that sword for, anyway?
Your words cut deep.
You've got it all wrong!
I'm basically useless here anyway,
Let go of me!
so I'm gonna summon a grown-up here, okay?
This isn't something us kids can fix ourselves!
You've gotta be kidding me! Are you serious?!
Wasn't the front door right here?
Where'd our way out go?
I mean, this door was...
Is it this one?
How about this one?
What about this one?
It's a monster!
The hell? What's with that look in your eyes?
Quit looking at me like that!
If it hadn't been...
If it hadn't been for their meddling...
Teruko, try to keep in your scream.
The room's going to change,
so don't run into the hallway.
Get back and hide behind the shelves.
Curses, curses!
Thanks to them, he got away!
When he was my prey!
Why is it? Why do they all keep
barging into someone else's home?
It's infuriating.
That was my prey!
The prey I discovered on my own turf!
Curse them!
Hey, you! Over here!
I'm a Demon Slayer!
My rank's Mizunoto, and my name is Kamado Tanjirou!
I'm going to slay you right here and now!
A rareblood child I found myself!
Got him!
Teruko!
The tatami floors are on the sides now!
The room's been flipped!
So that's his Blood Arts!
The entire mansion is this demon's territory!
What's this?
An odd scent is wafting this way.
It's not a demon's!
Chargin' through!
I'm chargin' through!
Wh-Who's this guy?
Why is he wearing a boar's hide?
And why is he wielding Sun Blades?
All right, you damn monster.
Die on the battlefield and serve as my springboard!
Die so I can get stronger and soar even higher!
Infuriating!
Here goes...
I'm chargin' through!
Say, Tanjirou,
I think that girl you forcibly pulled away
from me might love me after all.
What are you talking about?
It was obvious she wasn't into you!
That's not true! She might've said all those things,
but maybe she wanted me to chase after her!
I think there was love in her eyes when she slapped me,
and then all the other times she hit me,
she was really putting her heart
into it every single time!
If that isn't a sign of t-t-true love,
I don't know what is!
Say something, will ya?
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I hear that Zenitsu gets self-conscious
in front of girls, and his heart starts fluttering.
Not like I can help it!
Girls are so adorable, soft, and smell so nice!
Oh man, now that I'm thinking about them,
I just remembered that girl again!
If I make it out of this house, I'm gonna go
straight after her and tie the knot!
Next, Episode 12, "The Boar Bares
Its Fangs, Zenitsu Sleeps"!
Don't just ignore me, Tanjirou!