Wake up.
Hey, wake up already!
Wake... Are you serious?
Hey, you!
C'mon, dude!
Dude!
Are you gonna sleep all day?!
Open your damn eyes already!
How droll.
I heard he was a Slayer with a demon in tow,
so I was expecting someone with grandeur, but...
He just looks like your average bloke.
And now, we'll put this boy on trial!
I see!
He's been protecting his sister this entire time,
even though she's a demon...
What beautiful sibling love!
How brave!
Wh-Who are you peop—
Don't open your mouth yet, you numbskull!
Have you no clue who stands before you?
You're in the presence of the Hashira!
Hashira?
What's a Hashira?
What's he talking about?
Who are these people?
Where am I?
You're currently at the
Demon Slayers' headquarters.
And you're about to be put on trial,
Kamado Tanjirou.
First things first, let's go over
the crimes you're being accused o—
There's no need for a trial!
Defending a demon is a
clear violation of the code!
It's well within our rights to
handle his execution!
Let's behead him along with that demon!
I'd be glad to decapitate him,
with absolute brilliance.
I'll show you the most grandiose
blood splashes the world has ever seen.
I'm talking max grandeur.
You'd kill such a cute little kid?
That pains my heart! It's just too much!
What a pitiful sight this boy is.
The poor soul...
I pity him for having been born at all.
Um, what was that cloud shape again?
What was it called again?
Where's Nezuko?
Nezuko!
C'mon now, buddy.
Where do you think you're looking?
The Hashira are in front of you.
They're the nine highest-ranking
swordsmen in the Demon Slayers.
The Hashira...
Let's put him out of his misery.
Yeah, lets! But with full grandeur.
Dude!
Nezuko...
Nezuko, where are you?
Nezuko!
Zenitsu!
Inosuke!
Murata!
Forget about him. What do we do with Tomioka?
Seeing him just standing there unrestrained
puts a heavy weight on my mind.
Based on Kochou's report, Tomioka is just as guilty.
How will we deal with him?
How should we hold him accountable?
What kind of lesson should we teach him?
Don't you have anything to say for yourself, Tomioka?
Because of me, even Tomioka...
Iguro's as serpent-like as ever! Such a nag!
I love how pesky you are!
Meanwhile, Tomioka's keeping
his distance all the way over there!
He's so cute!
Oh, where's the harm?
He came along without resisting.
We can debate a suitable punishment later.
I'm much more interested in
hearing this boy's side of the story.
Why does he act as a Demon Slayer?
And with a demon in tow, at that.
I'd love to hear the reasoning from his own mouth.
Those actions are a clear breach
of the Demon Slayers' code, of course.
You're well aware of that, aren't you?
Kamado Tanjirou...
Why are you travelling with
a demon as a Demon Slayer?
No need to ask.
You can take your time. Just tell us why.
She's...
She's my little—
Let me give you some water.
Your jaw's busted, so please drink slowly.
I've mixed in a painkiller, so you'll feel better soon.
It's not like it heals your wounds,
so you mustn't push yourself.
Well then, Kamado Tanjirou...
That demon is my little sister!
While I was out, a demon attacked my family.
By the time I got home, everyone was dead!
My sister was turned into a demon,
but she's never eaten anyone!
She never has
and never will!
No matter what, she'll never hurt humans!
Spare us your absurd ravings.
It's no wonder you're defending her
if she's a family member.
I can't trust a single word you're saying.
I, for one, don't believe you.
She's been possessed by a demon.
Let us kill this poor child immediately
so that she may be liberated!
Listen to me, please!
I became a swordsman to cure Nezuko!
It's been two years since Nezuko became a demon!
And in all that time, she hasn't eaten a single human!
Your story's spinning in the
most dull way possible, idiot.
Just because she hasn't eaten anyone yet
doesn't mean she never will.
Lip service is cheap.
Prove it with maximum grandeur.
What was that bird called again?
Um...
Excuse me?
I do have my doubts, y'know.
I just can't imagine the Master being
in the dark about this situation.
Do you really think it's okay to
deal with him without his permission?
Shouldn't we at least wait until he arrives?
My sister...
My sister will fight by my side!
She can fight as a Demon Slayer to protect humans!
So please...
Well, well, I see you have some fun brewing here.
That the moron Slayer that had this demon?
Exactly what kinda stunt are you trying to pull here?
Shinazugawa!
You've gained even more gorgeous scars!
This won't do, Master Shinazugawa!
Please, would you mind putting that box down?
Shinobu looks pretty angry! How unusual!
She's so cool!
Shinazugawa, please don't act out of line.
What did you say about that demon, kid?
That she can fight as a
Demon Slayer to protect humans?
You know what we call that?
A total delusion, you moron!
Hashira or not,
I won't let anyone that hurts Nezuko get away with it!
That so? Good for you!
Stop it!
The Master will be arriving soon!
Pardon me.
Damn you!
Even with Tomioka intervening, I'm surprised
he managed to land a blow on Shinazugawa.
If you can't even tell the difference
between a good demon and a bad demon,
you should just quit being a Hashira!
You little...
I'll destroy you!
The Master
has arrived.
So good of you to come,
my beloved children.
The Master
has arrived.
Good morning, everyone.
The weather is splendid today.
I wonder if the sky is blue.
It pleases me that we've made it to our biannual
Hashira Meeting with no personnel changes.
Those scars...
No wait, an illness?
So that man's the Master?
So quick! I couldn't even react!
This...
I am pleased to see you in
good health as well, Master.
I fervently pray for your continued good fortune.
Thank you, Sanemi.
I wanted to be the one to offer
my greetings to the Master!
If I may, Master,
before we start the Hashira Meeting,
would you mind enlightening us
about this swordsman here that has
been accompanied by a demon?
He didn't seem to have a drop of intellect or logic,
but he's speaking so formally now!
Right.
I apologise for startling you all.
Regarding Tanjirou and Nezuko,
I've sanctioned their activities.
I'd also like you all to accept it.
Even if it's what you desire, Master,
I simply cannot agree to it.
I'm grandiosely opposed, as well!
A Demon Slayer travelling with
a demon is unacceptable!
I shall do whatever you wish, Master!
I'm fine either way.
I'll forget anyway...
I won't trust them. No way.
I despise demons with all my heart.
Although I respect you with all my heart,
that's an incomprehensible notion, Master!
I oppose it with everything I've got!
The Demon Slayers' mission is to slay demons.
I request that you punish both Kamado and Tomioka!
The letter.
Yes, Master.
This is a letter we have received from
a former Hashira, Urokodaki Sakonji.
I shall read you an abridged version.
"Please allow Tanjirou to be united
with his little sister, a demon."
"Because of her mental fortitude,"
"Nezuko has not lost her human emotions."
"Even when she was starving,
she never devoured humans,"
"and this remains true more than two years later."
"Although the situation seems somewhat
far-fetched, it is an indisputable fact."
"In the event that Nezuko does assault
a human, Kamado Tanjirou,"
"as well as Urokodaki Sakonji and Tomioka Giyuu,"
"shall atone by committing
ritual suicide by disembowelment."
So what if they commit suicide?
If they have a death wish,
they can rot for all I care!
This doesn't guarantee anything.
Not by a long shot!
Shinazugawa is right!
If she eats a human, we can't reverse that!
We can't bring back the dead!
You do have a point.
In that case...
Master!
We can't guarantee that she won't attack humans.
We can't prove it.
That said,
we also can't prove that she will attack humans.
The fact remains that Nezuko has refrained
from devouring humans for over two years.
Besides that, she has three people
willing to risk their very lives for her.
Those who reject this notion must offer
an even more convincing argument.
Do you all have the will to do so?
Also, there's something I'd like to
relay to you, my children.
Tanjirou here has met Kibutsuji.
No, impossible!
Even when no Hashira has ever
crossed paths with him?
You mean this kid...
What did he look like? What about his abilities?
Where did this take place?
Did you fight him?
What was Kibutsuji doing?
Did you find his stronghold?
Hey, answer me!
Shut up! I asked him first!
First, tell us what his abilities are!
Kibutsuji has sent pursuers after Tanjirou.
Though the purpose may simply be to silence him,
this has also opened him up to your pursuits.
I don't want to squander that chance.
I also believe something's happening to
Nezuko that Kibutsuji never saw coming.
Can you try to understand?
No. I can't, Master.
If it were human, I'd be okay with letting
it live, but a demon is a different story!
Not after all that we, the Demon Slayers,
have gone through in combat!
Not after so many people have lost their lives!
It's unacceptable!
What are you doing?
You're soiling the garden!
Master!
I will prove it to you myself!
The sheer ugliness of a demon!
Sanemi...
Hey, demon!
It's time for breakfast!
Sink your teeth into this!
No need to hold back.
Show us your true colours
and let me obliterate you right here!
Nezuko!
Shinazugawa, there's no reason to do it out in the sun.
The demon won't show its face
unless it's in the shadows.
Master, please forgive this discourtesy.
Stop it!
Rise and shine, demon!
Look, it's the human blood you love so much!
I can't breathe!
Or even move!
Nezuko...!
Imagine, Shinazugawa falling victim
to a head-butt by a mere rookie.
That was a mighty fine head-butt!
Yeah! The sound it made was grandiose!
How painful it must've been...
Praise to Amida Buddha.
But the way that boy stood up
to a Hashira was so brave!
What is this, a free-for-all?
You know I could've dodged it
if Tomioka hadn't gotten in the way!
Excuses, excuses.
I see none of you have changed.
And now, time for a Taisho secret!
The first one among us to speak
gets to greet the Master,
so we all had butterflies in our stomachs
until the Master got here!
Oh, next, Episode 23,
"The Hashira's Meeting".