How shall we go about killing them, I wonder?
I'm bursting with power.
It's all thanks to the blood he shared with us.
We shall be slaying them brutally, naturally.
Get down!
Have you decided how to kill them?
Brutally, of course!
You were spot on, Yahaba!
A building just popped up out of thin air!
The handiwork of a demon adept at hiding objects.
And is the demon hunter accompanied by a demon?
What's going on here?
Isn't this fun?
Still, I have to point this out, Susamaru...
Your way of doing things is too immature.
It's too careless.
You soiled me!
My kimono is all covered in dirt now!
Oh, stop whining!
We found them right away
thanks to my temari, so who cares?
And now we can have tons of fun!
You've gone and covered me in dirt again!
You're so uptight.
Your kimono isn't the least bit dirty.
And besides...
There they are!
A temari?
She caused this much damage
just by throwing around a toy?
That woman...
Is she one of Kibutsuji's minions?
Lady Tamayo!
Yushirou!
Dammit!
Nezuko!
Take the woman sleeping in the back
somewhere safe outside!
It's too dangerous outside!
We have a basement, so take her there!
Understood!
Nezuko!
That's one down!
She smells totally different from
every other demon I've seen so far.
Is it stronger? It's really thick!
It feels so heavy once it enters my lungs!
The demon hunter wearing hanafuda earrings...
That'd be you, huh?
Am I their target?
Miss Tamayo!
Please find a safe place to hide!
I'm the one they're after!
Tanjirou, please don't worry about us
and focus on fighting.
We don't require your protection.
We are demons, remember?
All right.
It's all over for you now!
That temari will only veer if I try to dodge it.
Of the ten forms,
the fastest thrusting technique is...
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Seventh Form!
Droplet Ripple Thrust-curve!
Oh, so your plan's to thrust at it
diagonally to soften the temari's blow?
However...
How can that temari move around like that?
It swerved unnaturally when it struck Yushirou, too!
It's not like it has any special spin to it, and yet...
What's going on?
Yushirou!
La—
Lady Tamayo!
Didn't I tell you?
We shouldn't get involved with that demon hunter!
I told you from the start!
My masking technique is still a work in progress!
I know you're well aware of that yourself!
I may be able to conceal the presence
of buildings and people, and even their scent,
but it's not like I can hide their very existence!
The greater our numbers, the more traces we'll leave,
which increases the odds of Kibutsuji discovering us!
Those demons got so close,
but I didn't catch their scent until they attacked!
So that was the work of Yushirou's Blood Arts, huh?
Those who ruins the time I spend alone with you...
I despise such people!
I despise them with all my heart!
I'll never forgive them!
Wow, look at him blabbering away!
This is fun!
I'm having so much fun!
You should feel honoured to be killed by me,
one of the Twelve Blood Moons!
Twelve Blood Moons?
They serve directly under Kibutsuji!
She grew more arms!
Let's keep playing!
Until the break of dawn!
Until you meet your demise!
If I were to cast my Blood Arts now,
it would affect Tanjirou as well.
And Yushirou needs time
to prepare before he can attack.
But if this goes on...
There it is again!
They changed trajectory
without hitting anything again!
Even if I cut them and they lose speed,
they still end up hitting me anyway!
I can smell two different scents.
There are two demons!
I can locate them with their scent!
But...
Miss Tamayo! Yushirou!
I can't!
I don't have time to cover them!
We'll heal soon enough!
Don't worry about us!
Hey! Dumbass demon hunter!
The arrows show which way they're going.
Focus on dodging the arrows!
Arrows?
For crying out loud, you can't even see them?
I will lend you my sense of sight!
That should at least enable you
to behead that temari woman!
I can see them now!
She was using those arrows to control
the trajectory of the temari!
Thanks, Yushirou!
I can see the arrows now!
Hurry up and beat her, then!
Nezuko!
Let's get outside!
Take care of the demon up in the trees!
I'm your target!
The demon hunter wearing hanafuda earrings...
No doubt about it.
I will deliver your head to our lord!
This is fun!
Nezuko, how much longer will it take?
They're gone!
Water Breathing!
Third Form!
Flowing Dance!
Miss Tamayo!
Do these two have a high
concentration of Kibutsuji's blood?
Most likely.
In that case...
I'm going to be extracting their blood!
I have two favours to ask of you.
One, permission to study your sister's blood.
Two, to retrieve as many blood samples from demons
with a high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood as you can.
A demon with a high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood
means a demon close in strength to Kibutsuji himself.
It won't be easy to extract blood from such demons.
Third Form!
Flowing Dance!
Miss Tamayo!
Do these two have a high
concentration of Kibutsuji's blood?
Most likely.
You think you can extract our blood?
I don't know what you're scheming,
but I won't allow you to do
anything that displeases our lord!
If you think you can extract blood
from us Blood Moons,
then go ahead and try!
Watch your back!
Don't let your guard down for even a second!
If these two really are Blood Moons,
then they're undeniably more formidable than
any other demon you've slain up to this point!
Right!
Understood!
Watch my back, don't let my guard down
for a single second, undeniably...
Until now...
Right! I'll do my best!
Lady Tamayo!
Let's use those two as decoys and escape!
Just kidding!
Don't stir up dirt like that.
It's dirty!
She grew new arms in such a short time!
She regenerates way faster than
the demons I fought during the Final Selection!
I will bring him that head of yours.
Nezuko!
Now then, why don't you two die together?
Are you okay, Nezuko?
Hey, demon hunter!
Take care of that arrow guy!
The three of us will take on that temari woman!
Understood!
Nezuko, don't push yourself too hard, okay?
I'm counting on you.
I swear...
I'm going to extract their blood!
If it means the cure will be
perfected even a minute sooner,
I'll gladly face any demon!
I'll fight and win!
There it is!
The opening thread!
You grimy little imp.
Stay away from me!
The thread snapped?!
It hurts! It...
It seriously hurts!
A technique!
I need to soften my landing
with one of my techniques!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
He's gone?
You hurt Lady Tamayo!
I'll never forgive you for that!
Tamayo?
Hey, Susamaru, the one over there...
Wouldn't that be Tamayo the Fugitive?
She'd make a great souvenir!
Really?
Idiot!
You mustn't kick it!
This is fun!
I'm having so much fun!
Kickball sure is fun.
Yahaba!
You think four heads will be enough to take home?
No. We're taking just two.
The demon hunter and the fugitive.
We have no use for the other two.
Nezuko...
The bleeding isn't stopping instantly.
She recovers so slowly.
This medicine will help heal
your leg straight away, all right?
What do I do?
I can't afford to go down here!
But even if I can see the opening thread,
tracing it will be difficult!
Any move would be pointless
unless I can land my blow with pinpoint accuracy!
If I'm off by even a little,
it won't be strong enough to kill him!
He'll just change the blade's direction
using his arrow ability!
And I hate to say it,
but those eyeballs are really creepy!
Though I hate to say it!
These arrows are so fast!
And they won't disappear until they hit me!
I can't cut them with my sword, either!
The instant my blade touches them,
I get blasted away in the arrow's direction!
What can I do?
Everything's going in the direction I want it to!
Your arm's gonna get twisted right off!
He eluded it by spinning in the same
direction as the Pure Crimson Arrow?
Damn monkey!
I can't take much more of his attacks!
I've gotta fight back!
I need to somehow change the arrow's
direction without touching it directly!
It's about time you died!
Adapt your movement!
First, use the Sixth Form to envelop the arrow!
Then use the footwork of the Third Form
to close in on him!
Twist!
Envelope!
Flowing Maelström Spin!
My sword feels so heavy!
But even so!
Modified Second Form!
Horizontal Water Wheel!
Those are some powerful demons!
Those temari-and-arrow combos
are giving me so much trouble!
Are you hanging in there, Nezuko?
Today's Taisho secret is about these two demons!
Yahaba and Susamaru, those two demons,
met for the first time today.
I hear they became friends
while chatting on the way here.
I can't believe they're so in sync
when they've only just met!
We can't let them beat us!
Nezuko, let's practise our teamwork!
First Form!
Second Form!
Third Form!
Looking good, Nezuko!
Next, Episode 10, "Together Forever"!
I'm leaving that temari woman to you!
Let's fight them together!