Those fox masks!
All of his disciples wear them.
I ate them because of the masks they wore.
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
First Form!
Surface Water Slash!
Urokodaki!
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
My body's crumbling away.
I can't stop it!
Damn it!
I can't believe a demon hunter's face
will be the last thing I'll ever see...
How did it come to this?
I'm so scared. I'm all alone.
Brother, where are you?
I want you to hold my hand again!
Like you always do!
Why?
Why on earth did I eat you, Brother?
Huh?
Wait, who was my brother again?
What a sad scent.
God...
Please...
The next time this man is reborn,
please make sure he doesn't become a demon.
Brother!
Brother! Brother!
Hold my hand, will you?
You're hopeless, you know?
You're such a scaredy-cat.
Sabito, Makomo,
and everyone else who lost their lives...
I won.
You can rest easy now.
I guess you're going home as promised.
Even though you've lost your bodies,
you're returning to Mt. Sagiri.
Back to your beloved Master Urokodaki.
Had I died,
my soul would've made it back there, too.
I want to ask you something.
Is there a way to turn a demon back into a human?
Please tell me!
How can I
turn Nezuko back into a human?
Wisteria?
I made it.
Only four of us?
But there were at least twenty.
I don't see that guy, either.
If I hadn't blacked out back then,
I might've been able to save him.
I'm gonna die. I'm a goner.
Even if I survive now,
I'm gonna die in the end anyway.
Welcome back.
Congratulations.
We're pleased to see that
you have returned safely.
So? What am I supposed to do now?
Where's my sword?
First, we shall issue you all uniforms.
We will take your measurements,
after which your rank will be engraved.
There are ten ranks in all...
Kinoe.
Kinoto.
Hinoe.
Hinoto.
Tsuchinoe.
Tsuchinoto.
Kanoe.
Kanoto.
Mizunoe.
And Mizunoto.
Currently, you are at the lowest rank, Mizunoto.
So? What about our swords?
Today, we will let you select the ore
to be used when forging your blade.
However, the swords will take
ten to fifteen days to complete.
You gotta be kiddin'.
But first...
We will assign each of you your own Kasugai Crow.
Kasugai Crow?
These Kasugai Crows are
primarily used for communication.
"Crow"?
But this is a sparrow!
Don't give me that crap!
Who gives a shit about some stupid crows?
I want a sword, y'hear?
And I want it now!
One of those Demon Slayer swords!
A Colour Changing Sword!
Get your hands off her.
If you don't, I will make you.
Who do you think you are?
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
Let's see you try!
Are you done chatting?
Now then, please select an ore.
You shall choose the ore used to
forge your blade yourself.
Well, not like I'll be alive for long.
They want us to choose,
but how are we supposed to pick?
I don't have any experience working with ores,
so I don't know the difference between them at all.
I don't have a damn clue.
I see.
Five of them survived, huh?
Excellent.
The number of my children has increased again.
I wonder what kinds of swordsmen they'll become.
I was naïve.
I couldn't even talk to a single demon.
They just tried to kill me straight away.
Sorry, Nezuko.
I couldn't find a way
to make you human again.
Even my uniform is heavy.
I want to get home as soon as possible,
but my entire body is aching.
I made it.
Nezuko... Master Urokodaki...
Hey! Nezuko!
You...
You've woken up?
Nezuko!
Why...
Why'd you fall asleep so suddenly?
Why wouldn't you wake up?
I was so worried you would die!
Good job coming back to us alive.
I see. You killed that deformed demon.
Yes.
At last.
I'm truly impressed that you made it back.
Yes.
There are several kinds of demons.
Some demons use special techniques called the
"Demon Blood Arts", granting them supernatural abilities.
You may find yourself facing
these kinds of demons as well from now on.
And battling them will be far more difficult
than anything you've faced so far.
But I'm sure you'll manage just fine, Tanjirou.
Right.
Say...
I think Nezuko's somehow different
from the other demons.
You think it could it be that Whatchamacallit-Arts?
No, I don't think so.
I wouldn't call that an example of a Blood Art.
I'm just taking a guess here,
but it could be that Nezuko's recovering her strength
through sleep rather than by consuming flesh.
I will protect you, Nezuko.
Uh...
My name is Haganezuka.
I have forged Kamado Tanjirou's sword
and am here to deliver it.
I'm Kamado Tanjirou.
Please come in.
This is the Sun Blade.
I'm the one who forged it.
Uhm...
I'll serve you some tea, so please come ins—
The materials for a Sun Blade can be obtained
from the mountain closest to the sun.
Scarlet Crimson Iron Sand and Scarlet Crimson Ore
are used to produce steel that can absorb sunlight.
Wow, is that so?
Mt. Youkou is bathed in sunlight all day long, you see.
You won't find—
You're going to get dirty,
so could you get up for a second?
There he goes again. Never listening to
a single word of what others say...
A clown mask?
Oh, you're a Child of Light, aren't you?
Now that's what I call lucky.
Oh no, I'm the son of Tanjuurou and Kie, not Light.
That isn't what I meant.
See how your hair and eyes are a reddish colour?
When a kid like you is born
into a family that works with fire,
it's considered lucky and a cause for celebration.
Is that so? I had no idea.
There's a good chance this sword will turn red!
Right, Urokodaki?
Yeah.
Come on, hurry up and draw it!
Sun Blades are also known as
"Colour Changing Swords".
They change colour depending on the bearer.
Black!
Black, huh?
Is that bad? Is it not supposed to turn black?
Is it unlucky?
No, not necessarily.
But you rarely see a blade
that's pitch black like this.
And here I was so hoping
I'd get to see a bright red sword!
Damn it!
Ouch! Stop!
Please calm down!
How old do you think you are?!
I'm thirty-seven!
Kamado Tanjirou!
Here are your orders!
It can talk?
Make your way to a town to the northwest!
Young girls have been disappearing there!
Night after night,
adolescent girls have been vanishing!
Hunt down the demon lurking there and kill it!
Kamado Tanjirou, prepare yourself well for this task!
This will be your first assignment as a Demon Slayer!
My first assignment...
Kasugai Crow, say hello to everyone.
I don't take orders from you!
Geez.
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
Forget about that!
It's time for your next mission! Hurry up!
Okay, okay! I get it!
Next, Episode 6,
"The Swordsman and his Demon Companion"!
Hey, you there!
If you miss it, I'll peck you!
Oi!