Are you heading into battle?
Oh, if it isn't Kochou!
A new demon has surfaced,
and the Slayers that confronted him were taken out.
Innocent folk have fallen victim.
We can't ignore this any longer.
Is a Blood Moon responsible for this?
Most likely. It might have even been
one of the Waxing Moons.
Sounds like you've got a tough mission ahead of you.
But I trust I'll have nothing
to worry about if you're in charge.
Kochou, what are you planning?
Why take that head-butting boy in?
You mentioned wanting to add
more Tsuguko to your ranks,
but I'm sure you've got other reasons in mind.
Relax. It's not like I'm gonna gobble him up, right?
Of course you're not!
Be careful.
No!
I can't take it anymore!
Seriously, it's always the same with you!
You're the worst off out of anyone here, Zenitsu!
Stuff it and take your medicine right now!
I swear, every time...
Tanjirou, here's your medicine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Hey!
Tanjirou's medicine goes down pretty easily, huh?
It's different from mine, right?
I sense favouritism! Favouritism, I say!
Zenitsu, this is a hospital ward!
Quiet down a little!
You seem to be doing well!
Murata!
Hey!
Are you all right?
Well, I almost got dissolved,
but I did still survive in the end.
I hear you guys took quite a beating, though.
Yeah, looks like we'll be taking it easy for a while.
And you ended up with throat issues, Boar Boy?
What's up with him?
He went through a lot.
If you could please let him be...
But for this guy of all people to be so out of it—
Tanjirou!
Who's this?
This is Murata. He fought with us on Mt. Natagumo.
I'm Murata! Nice to meet you!
Hey, your arm...
I almost got turned into one of those creepy spiders.
All my limbs are still just stumps.
And that's why you need to take your medicine!
But it tastes disgusting!
There's only so much a person can take!
Fine, but don't come crying to me
if your arms don't go back to normal!
That's so cold, I almost thought it was winter!
You don't know how good you have it!
If you take your medicine and bask in enough sunlight,
there won't even be any lasting effects!
I can't do it!
Gross is gross! No two ways about it!
Looks like fun. Lucky you.
Murata?
I was summoned to the Hashira Meeting
to give my report on the Mt. Natagumo incident.
I thought I accidentally walked into Hell!
They're absolutely terrifying!
They were pissed at how poorly the newer
Demon Slayers have been performing as of late.
Especially since it seems some of us
weren't following orders back on Mt. Natagumo.
They asked me who in their right mind even trained us.
Like, how is someone of my rank
supposed to answer that?
The Hashira terrify me...
Hello there.
Hashira! Lady Kochou!
Hello there!
Oh, hello! And goodbye!
Oh, my! See you soon!
Well? How's your rehab going?
It's going well. We've been steadily improving.
In that case, how about we start
your Rehabilitation Training?
Rehabilitation Training?
Yes!
I'm sorry for being so weak...
Tanjirou and Inosuke were taken away
by the Hashira, Lady Shinobu,
and started some kind of "Rehabilitation Training".
Lady Shinobu's voice is like no other.
I don't think I've ever heard anything like it.
It's irregular, and that scares me a little.
But she seemed like a goddess back when she
treated all those people that turned into spiderlings.
No wonder everyone crawled to her in tears.
Not only that, but she's cute beyond compare!
I bet she could make a living on her looks alone.
And this cute lady is now training Tanjirou
and Inosuke to help them get back in shape.
And any minute now...
...they'll come back, looking like they've seen a ghost.
Welcome back, guys!
How'd it go today?
What happened?
What's wrong? Hey...
Sorry.
Don't mind us.
For the love of God, please tell me!
I'll be joining you two in this death march tomorrow!
Oh god, no!
I'm scared! This is terrifying!
I don't wanna go!
Since Zenitsu is joining us starting today,
I'll go over the process again.
You'll start over there.
They'll make your bodies limber again
after having been bedridden for so long.
Next, there's reflex training.
These cups contain medicated water.
The objective is to splash it over each other.
However, if your opponent blocks
your cup before you can pick it up,
you're not allowed to move it anymore.
Now!
Again!
Stop!
Last up, we've got full-body training.
In simpler terms, you'll be playing tag.
You'll be up against me,
Aoi, and Kanao over there.
Excuse me. If I may?
Do you have any questions?
No, it's just...
You two. Come with me.
I'm staying right here.
Shut your mouth and come with me, now!
I said now!
Get a move on, you sleazebags!
You damn slowpokes!
The hell is wrong with you?
Sit up straight and listen to me, you morons!
You miserable maggots!
The hell was that, you damn—
Inosuke!
What are you thinking, Zenitsu?
Apologise to him right now!
It's you guys who should apologise!
C'mon, I'm waiting!
How dare you act like this was Hell
when it was Heaven all along?!
All you did was frolic with girls all day,
so why did you look so exhausted?
Prostrate yourselves and apologise!
Cut your own stomach and die!
How can you say that?
Shut it, you headbutting paragon of virtue!
Shut your trap and listen up, got it?
You get to touch girls!
Your bodies are getting massaged!
You get to touch hands with that cup game!
And with tag, you get to touch
their whole freakin' bodies!
Every girl has two bouncy boobs,
one fine rear, and two soft thighs!
They smell so nice when they pass by,
and simply looking at them fills me with bliss!
It's the greatest fortune! Heaven on Earth!
You're full of shit! Nothing you said makes any sense!
When you lose to someone smaller
than you, it destroys your soul!
Boo-hoo, poor you! You've never been
chummy with a girl before, have you?
Just what you'd expect from a mountain boy!
Oh, this is so sad!
That's it!
The hell do you think you are?
I'll have you know I've stomped on
plenty of little girls before!
That's the worst thing you could do!
The hell's wrong with you?!
That's not gonna get you any girls!
I can get as many girls as I want!
Please train me well!
This is fine! All good!
This guy ain't normal.
I'm always fighting back tears from the pain,
but he's just laughing it off.
I shall take you on.
Begin!
I would never splash tea on a lady.
Now then, full-body training!
Begin!
I win!
I won the battle but lost the war!
I'm gonna kick some ass, too!
All right!
Ouch!
I'm the only one on a losing streak and soaked.
This is so embarrassing!
But...
We just can't beat Kanao.
None of us can get to a cup before her
or stop her from splashing us.
For the next five days,
my losing streak against Kanao kept racking up.
As did Inosuke's.
Zenitsu's, too.
We couldn't so much as lay a finger
on a strand of her hair.
And then one day, the other two
stopped coming to the dojo entirely.
Z-Zenitsu? Inosuke?
Please train me!
Thank you for the good workout.
Why can't I beat her?
What gives her the edge over me?
Let's see. Her reflexes are way faster.
Even if I were in top form,
I'd probably be no match for her.
Her scent is totally different.
It reminds me of the scent of the Hashira.
Master Tanjirou?
Also... her eyes?
Her eyes are different!
Master Tanjirou?
I have the feeling that...
Um...
Master Tanjirou, are you okay?
We've been calling you over and over.
Sorry! I was lost in thought.
What's up?
Here's a towel for you.
Thanks! That's a big help!
You're all so kind!
Um, Master Tanjirou,
we were wondering if you keep up
your Breathing Technique at all times.
From dawn to dusk,
and even while you're asleep?
Do you use your techniques nonstop?
No, I don't. That's never even crossed my mind.
Is that even possible?
It is!
We're told that being able to
makes all the difference in the world!
Just using it for a couple minutes
at a time already takes its toll on me,
and you want me to do it around the clock?
Some people have already mastered it.
Every Hashira has—and even Miss Kanao!
You should give it a try!
Great idea!
Thanks! I'll give it a go!
Isn't it about time you came back to training, Inosuke?
Sulking won't do you any good.
Zenitsu, you should come, too!
Yup!
I think I did a splendid job.
Just tell 'em my injury's taken a turn for the worse!
Hey, Kakushi lady over there!
How's a drink with me sound?
Total Concentration Breathing.
From dawn to dusk, and even in my sleep.
I said I'd try to keep it up around the clock.
But there's no way I can do that!
I seriously can't!
If I try to keep it up for a long time,
it just makes me feel like I'm about to die!
The toll is too much for me to endure.
My lungs and ears hurt!
My ears are ringing like crazy!
My eardrums!
That scared the heck out of me!
I thought my heart was about to
come out through my eardrums!
This endeavour is gonna be fruitless at this rate!
When in doubt, return to the basics!
You spineless fool!
Breathing is all about lung capacity.
If I can't get the hang of it,
that means my lungs are too weak.
I have to improve it!
I have to give it my all.
That's how I've always managed!
Improvement is a daily process!
Slow and steady wins the race!
I've gotta take it one step at a time.
Yeah!
Master Tanjirou works hard every day!
Yeah! Let's bring him some rice balls, okay?
Good idea! And also...
Blow into these gourds?
That's right.
When she was training Lady Kanao,
Lady Shinobu often had her blow into gourds.
Oh, really?
That's an interesting technique, huh?
What kind of sound are you supposed to make?
Oh, no. Not like that.
She blew into it to make it explode.
Oh, really?
Explode?
What? You mean you blow these up?
Something this hard?!
Yes!
Not to mention, this is a special gourd,
so it's tougher than normal ones.
A girl that petite was able to
blow up such strong gourds?!
The gourds get bigger and bigger the better you get.
The biggest one Lady Kanao can blow up
is this one.
That's bloody huge!
I'll give it my all!
They're not coming today, either?
I'm so sorry.
I'll bring them tomorrow.
Again, I'm really sorry.
No. You need not concern yourself
with those two anymore!
I'll work hard.
I'll work hard!
While throwing myself into the drills
Master Urokodaki pounded into me,
I'm also trying to maintain my Breathing Technique.
I imagine myself running down the mountain
and race all around the mansion's garden!
All the obstacles are stand-ins
for the trees on that mountain!
Hard work!
I've regained most of my strength.
And now I can run farther than before,
and my lungs have also gotten stronger!
I'm making good progress!
During the day, I run all over the place
and put my lungs into overdrive with swift movements.
So now, I'll breathe in slowly.
Take slow, deep breaths
and send air all the way to my fingertips.
Meditation boosts concentration.
Master Urokodaki said so himself.
Master Urokodaki...
How dare you break my sword!
Please forgive me.
They're reforging my sword for me now, but...
I apologise from the bottom of my heart.
Concentrate! You need to concentrate!
Concentrate on your breathing!
Yoo-hoo!
Yes?
I can see you're working very hard.
Even though your friends ran off somewhere.
Don't you feel lonely all by yourself?
No! Because once I've mastered it myself,
I can teach them how to do it, too!
You really are one of pure heart.
Hey,
why did you take us all here?
Nezuko's situation has been officially acknowledged,
and the three of you were injured so horribly.
And besides that,
I'd like to entrust my dream to you.
Dream?
Yes.
My dream for humans to befriend the demons.
I'm sure that if anyone could do it, it'd be you guys.
Are you angry?
I always pick up this angry scent from you,
but you're always smiling.
Yes.
You're right.
It might be true that I'm
in a constant state of anger.
Ever since a demon slaughtered my beloved sister.
Every time I see the tears of those
who've lost their loved ones to demons,
every time I hear those cries of despair,
the anger keeps building up
inside me and continues to swell.
Deep down in the innermost depths of my body,
there's a revulsion that I can't fight.
I'm sure the same holds true for the other Hashira.
This time they saw Nezuko, who's never
devoured a human, with their own eyes.
And they can tell her apart now.
Out of respect for the Master's wishes,
I doubt anyone would raise a hand to her.
My sister was a kind-hearted person, much like you.
She, too, felt sympathy for demons.
Even on the brink of death,
she never stopped pitying them.
But I was never able to feel that way.
How can you feel sorry for
something that kills humans?
I've never heard anything so ludicrous.
But if that was how my sister truly felt,
then I must carry on that feeling.
If there's a way for us to no longer
have to kill those pitiful demons,
then I must continue searching for it.
All without losing that smile my sister always loved.
Kanae!
But I'm exhausted.
Demons do nothing but lie.
Losing all reason out of self-preservation,
they murder humans with their instincts laid bare.
Tanjirou, please continue doing all that you can.
Please be there for Nezuko until the bitter end.
Knowing that you're working so hard
in my place reassures me to no end.
It helps me rest easier.
Your Breathing has come to a halt.
I'll do my best.
Total Concentration Breathing!
Mom, Hanako,
Takeo, Shigeru,
Rokuta...
I'll restore Nezuko's humanity no matter what!
Sniff, sniff! Miss Shinobu,
did something nice happen to you?
Yes! I've acquired a precious drug.
Sniff, sniff! Are you angry?
Someone keeps swiping the candy from the shelves.
Sniff, sniff! You're also sad, right?
There's a disturbance in the mountain behind us.
Now, time for a Taisho secret!
Since Aoi has been training under Miss Shinobu,
I hear she can concoct the simpler medicines!
Nothing escapes your nose,
does it, Tanjirou? That's amazing!
Sniff, sniff! For some reason—
Because I enjoy talking with you, Tanjirou.
Thank you so much!
Next, Episode 25, "Tsuguko, Tsuyuri Kanao".