The blood of the Twelve Blood Moons should have
a high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood.
If I can extract some, we'll be one step closer
to restoring Nezuko's humanity.
Oh, right! What about Inosuke?
Did you beat 'em?
Are you all right, Inosuke?
I asked if you killed that damn thing or not!
Uh, yeah, I did!
Never mind that. How are you feeling?
Don't go coddling me now, dumbass!
Y'hear me? Got that?
Anything you can do, I can do too!
My head'll be harder than yours before you know it!
Not to mention... To mention...
Um...
He's wounded pretty badly.
I couldn't save our allies, either.
That person gave off a scent of terror and suffering.
Strong enough to make her yearn for death.
Just what is going on on this mountain?
You've got a Blood Moon and even
a family of demons living here.
Stay still, Inosuke!
Cut that out! I don't need that!
I'm fine, y'hear!
But...
I thought demons never banded together!
Ow!
Something just pricked me!
What the hell? This is seriously pissing me off!
Worst part is, I can't bloody find them! This sucks!
Where'd they go?
Which way?
And gee, it reeks! Phooey!
I'm gonna break down in tears at this rate!
That, and the sounds of these spiders
rustling about is so gross!
I know they're just trying to
survive out here, but c'mon!
Oh, for crying out loud!
Shut up and stay still!
The hell is that thing?!
That spider has a human face!
Is something like that even possible? What the hell?!
Please be a dream! Please be a dream!
I beg you, please tell me this is a dream!
If this could just be a bad dream,
I promise I'll work harder from now on!
If I wake up to find my head
resting on Nezuko's lap,
I swear I'll turn over a new leaf!
I'd even plough fields!
I'll plough as many acres as you want!
So please,
wake me up from this nightmare!
What the hell is going on here?
Are those humans transforming into spiders?
Is that house floating?
Hang on, there's a faint glimpse
of something. Threads?
And it reeks!
Pungent doesn't even
begin to describe it!
Tanjirou would drop dead on the spot
with his keen sense of smell!
This smell is making my throat ache!
I'm tearing up!
My eyes sting!
Huge!
It's large! Enormous!
Humongous!
That thing's a friggin' giant!
Y'know what? I refuse to even speak with
the likes of you, whatever the hell you are!
Running away is futile.
You've already lost either way.
The hell are you blabbering on about?
Y'know what, drop it! I'm not interested!
I hate guys like you, capiche?
You already know how dire
your situation is, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Look at your hand.
My hand?
What's wrong with my ha—
What's this?
It's venom.
A spider bit you, right?
That venom will slowly turn you into a spider, too!
Give it thirty minutes or so and you'll have
become my slave, crawling all over the ground!
Look at this pocket watch.
You still with me?
By the time the long hand has gone around once,
you will have long become a member of my spider den!
When the hand arrives here, you'll start to
feel tingling and pain in your limbs.
When it's here, you'll start feeling dizzy and nauseous.
Here, you'll begin to experience intense pain.
Your body will start shrinking and you'll pass out!
And by the time you wake up...
Running away...
...is futile!
Right, gotcha!
I get it, okay? You don't have to say it twice!
What are you doing?
Shut up! Just leave me be!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Once the venom makes its rounds,
you'll turn into a spiderling and lose all sentience.
Oh god, no! That's exactly what I hate about this!
What's so hard to understand about that?!
I bet nobody likes you!
You must have no friends at all!
I see someone here could use an extra
dose of venom to transform even faster!
No! Anything but that!
I don't wanna turn into that!
Get a hold of yourself!
Stop crying! Stop running away!
Neither of those will get you anywhere!
Zenitsu!
Come down from there!
We're going to continue training!
Hell, no! Any more training will kill me!
It's gonna be the end of me!
You won't die! Not from this level of training!
Come down from there, you little moron!
Gramps!
Call me "Master"!
But I love you, Gramps!
When the girl I loved made me raise money
so she could run off with some other guy,
you rescued me from my mountain of debt!
Although looking back, you may have
just been looking for a swordsman to train!
I want to live up to your expectations!
But it's totally beyond me!
I really do feel awful, but that's just how I am!
I'll have you know I've been training
on my own in secret, too!
I haven't been getting a wink of sleep!
But I have absolutely nothing to show for it!
Seriously, what the hell is wrong with me?
Calm down, Zenitsu!
You have potential!
I've just about had it!
Zenitsu!
Why does my life need to be so tragic?
I was even struck by lightning.
It even changed my hair colour.
Sure, I was thankful just to be alive, but...
I...
I hate myself more than anyone else.
I always think about how I need to
get my act together already,
but in the end I just end up cowering,
running away, and snivelling.
I want to change. I want to become a better person!
But...
I'm doing the best I can, y'hear me?
So why do I have to go bald
and turn into some monster?
You can't be for real, right?
You've gotta be joking!
What's wrong with this guy?
Oh, crap! Don't climb up here!
Just leave me alone for a bit!
Give me some time alone, please!
My hair's falling out already?
My hair is falling out.
Hey, he never said anything about that!
What's his problem?
Isn't he one of those demon hunters
that came to kill our family?
Did he pass out already?
I can't believe he's so spineless.
That fall's gonna split his head wide open.
The hell's wrong with him?
Thunder Breathing.
First Form.
Gastro Acid!
Did he just twist his body in midair to dodge that?
It's almost like he's a totally different person!
Thunder Breathing.
First Form.
Hey, you guys! Get him!
Thunder Breathing.
First Form.
He's been assuming the same stance over and over.
Oh, I see how it is. This guy...
He only knows that one move!
That's fine, Zenitsu.
That's good enough.
If you can master even one form,
that's a cause for celebration!
Take the one technique you can perform
and hone it to perfection.
Refine it! Polish it to its utmost limit!
But Gramps,
you were fuming not too long ago.
Because Thunder Breathing has six forms,
and I've only ever been able to grasp one.
Do you know how a sword is forged?
No, I have no idea.
Are you gonna keep hitting me?
I'm about to tear up over here.
When forging a sword,
you strike it over and over to get rid of impurities,
in turn increasing the purity of the blade,
allowing for a strong sword to be forged.
Is that why you keep clobbering me day in, day out?
But I'm not made of steel, am I?
I'm made of flesh and blood, y'know?
Not much of a threat, are you?
And you call yourself a demon hunter?
Any minute now and that venom
will render you immobile!
Zenitsu, perfect it!
It's all right to cry.
It's all right to run away!
But never give up!
Believe in yourself.
You endured all that hellish training!
You'll be rewarded for that without fail!
Hone it to the utmost limit!
Become the strongest blade of all!
Hone that one move to perfection!
Get out of my sight.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Get lost already.
Stop playing dumb.
Aren't you ashamed of crying like a baby all day long?
You laggard...
Any time spent on you is wasted.
Master is an extraordinary man.
But Gramps said—
"Gramps"? Just who do you think you are?
Master is a former Hashira!
He earned the highest title among the Demon Slayers!
Very few have the honour to
receive training from a former Hashira!
The time Master spends training you is all for naught!
You're an eyesore, you hear me? Beat it!
Why are you still here?
Why do you insist on dawdling here?
I have no parents, so there's no one
around to expect anything of me.
There isn't a single soul who has any hope for me.
No one who believes I can be useful.
That I'll manage to protect somebody
and make them happy for once in my life.
Not even something as simple as that.
There's no one with that kind of hope for me.
If you fail, cry, and run away even once,
people will just go, "Oh, this guy's a lost cause",
and turn their backs to you.
But Gramps was different!
Time and time again, he would patiently scold me.
All those times I kept running away...
Time and time again...
He'd drag me right back.
Well yeah, he did smack me around a tad too much.
But he never abandoned me!
Sting him! Give him another taste of your venom!
No way he's walking out of that alive!
What the—?
The very air is vibrating...
Thunder Breathing.
First form.
Thunderclap and Flash!
Sixfold!
He disappeared?
Did he get me?
Me? For real?
This guy?
I lost to someone like him?
You've gotta be kidding me!
How did I lose to a guy who can barely move?!
It's time to dream...
I want a happy dream.
One where I'm powerful.
Stronger than anyone else.
I could help the weak and anyone in trouble.
Anytime.
Everything that Gramps taught me,
all the time he spent on me...
It wouldn't be for nothing!
A dream where, thanks to Gramps,
I become powerful and help out a lot of people.
But now, that's all over!
Chuntarou...
I'm so sorry.
Never give up!
Never give up.
Breathe in slowly and slow down
the venom as much as you can.
No matter how painful or agonising it may be,
don't you dare take the easy way out.
Else Gramps is gonna let you have it!
Right.
Tanjirou will yell at you, too.
What was that sound?
Was that a lightning strike?
Hell if I know.
I'm not smelling any thunderclouds.
But that acrid odour in the air
is stronger now, so I can't tell.
Inosuke!
I think I'm gonna go check it out.
Go ahead and do whatever you want!
Are you descending, Inosuke?
Head down the mountain.
Why would I? Buzz off!
I mean, have you seen your injuries?
I am not hurt at all!
N-N-No, Inosuke!
Anyone could see you are just by looking at you!
A demon!
The odour wafting all over this mountain
completely masked her scent!
I'm gonna tear you to shreds, you damn demon!
Get back here!
Inosuke!
Daddy!
Who's your "Daddy"?
Inosuke!
Stay away...
from my family!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Father.
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Combined Junior and Senior High School!
Tales of the Demon Slayer Academy!
The disciplinary committee's day starts too early!
There's only one reason why I don't quit.
And that reason is the dress code check!
I can ogle at the girls all I want
without getting yelled at!
Nezuko!
Makomo's looking cute today, too!
And that upperclassman's gorgeous, as well!
Mr. Tomioka!
It's not what it looks like!
I'm just regulating the dress code.
Make your hair follow regulations
before regulating others!
This is my natural hair colour!
Next, Episode 18, "A Fake Bond"!
But it's my natural hair colour...