Are you done getting changed?
Yes.
Tanjirou,
now that you've officially become a Demon Slayer,
I'd like to explain a few things to you.
All right.
That uniform you're wearing right now
is made of a special kind of fibre.
The fabric is quite breathable,
but repels moisture and won't burn easily.
Even the claws and fangs of lesser demons
cannot rend that uniform.
It's that strong?
Also,
about that Sun Blade of yours...
Its colour varies from owner to owner,
and each hue has its unique properties.
But since very few people end up with
black blades, little is known about them.
So little, in fact, that—
"So little" that what, Master Urokodaki?
Since so little is known about them,
they are said to be wielded by
swordsmen who don't make it very far.
I don't know how well I'll do as a Demon Slayer,
but I'll do whatever it takes
to make Nezuko human again.
Yes, you're right.
I have faith that you can make that happen.
Right.
One more thing.
Take this.
It's a box for you to carry
your sister in during the day.
It's built out of an extremely light
wood known as "Cloud Mist Pine".
I coated it with rock lacquer to further reinforce
its exterior and make it even more durable.
Thank you so much!
Wow, it's so light, Master Urokodaki!
Nezuko!
Get in, will you?
Think you can do it?
Nezuko, we'll always be together now, okay?
All right, I'm off.
Stay still for a moment.
Nezuko, are you okay?
Nezuko?
I'm just taking a guess here,
but it could be that she's recovering her strength
through rest rather than by consuming flesh.
Nezuko...
Rest up well.
Could this be the town to the north-west?
Oh, deary me. Look at that, it's Kazumi.
Poor thing. He looks so haggard.
That's because he was with
Satoko when she disappeared.
It's the same story night after night.
It's seriously creepy.
It's so dreadful!
Once night comes, another girl will go missing!
Kazumi!
I'd like to have a word with you, if I may.
Is that all right?
This is where she disappeared.
You may not believe me, but...
I believe you!
I absolutely do.
Really!
There's still faint traces of the demon here,
but it's... uneven, so to speak.
Something's not right here.
Who is this kid, anyway?
How dare you!
The hell do you mean, "disappeared"?
You bastard!
Dear!
That's enough! Please stop!
Please, believe me.
She really did disappear.
I believe you.
That's what I came to this town for.
You're gonna keep going?
Yes.
It's gotten pretty dark.
I'm flattered that you're so concerned about me,
but shouldn't you go get some rest
and pick this up again tomorrow?
They're active during the night.
I can't afford to rest now.
I've caught a fresh scent in this area.
It's gotta be somewhere nearby.
They?
Don't tell me you're...
Seriously...?
How terrifying.
I want you to stay indoors for the time being.
Okay, Mother.
Well then, good night.
I wonder what became of the girls that disappeared.
I just hope they're okay.
What's gotten into you suddenly?
He's fast!
The scent just got stronger!
The demon's active!
He jumped?
He just mentioned demons...
The Demon Slayers...
Do they actually exist?
This is the place.
They're here!
I can pick up two different scents.
A demon and a human girl!
They're nowhere to be seen.
But...
The scent is strongest...
Here!
A deformed demon!
Some demons use special techniques called the
"Demon Blood Arts", granting them supernatural abilities.
You may find yourself facing these
kinds of demons as well from now on.
Where are all the girls you kidnapped?
I've got two more questions for you!
What was that thing?
Kazumi,
please take care of her and be on standby nearby.
So long as you stay close, I will protect you!
He's likely able to emerge from any surface,
like the ground or the wall...
Odds are he could even appear out of thin air.
However,
submerged or not, he can't erase his scent!
Here he comes!
Water Breathing!
Fifth Form!
There's three?!
Stay calm!
You've got this!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
Tanjirou, listen to me closely.
There is but one demon in the whole world
with the kind of blood that
can turn humans into demons.
Just one...
The first to become a demon millennia ago.
In other words, your true enemy.
Moreover, I believe he's the only one who might
know how to restore your sister's humanity.
That demon is known as...
Kibutsuji Muzan!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
Too shallow!
I missed all the crucial areas
because I switched forms mid-swing!
They all share the exact same scent!
I was told that demons don't band together as a rule.
That means it's one demon who's split into three.
I've gotta fight three demons
while protecting these two...
I can't let it get to me!
I'll make him tell me everything!
Everything he knows about Kibutsuji Muzan
and about how I can turn a demon back into a human!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Still not deep enough!
I can't chase him too far.
And I can't take a full swing while guarding others!
You fucking bastard!
Screw off, will ya?!
That girl's gonna go stale, goddammit!
She's already sixteen!
If I don't eat her soon, she's gonna
keep losing flavour by the second!
Calm down, my other self.
So what?
There are gonna be nights like this.
I've already fed on plenty of
sixteen-year-old girls in this town.
They were all quite meaty and delicious.
I'm satisfied.
Well, I'm not satisfied, my other self!
I wanna feast on more!
You monsters...
Give me back Satoko—the girl you guys
abducted two nights ago!
Satoko?
Who is that?
If her hairpin is among these collectibles,
I've already eaten her.
I missed again!
He escapes underground too fast!
Crap! I got too close to the wall!
Why is a demon accompanying a mere human?
What's the meaning of this? Who are these two?
A swordsman and a demon working together?
I don't get it.
Nezuko...
It may only help to console her,
but while Nezuko was asleep,
I placed her under a hypnotic suggestion.
Suggestion?
"All humans are your family."
"Protect humans."
"Demons are your enemy!"
Nezuko!
"Never forgive any demons"
"who bring harm onto humans!"
Your kicks really saved the day, Nezuko!
Thanks!
It didn't break even after
getting kicked from the inside.
That box is super strong!
But isn't it cramped in there?
Aren't you uncomfortable?
Your big brother will build you a much bigger box!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I heard today's demon has had the bad habit of
grinding his teeth like mad since he was a human.
Next, Episode 7, "Kibutsuji Muzan"!