I don't want to be a prisoner of my own misery
kanashimi ni torawaretaku wa nai
I don't want to go back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Cry for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's just one path for you to take:
mou michi wa erabenai
Making it out alive!
kachinokore
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
hakari ni kakeru
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
And now, with that blade of yours in hand
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
Where might you end up striking down?
doko e furiorosu