Blood Arts!
Blood Burst!
No one can ever sever
the bond
between us!
Nezuko!
I... I won!
I won!
Dad saved me!
I don't know how I was able to pull that off
with the dance that's been passed down
in our family for generations.
But that saved me!
I was able to beat him!
Huh?
I can't see her properly anymore...
I might've pushed myself too far.
The ringing in my ears is brutal!
All I can feel is pain!
I've gotta
recover quickly!
This isn't the end yet.
I still have to go help Inosuke!
I've gotta hurry!
The scent of blood just got stronger!
Come to think of it, every demon
I've slain so far gave off the scent of ash.
Don't tell me...
But I cut his head off!
Did you really think you killed me?
Poor thing.
Did your pathetic delusion bring you joy?
Before you had the opportunity to decapitate me,
I cut off my own head with my threads.
I've had enough.
I'll kill both you and your sister.
It's been a long time since I've been this pissed.
Get up!
Get up right now!
Get your breathing under control!
Hurry!
Right now!
What's the deal with those flames anyway?
Why did only me and my webs catch fire?
I don't know if that was because of your sister's power,
but you have my thanks for making me this angry.
Now I can carve you up without regret.
With the correct breathing technique,
it doesn't matter how exhausted you are!
Blood Arts!
Deadly Eye Basket!
Don't panic!
Don't let it disrupt your breathing!
Calm down.
Just stay calm!
I can't raise my arm!
Someone's there...
Who is it? Zenitsu?
You did well to hold out until I got here.
Leave the rest to me.
It's just one after another with you guys.
It's like you barbarians exist only to get in my way!
Blood Arts!
Cutting Web Mandala!
Total Concentration.
Water Breathing.
Eleventh Form.
Lull.
Eleventh Form?
Who gives a damn about your Eleventh Form?
Huh?
Wh-What did he just do?
The instant my webs reached him, they were shredded.
Not a single one made contact?
Did he cut through my toughest webs just like that?
That's impossible!
One more shot!
I messed up!
Even though I was the only one who
had no once messed up before
in this "Pretend Family" game!
We finally drove it into a corner!
Hey, look at that.
Another demon?
It's just a kid.
But kid or not, that thing's still a demon.
If we let it go, it'll eat humans.
Hey.
Hey, you.
Do you want me save you?
In return, will you do what I ask?
I'll do anything!
I'll do whatever you want, so please save me!
Then, become a part of my family.
I will! I'll do it!
What are they talking about?
All right, say your prayers!
Welcome.
Starting today, you're part of my family, too.
Drink this.
Our family's power belongs to Rui.
Since we were all weaker demons,
Rui shared some of his power with us.
Since Rui is one of our lord's favourites,
he gets special permission to
perform these kinds of rituals.
Do you feel it?
You have nothing to fear from
those demon hunters anymore.
Now then, time for the finishing touches.
All right, you can look up now.
Congratulations.
You're truly part of our family now.
We're just playing house.
Huh?
We have no blood ties.
We're just assorted strangers
who call each other "family".
I'm so sorry!
I'll do better, Rui!
I'll practise! Forgive me!
I'm so sorry for being unable to do it well!
It's just that I revert by accident sometimes!
I don't want to hear your excuses, Mother.
Play the role of a mother, like you should.
I know what I must do, Rui.
We were all scared of the demon hunters,
and just wanted companions.
No one really wanted to take part in
this baffling "Pretend Family" game.
But those who fail to fulfil
Rui's demands get mutilated,
have their sentience stripped from them,
or are strung up and left to roast.
I've about had it here.
I'm gonna pretend I never heard you say that—
I know you're not stupid,
unlike all the others.
Let's run away together.
I wouldn't say this to just anybody.
You're the one person
I truly think of as a younger sister.
Tomorrow, Rui will be summoned by
our lord and descend the mountain.
That's when we make our getaway.
How disappointing.
They were all stupid, each and every
one of them. But I was different!
But despite that, I still messed up!
Rui!
They killed Mother!
And our elder brother, too.
What should we do?
The demon hunters aren't far behind.
Hey...
Sh-Shouldn't we make a run for it?
Don't!
You should know already.
I really hate it when your face reverts.
What are you looking at?
We're not holding some theatre play here.
He only went for my face, so I got off lightly.
A demon!
What the—?!
It's futile. You'll never cut your way out.
You see, my Ball of Yarn may feel soft,
but it's extremely tough.
Wha—?
First, the solvent will melt
those clothes out of the way.
And after that, it'll be your turn.
You'll be reduced to mush in no time,
and then I'll feed on you.
That's quite impressive!
Do you shoot out those webs from
the palms of your hands?
Good evening.
The moon is quite lovely tonight,
wouldn't you agree?
I see you have no intention of being my friend.
W-W-Wait!
I beg of you!
I'm being forced to do this!
If I go against him, he'll cut me into pieces!
Is that so?
That does sound very tragic!
I'll spare you!
Let's be friends!
Y-You'll spare me?
Yes!
But in order for us to be friends,
I must ask you a couple of questions.
O, sweet little girl,
how many people have you murdered?
Five.
But I was ordered to! I had no choice!
Now, now, there's no need to lie to me.
I'm already well aware.
That spell you cast to turn one of our men
into a cocoon was most impressive!
Help me!
Somebody!
You've feasted on at least eighty humans, right?
No, of course not.
I only killed those five.
Did you know I came here from the west?
The west, my dear.
On the west side of the mountain,
I found hordes of cocoons hanging from the trees.
The humans inside had been liquefied.
Every single one had been murdered.
In that area alone, I counted at least fourteen cocoons.
Fourteen humans.
All dead.
It's not that I'm angry you did that.
I simply want to get an accurate count.
What good will it do you to confirm that?
It's so you can receive the punishment
you deserve and be reborn!
Punishment?
That way, you and I can become friends.
If you go unpunished for taking all those lives,
your victims will never receive justice.
I could gouge out your eyeballs
or cut your stomach open and play with your insides.
For every person you've killed,
I'll give you the appropriate amount of torture.
And once you've suffered through all that
pain and suffering, your sins will be forgiven.
Let's both do our best here.
It'll be fine!
You're a demon, so you don't have to be afraid of me
killing you or leaving you riddled with scars!
Who do you think you're kidding?
Die!
You damn vixen!
I see we'll never be friends.
What a pity!
Insect Breathing.
Butterfly Dance.
Whimsy.
She didn't cut my head off?
That's the sword she's using?
I see.
She's too small and has no arm strength,
so she can't behead anyone.
I can beat her!
You mustn't think you're safe just because
you've still got a head on your shoulders.
There's swordswomen like me
who use poison out there, after all.
From the Demon Slayers, Insect Hashira,
Kochou Shinobu.
I may be the only swordswoman among
the Hashira who can't behead demons,
but as I've created a poison that's lethal
to demons, I'm also rather exceptional.
Oh! Pardon me!
You're dead, so you can't hear me, can you?
How silly of me!
You still in one piece?
Just barely!
What happened to the demon?
Shouldn't you kill her already?
That dose of wisteria poison is plenty.
She's already dead, so she'll simply
rot away if we leave her.
I'm a pharmaceuticals expert!
Your clothes may have been dissolved,
but your body's more or less unscathed!
I'm glad for you!
Now then, as for that demon
who forced that lady to do his bidding...
Did Tomioka beat me to him already?
Nezuko.
Nezuko!
I'll kill him! I'll kill him no matter what!
And after that, I'm gonna kill those siblings!
Siblings!
What do you want, Rui?
What do you mean by "family"?
I don't know.
Because I have no memories of when I was human.
Is that why you made us pretend to be your family?
I thought that if I could feel a family bond,
my memories would come back.
The bond of a real family...
That's right.
I...
Nezuko!
That's amazing! I didn't think you could
create poison to kill demons!
I study the pharmaceutical sciences.
There's more to being a Demon Slayer
than just swinging a sword, y'know?
I-I see.
And now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I formulate my poison inside my scabbard.
As for how that's done,
my and my swordsmith's lips are sealed!
All right! I'm gonna shoot up
the ranks with a special sword, too!
First things first, make sure you don't
get your uniform melted off again!
That sure is a toxic way to put it!
Next, Episode 21, "Code Violation".
It's never bad to have high ambitions!
Let's both try our best!