How?
How did this happen?
Nezuko, don't die! Don't you die on me!
I will save you no matter what!
So please, don't die!
Your big brother will definitely save you, you hear?
Tanjirou?
Your face is all covered in soot.
Come over here.
It might get dangerous once it starts snowing.
You don't have to head out now.
Well, I want everyone to eat their fill on New Year's,
so I'm gonna go sell as much charcoal as I can.
Thank you.
Tanjirou!
You're going into town again today?
I'm coming with you!
Oh no, you won't!
You know you can't keep up with your big brother.
But Mom!
No buts.
He won't be taking the cart today,
so you won't be able to ride along if you get tired.
Tanjirou!
I wanna come with you!
I promise I'll help!
Thank you, Hanako.
But you're staying home today.
And so are you, Shigeru.
I'll get you lots of tasty souvenirs
while I'm there, okay?
For real?
For real.
And Hanako, I'll read you a book when I come home.
Okay!
Attagirl.
Thank you so much, Tanjirou.
No problem.
All right, I'm off.
Takeo.
Could you chop me some wood?
Don't overexert yourself, though.
I mean, sure, but...
I wanted to do it with you...
There, there.
What's your problem?!
Take's all red!
Sh-Shut up!
There, there.
Knock it off already!
Hurry back, okay?
Have a safe trip!
Tanjirou!
Ah, Nezuko.
I was just putting Rokuta to sleep.
Didn't want him making a scene when you left.
He really misses Dad.
Everyone's been clinging to you
a lot more since he passed away.
Have a good trip!
Our lives aren't always easy,
but we're happy.
However, life can be as fickle as the weather.
Ever-changing, never stagnating.
It won't always be sunny,
but snowfall won't last forever, either.
And...
whenever happiness meets its end,
it always carries
the smell of blood.
Oh my, Tanjirou!
I can't believe you came all the way
down in this weather today!
Always a hard worker, aren't you?
Be careful not to catch a cold!
This is nothing, really.
How about you? Do you need some charcoal?
Hey, Tanjirou!
Can I have some?
Oh, and thanks for fixing
my sliding doors the other day!
I would like some as well!
Tanjirou!
Oh man, perfect timing!
She's accusing me of breaking this plate!
Help a brother out, will ya?
Give it a sniff!
Smells like cat.
See?!
Oh dear, so it was a cat?
I told you it wasn't me!
Tanjirou!
Could you give me a hand with this luggage?
Gosh, it's gotten dark already.
I'm glad I sold everything, though.
Tanjirou, hold it!
You weren't planning on hiking
up the mountain, were you?
It's too dangerous.
I've got a good nose, so I'll be fine.
You can stay here for the night.
Get over here.
But...
Don't argue, make haste!
Before the demons come.
Thanks for dinner.
Say, Saburou.
What are demons like?
Man-eating demons have always
roamed the land after dark.
That's why you shouldn't stroll around at night.
If you're done eating, sleep.
You can set off at sunrise.
Couldn't these demons enter people's homes?
They can. And they do.
But can't they just eat everyone then?
That's why the demon hunters hunt them down.
Have for ages.
I'm snuffing the lights.
Go to sleep now.
Saburou has been all alone ever since he lost his family.
He's probably lonely.
I'll bring my siblings along next time.
It's fine, there are no demons to be afraid of.
But, come to think of it,
Grandma used to say the same thing
when she was still with us.
You be careful now, y'hear?
Sure!
Whenever happiness meets its end,
it always carries...
The smell of blood!
Nezuko!
What happened here? Are you okay?
What happened?
Mom...
Hanako...
Takeo...
Shigeru...
Nezuko...
Rokuta...
Nezuko's the only one who's still warm!
If I can get her to a doctor, she might make it!
How did this happen?
Was it a bear?
It might've been unable to hibernate.
It hurts!
It's so cold, it hurts to breathe!
Keep walking!
Move your legs faster!
It's still a long way to town.
Hurry!
Don't you die on me!
I will save you no matter what!
Your big brother will definitely save you, you hear?
Oh, crap!
The snow saved me.
Though it's why I slipped to begin with.
Nezuko?
Nezuko, are you all right?
Don't get up!
Let me carry you to town, okay?
Nezuko!
Sh-She's...
a demon!
Is this what Saburou was talking about?
Nezuko? A man-eating demon?
No, there's no way.
Nezuko's been human from the day she was born!
However, her scent is no longer the same.
But there's no way she killed them!
It looked like she was trying to protect Rokuta,
and there's no blood on her mouth or hands.
And then there's that scent...
That one other scent!
Her body got bigger!
And she's getting stronger and stronger!
While I was sleeping all carefree at Saburou's house,
everyone was brutally murdered!
It must have hurt a lot.
You must've been suffering.
I'm so sorry I wasn't there to save you.
I have to at least save Nezuko somehow.
But I'm not strong enough to push her back!
Nezuko!
Fight it, Nezuko!
Don't give in!
You've gotta hang in there!
Whatever you do, don't become a demon!
You've gotta stay strong!
Hang in there!
What the...
Who's that?
A sword?
Why are you protecting that thing?
She's my sister!
She's my little sister!
Nezuko!
You call that thing your little sister?
Don't move.
My job is to slay demons.
As such, I will claim your sister's head.
Please wait!
She hasn't killed anyone!
There was another scent back there.
One I had never smelled before!
It probably belongs to the one who killed my family!
It wasn't Nezuko!
I don't know what's wrong with her now, but...
But still...
It's simple.
Her wounds were exposed to demon blood,
so she transformed into a demon.
That's how they multiply.
Nezuko would never eat humans!
You can't be serious.
She was about to eat you just now.
You're wrong!
I'm sure she still recognises me!
I won't let her hurt anyone!
I'll make her human again!
I swear I'll cure her!
There is no cure.
Once a human becomes a demon,
there is no turning back.
I'll find a way!
I swear I'll find a way to turn her back!
So please! Please don't kill her!
I'll hunt down the one who slaughtered my family!
I'll make everything okay again!
So please!
Please!
Please don't do it!
Please, don't take anyone else from me.
Please stop.
I beg you!
Please don't kill my little sister!
Please, don't do it!
Please...
Never show your back to an enemy!
Stop that pathetic grovelling!
If it was the least bit effective,
your family wouldn't be dead!
You're a weakling—a coward who folds at adversity.
And you think you can cure your sister,
let alone even find your enemy?
Don't make me laugh!
The weak have neither rights nor options!
It's their fate to be crushed by the strong!
There may be demons out there
who know how to cure your sister!
But don't think for even a second that
they'll happily go along with your wishes!
Naturally, I have zero reason to care about you either!
That's just reality!
Why did you throw yourself over your sister earlier?
Was that your way of protecting her?
Why didn't you swing your axe?
Why did you turn your back to me?
All those blunders led to your sister's capture!
I should've skewered her along with you!
Don't cry.
Don't despair.
Now's not the time for that.
I know you're devastated right now.
Your family was massacred,
and your sister turned into a demon.
It must be painful.
Your heart is likely crushed right now.
I get it.
Had I gotten here even half a day sooner,
your family might still have been alive right now.
However, you can't turn back time.
Feel the anger.
This pure, unforgiving wrath will
become the force that drives you forward!
With such fragile resolve,
protecting or curing your sister,
let alone getting revenge will be mere fantasy!
N—
No!
A straightforward attack driven solely by emotion.
You fool!
Where's his axe?
Right before he passed behind the tree,
he threw that rock at me
and, simultaneously, flung his axe into the air.
He hid his hands as he pretended to attack
so I wouldn't realise he was unarmed.
He knew he didn't stand a chance head-on,
so he tried to take me out after I struck him down!
This kid...
Damn it!
She's gonna eat him!
Nezuko...
It wasn't Nezuko!
She would never eat humans!
This kid is by no means
the first to make such claims, only to be eaten later.
When a demon is starving, it will eat any
human flesh it comes across. Even its own family.
They have no other way to sustain themselves.
I've seen it happen more times than I can count.
This girl has been gravely wounded,
and she's expending energy to heal those injuries.
Her transformation must have also drained her greatly.
That means she's undoubtedly
severely starved right now.
She must've wanted to feast on
a human as soon as possible.
Yet she opted to protect him instead,
and is even going so far as to attack me...
There might just be
something
special about these two.
I'm sorry for leaving you behind, Tanjirou.
Take care of Nezuko for me, okay?
You awake?
Go see an old man named Urokodaki Sakonji
who lives at the foot of Mt. Sagiri.
Tell him Tomioka Giyuu sent you.
Your sister should be fine while it's still cloudy,
but make sure she's never exposed to the sun.
Let's go.