Naho! Kiyo! Sumi!
I'd like you to help me train.
If I stop using my Breathing Technique
in my sleep, I want you to clobber me.
Please help me out!
Sure!
Thank you!
He's got it, right?
He's doing a great job!
Yeah!
What a sad display...
Please give me another chance!
Sure!
If you'd please!
We believe in you!
This time for sure!
Please give me one more chance!
You came alone again today, Tanjirou?
I'm sorry!
I tried my best, but...
Well, it doesn't matter to me.
I'll give them another nudge later!
I'm slowly getting used to training
while maintaining my Breathing!
I still can't keep it up all day
without pushing myself,
Four-hundred-ninety-seven!
but the longer I last,
the more stamina I build up!
Four-hundred-ninety-eight!
Four-hundred-ninety-nine!
Five hundred!
Five-hundred-one!
You can do it!
I can do this!
I'm slowly catching up to her!
I can keep up!
Ow, ow, ow...
Thanks a bunch!
Zenitsu! Inosuke!
I refuse to get involved.
You can do it!
It broke!
Now the only one left is this big one!
Yeah!
I did it!
Thanks, you guys!
Crap.
Tanjirou's already gone off to train.
The sun's only just come up.
I'm not really one to give anything my all.
There's nothing more draining than perseverance.
Oh, it's you.
Maybe it's just because
Tanjirou's so far beyond us now,
but no matter how long he instructs us,
I just can't seem to get the hang of it.
I've since realised that we're
complete and utter lost causes.
Wait, did you just say "Yes, you are"?
Bit cruel, don't you think?
Would it kill you to say
"You're working hard, too" for once?
What was that? "Work harder"?
Guess there's no way around it.
Gross!
Come on, Monitsu.
What Tanjirou is mastering is a skill known as
"Perpetual Concentration Breathing".
By continually using your Breathing
Technique every second of the day,
your base stamina will skyrocket!
Let's give it a go!
Impossible!
Seriously impossible!
I still can't maintain it all day
unless I really throw myself into it,
but if anyone can, it'd be you two!
You go like this to make your lungs expand!
When that rattles your blood, your bones and muscles
will go, "Boom! Pow! You gotta stop it!"
All that's left is to train like crazy!
Now, now.
We're talking about a basic—Nay, an entry-level skill,
so there's no reason you shouldn't be able to do it.
That said, it is true that one must
put in a lot of effort to master the basics.
But hey, this shouldn't
be difficult for you, should it?
Something as easy as this
ought to be child's play. Right, Inosuke?
It'd be a downright shame if not,
what with being an entry-level skill and all.
But if you disagree, I suppose that's that.
No need to brood over it.
The hell you tryna say?!
Of course I can!
Look down on me and I'll rip off your damn tits!
Good luck, Zenitsu!
I'm cheering for you!
Yes, ma'am!
Why not join your comrades, Kanao?
More! More! Boom! Boom! Pow!
Man up, wimp!
You got this, Zenitsu!
It hurts.
I'm hungry.
I'm sad.
I feel hopeless.
I'm in agony.
I'm lonely.
That's what my life was like.
But then, one day,
I heard a snap.
And I never knew pain again.
I never knew pain again.
Living in poverty, even after my parents
sold me, didn't make me feel sad.
Excuse me, may I have a minute of your time?
Could you tell us why that child is all tied up?
Is she a criminal, perhaps?
Can't you tell?
She's covered in dirt and fleas.
And who knows, she might make a break for it.
Hello there. Nice to meet you.
My name is Kochou Kanae.
What's your name?
She ain't got one, y'hear?
Her parents never gave her one.
Happy now? Get out of our business already.
Please don't touch my sister.
The hell's your problem?
If you wanna chit-chat with
the kid, you'd better pay up!
Very well. We'll purchase her.
Would this suffice?
Hey! Get back here!
I'd pick it up right now if I were you!
Y'know, what with the crowd and wind!
Is it really okay to do this?
It's fine!
Please excuse us!
Hands off! It's my property!
Oh, my.
Kanae! Kanae!
Kanae, this child is hopeless!
She won't even touch her food
unless we order her!
She doesn't do anything unless told to act!
Even as her stomach growls and growls!
Oh, my.
What do we do with her?
Now, now, don't be like that, okay?
I love seeing you smile, Shinobu.
But we can't do anything with a kid who
can't even think for herself! It's too dangerous!
Well, you may have a point, but...
She can't do anything by herself!
When you're alone and unsure of what to do,
you can decide by flipping this coin.
Sounds good, right, Kanao?
Sister!
You don't need to get up in arms about it.
Since Kanao is so adorable!
That's not a valid reason!
When given the chance, a person's soul
will open up, so don't worry.
I'm sure yours will one day change
once you fall in love, Kanao!
You're doing great! Keep it up!
Right now! Harder! Bam!
That's it! You can do it, Zenitsu!
You've got this! Looking good!
Inosuke! Inosuke!
Our reforged Sun Blades
will be arriving any minute now!
For real?
Yeah! The crow just told me!
That's Mr. Haganezuka's scent!
Yahoo!
Hurry! Hurry!
Mr. Haganezuka!
Hey! Over here! Mr. Haganezuka!
Long time no see!
Have you been well...
M-Mr. Haganezuka?
How dare you? How dare you snap my sword in two?
You've got a lot a nerve!
I'm sorry!
B-But in my defence,
I came this close to being killed!
My opponent was insanely strong!
Rubbish! That's got nothing to do with it!
This is your fault! All. Your. Fault!
It broke because you're so pitifully weak!
There's no way my sword would snap otherwise!
But...
I'm gonna kill you!
Is that a new training regimen?
As if.
Well, Haganezuka is a very passionate artisan.
Right.
He loves his swords more than anyone.
Even in the land of the swordsmiths,
there's nobody quite like him.
I wouldn't doubt it.
My name is Kanamori.
I was the one who forged Sir Inosuke's new swords.
I would be thrilled if they prove useful in battle.
Pristine, are they not?
The dull sheen of that cyan-grey hue is so cool.
It's a fine colour for a sword.
I'm happy for you, Inosuke.
Your old swords were chipped all over.
How do you like the grips?
The thing is, this is the first time I've ever
forged swords for a dual-wielder.
Sir Inosuke?
Better.
I'll kill you, you ungrateful brat!
You bastard! Are you proud of what you've done?
We're sorry! We're really, really sorry!
You fiend!
That's it! You're bloody dead, kiddo!
Unbelievable! Simply unbelievable!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
Taking a stone to those swords? Unbelievable!
We're really sorry!
Looks like he'll manage.
He was doing his best, after all!
Let's make him rice balls again!
Yeah!
My body's changed!
I can't wait to swing my sword with these hands!
I did it!
Good move! You can do it!
Stay focused! Persevere!
I got past her!
Go!
It'd be cruel to splash this
stinky medicated water over her.
He won!
Does that even count?
Doesn't matter. The result is the same!
Hooray! I did it!
I did it!
Crap.
Just you fucking wait!
All right, say "ah"!
Good! Looks like your jaw is as good as new.
You can close your mouth now.
That concludes the examination.
Since you've recovered physically,
you may take on your missions without qualms.
So I'm done with my training?
Yes. All that's left for you now is actual combat.
Right!
Oh, before I forget.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
What would that be?
Have you ever heard of the Fire God's Dance?
I'm afraid not.
Uh, i-in that case, how about Fire Breathing?
Doesn't ring a bell.
A-Actually, this is something that
happened during my childhood.
Yes, yes.
I see.
So, for some reason, your father used Fire Breathing.
All I can tell you is that while Flame Breathing
does exist, it's different from Fire Breathing.
What? They're not the same thing?
Sorry, I'm not familiar with the details myself.
But I do know they're very strict
about the exact phrasing.
You must never refer to
Flame Breathing as Fire Breathing.
The Flame Hashira, Rengoku,
might know the specifics.
But unfortunately, he's out on a mission currently.
Understood!
Thank you for all you've taught me.
I'll be sure to ask Mr. Rengoku if I see him again.
Right.
Now then, please excuse me!
Kamado?
Yes?
I'm expecting great things from you.
Got it!
She's slept through the entire day again.
I know they said you could be
sleeping to recover your stamina,
but if you don't open your eyes
once in a while, I get worried.
Hey, your brother's probably gonna
be heading out on his next mission soon.
My wounds have healed,
and I've gotten even stronger!
I'm maintaining my Breathing even now!
I think Zenitsu and Inosuke will tag along, too.
Having those two by my side fills me with confidence.
I see.
You think so, too, Nezuko?
They're good guys.
If I want to restore your humanity,
I must take down the strongest demons I can find
and send Miss Tamayo their blood samples.
Am I capable of doing that?
I know you can do it, Tanjirou.
Thanks, Nezuko. You just encouraged me, didn't you?
I'll do my best, okay?
Maintaining my Breathing is way too demanding!
There's just no damn way.
You both look wiped out.
Oh, I know!
Here's a Taisho secret for you!
The medicated water we use for
reflex training, when added to your bath,
is actually great for healing exhaustion and wounds.
Well, I'm off to train,
but maybe you two should catch a break.
Say what? I ain't even close to done!
Gimme more credit than that!
We're doing even more training?
Okay, fine! I just have to show up, right?
Next, Episode 26, "New Mission".
Okay, I'm heading out now, Nezuko!