It's about time you died!
Twist!
Envelope!
Flowing Maelström Spin!
My sword feels so heavy!
But even so!
Modified Second Form!
Horizontal Water Wheel!
I did it!
The Maelström technique loses
a lot of force when it's not underwater!
But thanks to my opponent's attack,
it gained more spin,
and I was able to envelope the arrows!
Curse you! Curse you! Curse you!
All I had to do was bring back your head,
and I would've won his approval!
I'll never forgive you!
I won't ever, ever, ever, ever forgive you!
How dare you shove my face into this vile dirt?!
Don't think I'm going down alone!
Crap! He got me!
The force of these arrows is
much stronger than the ones he used before!
I've gotta keep up using my techniques,
or my body's gonna get smashed!
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide!
The pressure is bearing down on my body...
I can't swing my sword!
I have to...
I have to unleash a technique!
Not here!
I can't lose now!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Waterfall Basin!
Water Surface Slash!
Droplet Ripple Thrust-curve!
Maelström!
I've never used so many techniques
consecutively before!
It feels like my arms are about to get torn off!
Nowhere near enough!
More...
Suffer more!
How much longer...
How long will I have to keep up?
Don't think about it!
Focus on using your techniques!
Keep throwing them out!
Not yet!
It's still not enough yet!
Nezuko...
Miss Tamayo...
Yushirou...
My leg's broken, and I think he got a rib, too.
Th-This isn't good!
I don't even have the energy to grip onto my sword.
I need to get over there!
There's still one more demon!
I'll be there soon!
So be safe, all right?
Please...
Please be safe!
Ridiculous!
Evading linear attacks like these is child's play!
Locating you is a breeze, as well!
Right back at you!
No matter how well you might conceal yourself,
I can see you clear as day!
This is fun!
Hey, you!
Don't be so rash just because you're immortal!
Wh-What's wrong?
What do you think you're doing?
Here she comes!
Look at her...
Lady Tamayo...
You little brat!
You can kick my temari back at me now?
The arrogance!
You damn brat!
Unbelievable.
Lady Tamayo, is this...
All I used on her was a healing serum
made specifically for demons.
Nothing more.
It doesn't make one physically stronger.
What we're seeing is Nezuko's own power.
Without consuming human blood...
Solely through her own power...
Nezuko is gaining strength at a rapid rate.
However, her opponent is also formidable.
If she were to go all-out,
Nezuko would surely fall.
I've got to
do something.
You're pretty fun, you cheeky little thing.
This time, I'm going all-out against you!
Let's see how long you last!
Demon girl of the Twelve Blood Moons.
You're in the way!
Stay on the sideline, you damn fugitive!
Just tell me one thing, please.
Are you aware of Kibutsuji's true identity?
What the hell did you say?
That man is nothing but a coward.
He lives in constant fear of something.
Silence!
Damn you! Shut up!
Do you know why it is that demons
aren't allowed to band together?
The reason why demons cannibalise each other?
It's to prevent other demons from
grouping up and attacking him.
He manipulates demons into acting this way.
Demons like you.
Shut up!
Shut up, shut up!
There's no way he's that petty!
Lady Tamayo is using her Blood Arts.
The power our lord wields is absolutely outlandish!
There's nobody that can beat him!
Not Lord Kibutsuji!
You've uttered his name out loud, haven't you?
You just triggered his curse.
Magical Incense of Broad Daylight.
It weakens its target's brain functions,
rendering that person unable to lie or keep secrets.
It's immensely potent, Lady Tamayo!
I do feel sorry for you, but...
Farewell.
Please forgive me!
I'm begging you! Please! Please forgive me!
Did she just die?
She will die shortly.
That's the curse.
Her physical body will be destroyed
by Kibutsuji's cells that remain in her body.
In general, battles between demons are futile.
It's pointless.
They can't inflict fatal wounds upon one another.
The only things that can are sunlight and
the swords the Demon Slayers wield.
Kibutsuji alone appears to be
able to destroy demon cells.
Don't inhale Lady Tamayo's spell!
It's harmful to the human body!
You catch that?
Tanjirou...
She was not one of the Twelve Blood Moons.
The Twelve Blood Moons have numbers
engraved onto their eyeballs,
but she's lacking one.
That other demon was most likely
not a Blood Moon, either.
They were too weak.
Too weak?
At that level?
If Lady Tamayo says so, there's no mistake.
Still, who knew there were such stupid demons?
She had the gall to harm Lady Tamayo.
Got her just desserts if you ask me.
I hope this blood will be instrumental
in developing the healing serum.
I will treat Nezuko.
Not only did I medicate her,
she also inadvertently inhaled my spell.
I'm so sorry.
Don't move a muscle!
You're on your own now!
I don't want to leave Lady Tamayo's side!
Not for a second!
Ma... ri...
Mari...
Here's your temari.
Play with me.
It's like she's a child.
Even though she must've murdered dozens of people.
She was deluded into thinking
she was a Blood Moon.
Deceived and compelled to fight...
And finally,
she fell victim to Kibutsuji's curse.
There's no salvation for her.
After you die, not even your bones will remain.
Is this the price you pay for killing others?
Kibutsuji...
This is how that man treats even those who revere him!
He's a true demon!
Miss Tamayo!
Yushirou?
Over here!
Not that you need to come at all.
But if you want to, get down here.
Yushirou!
I was just joking!
Hurry down, Tanjirou!
Oh, right!
Nezuko!
I moved her to this basement,
where the morning sun won't reach her.
Nezuko?
Why, you!
Step away from Lady Tamayo!
That's so rude!
Stop it, Yushirou.
I don't mind at all.
Yes, madam!
You have such a kind heart, Lady Tamayo.
Your beauty goes beyond compare!
Cut that out!
Nezuko has been acting this way since she woke up.
Is she all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
She's okay.
She probably thinks of you as family.
Cut it out!
Family?
But I thought the spell Nezuko is under
causes her to see humans as her family.
And Yushirou and I are demons.
Cut it out!
But Nezuko sees you two as humans.
That's why she tried to protect you.
At first, I didn't like the idea of
Nezuko being under a spell,
but since it looks like she still has
a will of her own, I'm glad tha—
I-I'm so sorry! Nezuko!
Nezuko! L-Let go of her!
It's rude, y'know?
Thank you...
Nezuko!
Thank you!
Do you still wish to live?
Do you still wish to live, even if
it means giving up your humanity?
If this goes on, you will most likely
succumb to your illness.
However,
to stop being human will
cause you much pain and grief.
Regardless, do you still wish to live?
Yushirou and I will leave this region.
We've gotten too close to Kibutsuji.
We must conceal our whereabouts soon,
or the risk will be too great.
Not to mention, even if I think
I've managed to conceal my identity,
when I interact with humans as a doctor,
people sometimes see through me.
The young and elderly are particularly perceptive.
Tanjirou.
Yes?
Would you like us to take Nezuko in?
I can't fully guarantee her safety,
but I believe it will be less dangerous
than taking her into battle.
That might be true.
She's got a point.
It would probably be better
for Nezuko to be in their care.
Thank you for the kind offer, Miss Tamayo.
However...
We'll be staying together.
We refuse to be apart from each other.
Never again.
Very well.
In that case, I wish you
long-lasting fortune in battle.
Goodbye, then.
We'll be leaving after we erase all traces of ourselves.
You two get going now!
Right!
Well then. We wish both of you well!
Let's go, Nezuko.
Hey!
Don't go rushing off like that!
Tanjirou!
Your kid sister...
She's beautiful.
South-south-east!
Your next location is south-south-east!
I heard you the first time!
I know already. Give me a break and pipe down!
I'm begging you!
Message received, so please!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
I could drop dead at a moment's notice, y'know!
That's why I want you to marry me!
So please! Please, I'm begging you!
Wh-What's going on over there?
What on earth?
"South-south-east!"
I mean, I just fought! Does it hurt
to give me some time to rest?
What? I nailed it?
Not that I was really trying to or anything.
Well, it's time for a Taisho secret!
The Demon Slayers' messengers,
the Kasugai Crows, each have their own name.
I hear that mine is named Tennouji Matsuemon.
Okay, one last impression.
"This is your first assignment as a Demon Slayer!"
Hey! We've been fighting non-stop
ever since I started getting assignments!
Next, Episode 11, "Tsuzumi Mansion"!
Demon Slayers don't really get much time to rest, huh?