tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
I've found my reason to become stronger
boku wo tsurete susume
So let's go and press on 'til the end
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Hung up on memories of a life of grief
kowabaru kokoro
My heart barely stirs
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
My trembling hands are still looking for what they long to grasp
sore dakesa
And that's all I need
yoru no nioi ni
Even gazing up at the sky
I spent all thirty nights
sora nirandemo
Through the fragrance of the night
Staring into the sky
kawatte ikeru no wa jibun jishin dake
The only thing I can change is myself
sore dakesa
And nothing else
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
I've found my reason to become stronger
boku wo tsurete susume
So let's go and press on 'til the end
doushitatte
No matter what!
kesenai yume mo
My dreams can't be erased
tomarenai ima mo
And time refuses to wait
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
But so long as there's someone left to protect
nandemo tachiagare
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
sekai ni uchinomesarete
I learnt what it meant to lose
makeru imi wo shitta
As the world brought me down
guren no hana yo sakihokore
May the blood-soaked lotuses bloom bright
unmei wo terashite
Illuminating our path ahead
hito shirezu hakanai
Ever-fleeting visions of what could have been
chiriyuku ketsumatsu
Wilting away before my very eyes
mujou ni yabureta
Dominated by selfish cruelty
himei no kaze fuku
A raging storm plows over the land
dareka no warau kage
Crying out with laments of others
dareka no nakigoe
As everyone willingly sacrifices one another
daremo ga shiawase wo negatteru
Just wishing for their own happiness
doushitatte
No matter what!
kesenai yume mo
My dreams can't be erased
tomarenai ima mo
And time refuses to wait
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
But so long as I have someone left to protect
arigatou kanashimi yo
I'll take pride in bearing their pain
sekai ni uchinomesarete
I learnt what it meant to lose
makeru imi wo shitta
As the world brought me down
guren no hana yo sakihokore
May the blood-soaked lotuses bloom bright
unmei wo terashite
Illuminating our path ahead
My fate dyed a deep red
unmei wo terashite