Beast Breathing! Seventh Form!
Spatial Awareness!
Found them?
Yeah! That way!
I'm picking up a powerful aura from that way!
You are?
Way to go, Inosuke!
We gotta take care of these guys
or we'll never get anywhere!
Damn. Isn't there...
Isn't there something we can do?
Ne—
Nezu—
Whe— Whe—
Wh-Whe—
Whe—
Where are you?
Dammit!
What a pain in the ass!
I'm just gonna demolish 'em all at once!
You can't do that!
There's gotta be something we can do!
So let's try not to hurt our—
Murata?
Leave these guys to me and go on ahead!
Why you tryna sound so cool,
Mr. Pissed-My-Pants?
I never pissed my pants, you stupid boar!
I wasn't talking to you, so butt out!
I know that wasn't my finest moment
back there, but I'm a Demon Slayer, too!
I'll find a way to deal with these guys!
I now know I just need to cut the threads,
and that they can only move in very basic ways!
I'll watch out for the spiders as well!
Plus, the demon probably has
better control the closer they are!
So both of you should go!
Understood! We appreciate it!
Let's go, Inosuke!
Let go of me, dammit!
Let me introduce my fist to his face first!
Who you calling a stupid boar?!
Oh, shut up already!
Drop it and get the hell out of here!
Just you wait! I'll kick your teeth in when I get back!
Dammit! I'll punch his lights out
if it's the last thing I do!
Knock it off, will you?
He called me a stupid boar, Monjirou!
It's "Tanjirou"!
That aside, you sure we're heading the right way?
My senses never lie!
But...
The hell is up with these annoying webs?
That's just a sign that we're closing in on them!
Here comes another bunch.
No...
Don't come any closer.
Please summon someone of a higher rank!
If you don't, everyone will end up dead!
Please...
Please!
I wonder if you can defeat them.
The closer you get to me,
the thicker these webs are,
and the stronger my marionettes become.
Mother...
You can win, right?
Rui...
Don't you think you're taking too long?
You'd better hurry up
or I'll tell Father.
I can do it! I can handle this!
I promise to protect you!
So please! Not your father!
Don't tell your father! Anyone but him!
Hurry up, then.
Die! Die! Just die already!
Or else there'll be hell for me to pay!
Run!
She's fast!
I'm being controlled!
I can't move my own body!
I was never this strong!
Since the demon's forcing her
to move with the threads,
it doesn't care if her bones break!
This is cruel!
You're so stubborn!
How about this?
That sound!
P-Please kill me!
My arms and legs...
The bones are piercing my organs!
Every time I'm forced to move,
the pain becomes stronger!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm a dead man no matter what, so...
So please, save me!
Please, put me out of my misery!
Sure, leave it to me!
Wai—
Wait! We've gotta find a way to save him!
Oh, shut up!
You've gotta shut your damn mouth already!
But...
He wants us to kill him, right?
These guys are pretty fast.
If we get caught napping, we're dead!
I know that!
Let me think for a second!
I don't want to attack them.
But there's no point in cutting the threads.
They'll just get reattached!
If we want to prevent them from moving...
I know!
Huh? Hey!
Good! She's following me!
Hey, what are you runnin' around in circles for?
Stop messing around!
Total Concentration!
What unbelievable strength!
Good! You're all tangled up!
Wha—
The hell is up with that?
I wanna do that, too!
Take this!
Y'see that? Whatever you can do, I can do too!
My bad! I kinda missed it!
What the—?!
I mean, can you really blame me?
Damn!
These puppets are all useless!
I have no choice but to bring out that marionette.
Nezuko!
Nezuko! Where are you?
Nezuko...
Tanjirou...
Wild Boar...
Chuntarou!
Where did everyone go?
I'm sorry about everything, okay?
Chuntarou?
You mean you came after me?
You're so adorable!
Second to Nezuko, but still!
I apologise for everything!
All right, let's go look for Nezuko together!
Look at that!
Check it out! I've tossed up more than you!
Right! One more to go!
Okay. I'm gonna do it one more time,
so keep a close eye this time!
You got it! Go get 'em!
Just try not to be too rough!
I don't need these fragile human puppets anymore!
They're useless!
Absolutely useless!
Dammit! They're all dead now!
Let's go.
Yeah, let's...
This way! We're startin' to get real close!
Now that the wind's changed direction,
I can pick up scents properly again!
I can pinpoint the demon's location now!
There's two scents left!
There!
Inosuke!
I sensed that thing long before you did!
I'm gonna shave its head clean off!
That thing...
It's got no head!
Nezuko!
Where are you?
Where are you, Tanjirou, Inosuke?
Don't just leave me all by myself
in this terrifying forest!
What was that?
Y'know what?
I'm starting to get really pissed.
I'll find Nezuko as soon as possible,
and then it's so long, scary forest!
Nezuko!
That thing's got no weak points!
I can't chop off something that ain't there!
Inosuke!
What do we do?
Calm down! We'll inflict a monk's robe cut on it!
Let's try slicing from the right side of
the base of its neck down to his left waist!
It's a lot to cover, and I'm sure
it's really tough, but I bet...
Hold up! In unison...
He's fast!
But not too fast for me to dodge!
Crap! I forgot about the spiders!
I can't move!
I'm screwed!
Inosuke, we have to fight alongside each other!
Let's put our heads together!
Let's work together so we can take down this demon!
Damn you!
Don't make me any giddier than I already am!
You're in my way!
Inosuke, launch yourself off me!
Jump, Inosuke! Jump!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide!
Go for the monk's robe cut!
Dammit, the hell's with him? He really pisses me off!
Everything's just gotta go his way, huh?
He acts as if this was all predetermined or somethin'!
As if it were flowing as naturally as water in a river...
It ain't about being first to him, but...
He's got his eyes set on the overall flow of the battle!
Great! He cut it just right!
Way to go! You defeated it, Inosuke!
Inosuke?
Anything you can do, I can do too, dumbass!
This scent...
So that's your aim, huh, Inosuke?
They got him! He's dead!
My strongest and fastest marionette was...
It's Rui's fault for threatening me!
He made me panick!
I panicked! Panicked!
Above me?
Water Breathing!
First Form!
He'll kill me! He's gonna chop my head off!
Think! You have to think!
But...
If I die, I'll be free.
And then I'll finally know peace.
Fifth Form!
Blessed Rain After the Drought!
This is...
It feels like I'm being showered by a gentle rain.
It doesn't hurt at all.
It's not agonising.
I just feel warm.
I never dreamt that my end would be this tranquil.
And now
I'll be free.
I'm so sorry! I apologise, so please forgive me!
What are you angry about?
Why are you so discontent?
It's your own fault for not realising why he's mad.
But how could I?
Mom's in trouble with Dad again!
Stop! No! No!
Those eyes...
Such kind eyes...
Back when I was human,
I think there may have been someone who
looked at me with such kind eyes.
I wonder who it could've been.
I can't remember.
It was someone who always treasured me.
I wonder how they're doing now.
There's a Blood Moon here.
Wait!
Be careful...
There's a Blood Moon here...
A genuine member of the Twelve Blood Moons
on this mountain!
Anything you can do, I can do too, y'know!
Maybe, but I know something you can't do, Inosuke.
What'd you say?
After all this time, you still can't get my name right.
I do remember your damn name,
Kamaboko Gonpachirou!
Wrong.
Shakariki Gengorou!
Itadaki Tontarou!
Totally wrong!
But now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I hear that Inosuke can call someone by their
correct name about once every seven times.
You've already mangled it three times.
Can you really get it right?
Anago Kanjirou!
Hey, you're getting warmer!
Hamado Tangorou!
So close!
Amado Jangorou!
Ninety-nine percent there!
Kamado...
Hey, who cares about your name anyway?
I was this close to hearing it.
Next, Episode 17, "You Must Master a Single Move"!
You are you, and I am me.
Got that, Tanjirou?