What's the matter, honey?
Honey?
Stop!
What the—?!
What happened?
I-Is that blood?
Stop!
Honey!
Ma'am!
Worry about yourself first!
Please take a cloth and apply pressure to the wound!
It'll be okay. I'll figure out a way to handle this.
Her wound isn't fatal!
Apply more pressure!
More! Tie it up with a rope!
Everything's gonna be okay.
He hasn't killed anyone yet!
He was walking down the street
like normal just a second ago.
Are you okay?
You mustn't look.
It isn't safe here, Rei. Let's be on our way.
Where'd he go?
Dammit!
I can't just leave this guy here!
Kibutsuji Muzan!
You won't get away from me!
I'll find you no matter where you go!
What's the matter with that boy?
What do you think, Tsukihiko?
It doesn't matter how far you run!
I'll follow you to the depths of Hell,
and my blade will claim your head!
For as long as I breathe, I will never forgive you!
What the hell is going on here?
Is it a drunken brawl?
Step away from that man, kiddo!
I can't!
Please get some restraints!
I beg you!
Shut up and get off him already!
Please stop!
I'm the only one who can pin him down!
Move!
Please don't do that!
Just look at his face. He's lost his mind!
Pull this kid off of him!
Please stop!
I don't want this person to kill anyone!
Don't interfere, please!
Dammit! Look, you little...
If you're gonna keep resisting...
Bewitching Blood.
Incense of Visual Phantasm.
What is that smell?
What are all these patterns?
What's going on? I can't see anything!
Are we under attack?
If so, we're in trouble!
Is the scent growing stronger?
You still
refer to those who have become demons
as if they were human.
And you even tried to save him.
If you're willing to go that far,
please allow me to lend you a hand.
But why?
You...
You smell like a...
That's right.
I am...
a demon, and also a doctor.
And I wish to obliterate Kibutsuji.
Are you not coming with us, Daddy?
Daddy has work.
I have a business meeting to attend.
That disturbance still weighs on my mind as well.
Dear...
It's all right.
I'm just going to have a word with the police.
Now, hop in.
Daddy, come home soon, okay?
I will. You be a good girl now.
Take them back to our house.
Go on.
C'mon, Bro! Let's hit another bar!
You good, Yacchan?
Never been better!
I ain't even drunk ye—
The hell's your problem, dude?
My apologies.
Hey, hold it!
I'm in a bit of a hurry, so if you'll excuse me...
Whazzat? Come again?
Those're some fancy threads you got there.
Pisses me off!
And you're as pale as a ghost.
It looks like you'll drop dead at any second!
What's up? Cat got your tongue?
Yacchan!
What're you doin' to my little brother?!
Love!
He's dead!
Yacchan's not breathing!
You son of a—
Does my complexion look unhealthy to you?
Is my face pale?
Do I appear sickly to you?
Does it appear like I'm at death's door?
Does it seem as if I'm dying?
Oh no, no, no, no.
I'm a living being who's infinitely close to perfection.
What do you think will happen
if I keep flooding you with my blood?
The human body cannot withstand
the speed of transformation.
Your cells will rupture.
Bring me the head of the demon hunter
with the hanafuda earrings.
Understood?
As you wish.
Your wish is our command.
Those earrings...
Aight, listen up here!
I'm telling you this ain't about the money!
What I can't forgive is that you
refuse to eat my udon, got it?
I'm sorry! Please serve me another bowl!
You gonna eat it?
Yes!
Every last drop?
All of it!
Good!
You, too!
If you're gonna have udon,
take off that bamboo thingy first!
What's it even for?
Take these chopsticks and chow down, all right?!
I'll have her share!
Two bowls, if you'd please!
S-Sure thing.
Thank you kindly for the meal!
That was delicious!
So long as you get that, we're all good!
Come again!
Sorry for leaving you behind like that, Nezuko.
What's wrong, Nezuko?
Were you waiting for us?
I was instructed by my lady to take you to her.
I could've just tracked you by scent.
She's in a place that's covered under a cloaking spell.
No way you'd find it.
Cloaking spell?
Anyway...
Isn't she a demon?
And an eyesore to boot.
Eyesore?
Does he mean "ugly"?
Who?
Nezuko?
Who in their right mind
would call her an eyesore?
Just take a good look at those features!
Nezuko was known as the town beauty!
Let's get a move on.
Yeah, let's!
But no way is she an eyesore! Not on your life!
Look at her someplace with better lighting!
Like over there! C'mon, let's go!
Oh, I get it, I get it! It's the muzzle, right?
Yeah, that's gotta be it!
Take another good look at her after I take it off!
Hurry up.
Before someone sees us.
There's a house behind the dead end!
Get over here!
Listen. Make sure not to offend my lady in any way.
Personally, I couldn't care less
about what happens to you.
I only brought you here because she insisted!
R-Right.
Come in.
I have returned.
Welcome back.
Sorry about leaving them to you.
How's the woman?
She'll be just fine.
Unfortunately, I have to keep her husband
restrained in an underground cell.
Isn't it hard for your kind to treat people's wounds?
Are you insinuating we drool at
the smell of our patients' blood?
I'm sorry.
Enough. Why would you resort to violence?
I never introduced myself, did I?
My name is Tamayo.
This boy here is Yushirou.
Please, try to get along.
I don't think that's gonna happen.
It isn't hard for us.
I believe it's considerably easier
for me than for normal demons.
I've altered my body considerably.
I've also removed Kibutsuji's curse.
Curse? A-Altered your body?
Come this way.
Nezuko! Where are your manners?
That's quite all right.
Please make yourselves at home.
Sorry.
Now then, allow me to continue.
I adjusted our bodies so we no longer
need to feed upon humans to survive.
A small amount of human blood is all we require.
Blood?
You mean...
You may find it distasteful, but what we do is
buy blood from people unable to make ends meet,
and tell them that it's for transfusions.
Of course, we never take enough to harm them.
I see.
So that's why they don't have
the distinct smell of demons.
But they still need human blood.
If blood is all they need, then Nezuko...
Yushirou can get by with even less blood.
I was the one who made him a demon.
You were?
But...
Indeed.
It is said that no one but Kibutsuji
holds the power to produce demons.
And that's essentially correct.
In the last two hundred years,
Yushirou has been the only person
I've managed to transform into a demon.
Two...
Two hundred years...
Yushirou's the only one you
transformed in two hundred years?
Just how old are you, Miss Tamayo?
Don't ask a lady her age,
you ill-mannered scoundrel!
Yushirou!
The next time you hit that boy,
I'll make you regret it!
Yes, madam!
She's beautiful even when she's angry!
There's one thing I'd like to clear up with you.
I am not out to create more demons.
I only perform the procedure on the terminally ill
or those so gravely injured,
they don't have long to live.
And in those cases,
I always ask them beforehand
if they wish to live on as demons.
The scent she's giving off
is pure and devoid of deception.
I can trust her.
Miss Tamayo,
once someone has become a demon,
is there a way to restore their humanity?
Spot anything?
I do.
I see footprints.
We got them.
Up ahead, around the corner.
There are three of them.
And one's carrying some kind of big box.
How shall we go about killing them, I wonder?
I'm bursting with power.
It's all thanks to the blood he shared with us.
We shall be slaying them brutally, of course.
A way to restore one's humanity...
does exist.
Please tell me how—
Don't you dare get close to Lady Tamayo!
Yushirou...
I only threw him, Lady Tamayo. I did not hit him.
You mustn't do either.
Yes, madam!
Ow, ow, ow.
Please tell me how.
No matter the wound or ailment,
there is always a cure or treatment.
At this point in time, however, I am
unable to reverse the transformation.
But surely, one day...
Nevertheless,
we are dedicated to establishing
such a method of treatment.
Towards that end, I'd like to request your aid.
To produce such an elixir,
it is necessary to study the blood of numerous demons.
I have two favours to ask of you.
One, permission to study your sister's blood.
Two, to collect as many blood samples from demons
with a high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood as you can.
Nezuko's condition is extremely rare and unique.
I understand that she was
asleep for two straight years,
and I believe that her body
underwent changes during that time.
Normally, any demon who went that long without
consuming the flesh or blood of human or beast
would unquestionably go berserk.
Lady Tamayo is beautiful today, too!
I'm sure she'll be beautiful again tomorrow!
And yet, surprisingly,
Nezuko shows none of those signs.
This miracle might prove to be
the key to finding a cure.
Nezuko...
The second request will be a harsh one to fulfil.
A demon with a high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood
means a demon close in strength to Kibutsuji himself.
Extracting blood from such demons will be no easy task.
Are you still willing to go along with my requests?
If there's no other way, I'll do it.
If it means you'll be able to research all these
demons' blood and develop a cure...
If that happens, it won't just help Nezuko.
We'll be able to save lots of people, right?
That's right.
Get down!
Have you decided how to kill them?
Brutally, of course!
I'm starting with the Taisho secret today!
Yushirou's hobby is to
write in his Lady Tamayo journal.
I hear that he churns out seven to ten pages a day.
And now, I've found that very journal.
Shall we have a peek?
Let's see.
"January 10th. Lady Tamayo was
ethereal and gorgeous again today."
"At 17:10, she called my name. Twice, no less!"
"Her voice was beautiful."
"At 17:29, when Lady Tamayo,
deep in thought, slipped on the step..."
Next time, Episode Nine,
"The Temari Demon and The Arrow Demon"!
Let's pretend we never saw this.