Were you acquainted with any of them?
There don't seem to be any survivors around here.
We were informed that several
rookie Mizunoto had joined the battle,
but they may be dead by now, don't you think?
Let's go.
Isn't the moon lovely?
Won't you be a bit more chummy with me?
We're in this together.
I'm only here to slay demons.
How callous of you!
All right. Let's split up here, then.
I shall proceed from the west.
Agreed.
Stay away...
from my family!
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
No way!
My blade won't cut through!
That's damn tough!
My Water Wheel didn't even leave a scratch!
What should I do?
Stay away...
from my family!
What're you looking at?
I'm over here!
Go screw yourself!
Ouch!
That slap packs a fuckin' punch!
What do I do? I'm not strong enough!
I can barely focus after losing so much blood.
Water Breathing!
Modified Second Form!
Horizontal Water Wheel!
The hell?
What was that?
Inosuke! You okay?
He did that?
That was some stunt, dammit!
All right!
This is the perfect opportunity
to cut through his neck!
Water Breathing!
The final and most powerful form!
His aura's changed!
This guy's about to pull off something mind-blowing!
This will be the end of him!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Tenth Form!
W-Watch out!
Kentarou!
I-Inosuke!
Survive! Pull through until I'm back!
That guy's a Blood Moon!
Don't die!
Whatever you do, don't die!
Oh, shit!
It's getting really hard to breathe.
I can't even feel my arms or legs anymore.
Nezuko...
I'm sorry.
Don't give up!
Don't
give up!
Who are you?
Yoo-hoo!
Are you okay?
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Good, I managed to break my fall...
I beg of you! Please stop!
What are you looking at?
We're not holding some theatre play here.
Wh-What are you doing?
Aren't you two allies?
Allies?
Don't lump us in with such frail trifle.
We're family.
We're joined by a much more powerful bond.
And besides,
this is a matter between me and my sister.
Don't interfere.
Or I'll carve you up.
You're wrong!
If the bond between you is strong enough,
it doesn't matter whether you're family or allies.
They're equally precious!
Calling it shallow simply because
there's no blood relation...
That's simply not true!
Not only that, but those who share
a strong bond give off the scent of trust!
But all I'm picking up from you two
is the scent of terror, hatred, and repulsion!
You can't call that a bond!
It's an imitation!
Your bond is fake!
You...
Wow, would look at that!
A demon that's just the right size.
Even I can take down a kid like him.
Please hold on—
You care to back off?
I'd much prefer to take the safe route up the ladder.
The higher your rank, the bigger
your paycheque and all that.
My unit may have been wiped out,
but at least I get to slay a proper demon
and head down the mountain in one piece.
Take this!
No, stop! Don't do it!
He was cut into pieces in an instant!
But how did he...
Hey, what did you just say?
Hey,
care to repeat what you just said?
He's so intimidating!
He's so overbearing, I can hardly breathe.
I'm sorry, Inosuke.
Hang in there a little bit longer, okay?
I'll come running over
as soon as I defeat this demon!
I'll come save you, no matter what!
What are you waiting for?
Let's hear you say that again.
Come on.
Say it again for me, will you?
Sure!
I'll say it as many times as you want!
The bond between you is fake!
Oh, f-fuck!
Dammit!
All I can do is hide.
This is just pathetic!
I've gotta come up with something.
How do you cut through
something that's sword-proof?
What do I do?
I've gotta think up something!
Think! Think! Think! Thi—
Whoa!
This is bad! Really, really bad!
I've gotta...
I've gotta hang in there until he comes back!
What the hell am I thinking?!
This ain't the time
to screw around, shit-for-brains!
Screw you!
Looks like I got infected by Tontarou's germs!
Stop and think?
What was I thinking?
What am I, some jackass?
Why the hell would I use my head?
Fuck yeah!
I cut through!
The answer is actually pretty simple.
If one sword don't work, just use more sword!
I mean, look at this!
I've got two of these bad boys!
I'm almighty!
Where the fuck do you think you're going?
Screw you!
Get back here, asshole!
I'll give you a small heads up:
I don't plan on killing you quickly.
After ripping you to shreds, I'll carve you up.
That said,
if you take back what you said,
I'll do you a favour and make it swift.
I refuse!
I meant every word I said!
What I said was the truth!
You're the one who's in the wrong!
You son of a bitch!
Where the hell did you run off to?
I'm telling ya this doesn't hurt!
What doesn't hurt doesn't hurt!
If it's come to this,
I'll hafta sniff 'im out!
There you are!
You dumb piece of shit!
Why'd you climb so high up?
Damn you!
Tryna make me use my head again, are ya?
In your dreams!
What the...
Oh, I get it!
He's trembling at the sight of me, huh?
It's a little late for that!
What the...
Now what?
D-Did he just fucking molt?
Nope.
That's too big, even for me.
This is looking pretty bad!
I've never felt this much pressure
from an opponent before!
This force alone is gonna crush me!
There's no point.
I can't win.
I'm dead meat.
I'm gonna die.
Don't die!
Survive! Pull through until I'm back!
Always live your lives with great pride.
I wish you much luck in battle!
I won't lose!
No way in hell am I gonna lose!
I'm Hashibira Inosuke of the Demon Slayers!
Come and get some, motherfucker!
That was fast!
I couldn't even see him!
Beast Breathing!
Third Fang!
Tear and Gorge!
They snapped?
Shit!
I couldn't react in time!
Stay away from my family!
I won't die!
Beast Breathing!
First Fang!
Eat this!
Pierce and Bore!
They're in!
They're in, but...
You've gotta be kiddin' me.
It doesn't even make him flinch!
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Inosuke.
I want at least you to survive,
Inosuke.
Wh-Who's that?
Wh-What was that?
Did he cut through him?
Wh-Who is that?
Who on earth...
He's fast!
Water Breathing.
Fourth Form.
Striking Tide!
H-Holy shit!
I-I've never seen anyone
as incredible as this guy!
I can smell again!
The acrid odour's starting to fade.
I can pick up the scent of the threads now!
It's an even playing field now!
He's smarter than I gave him credit for.
He doesn't flinch back in fear.
Oh well, not like it matters anyway.
Water Breathing!
First Form!
Water Surface Slash!
Hey!
Wow! I'd be damned if you didn't
take out that demon in a flash!
Who are you?
I saw you using the same attack
as Monjirou! You his friend?
What, you don't see me here?
Look at me, dammit!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What do you say to that?
Hey!
Okay, then, I'll let you in on a secret!
I hear that Tanjirou's favourite rice ball flavour
is plum seaweed, and Zenitsu really digs salmon!
Next, Episode 19, "The Fire God".
So you can talk!