I've been able to handle anything thrown my way!
I have what it takes!
And not today!
Not tomorrow!
Not even if I'm torn
will I ever stop flowing!
Where are you, Tanjirou?
I can still hear that creepy sound.
Just be safe, Tanjirou!
Say, Zenitsu...
Is it just me, or are we going around in circles?
You think so, too?!
I was getting the same feeling!
Attaboy, Shouichi! I knew I could count on you!
All right, could you check if this room is safe?
What the heck?
Okay, fine! Please, just stop giving me that look!
I'll do it myself!
The coast is clear.
Let's go this way!
Tanjirou,
please show up!
Th-The room...
just flipped!
I can do it!
I know I can!
I'm a guy that gets things done!
Broken bones or not, it doesn't matter!
I can do it!
I can fight!
I'll show him that I'm unstoppable,
no matter what he throws my way!
It's no good! Nothing's changed at all!
Spirit alone isn't gonna get me anywhere!
Your head...
Use your head, not just your spirit!
Think! Think! Thin—
Close call!
That was way too close!
Damn! This is so annoying!
I've got to consume more rareblood!
There's no time to waste!
There isn't even time to stop and think!
Hey, you!
What's your name?
Kyougai.
Kyougai!
I'm not handing over Kiyoshi—
the rareblood to you!
I won't cave in!
I'll never give up!
Just give it up, will you?
I'm going to get my hands on some rareblood
and reclaim my spot among the Twelve Blood Moons!
Just give it up, will you?
It's really boring!
There's no excitement to be had in your writing.
Every last word is utter tripe!
No beauty, no fragility, no impact to speak of.
Why don't you just give up on writing already?
You're just wasting paper and fountain pens!
You don't even step outside anymore these days.
It's no wonder you've grown completely dull.
You should just continue playing the drum instead
if you're gonna shut yourself in anyway.
Although it's not like you're
skilled enough to play it for others, either!
Get out of my sight,
you damn insect!
Rapid Drumming!
Don't tell me he can drum even faster!
The speed of these rotations is making me dizzy!
This is bad!
What amazing skill!
Not only that,
but he's got five claws now instead of three!
I get it.
Dodging his blows without
stepping on the papers
helped me figure out how to move my body without
aggravating my wounds, as well as how to breathe!
Take shallow breaths. Quickly!
That breathing technique will help reinforce
the muscles around my broken leg!
And before each claw attack,
there's the scent of mold!
Here comes that claw attack!
Above!
Left!
Right!
Behind!
He's dodging all of my attacks!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Ninth Form!
Splashing Water Flow, Turbulent!
Minimise the landing time
and area as much as possible!
He's adapting to the room's orientation changes!
Go! Get in there!
Get within striking distance!
Forward!
Get right up in his face!
There it is—the opening thread!
Kyougai!
Your Blood Art was incredible!
Ow, ow, ow!
I shouldn't have taken in such a deep breath!
I'm the eldest son!
The eldest!
Boy...
Answer me.
Was my Blood Art
really incredible?
It absolutely was.
However...
I can't forgive you for killing humans.
I see.
Oh, wait. I've got to get a blood sample.
It extracted the blood.
It really does draw it automatically
if you stick it in there.
That Yushirou sure is skilled,
creating something like this.
A cat?
You're the one who's going to
deliver this to Miss Tamayo, huh?
There, there. Thanks!
Now you're all set.
All right, take care now!
Hey—
I was told that under Yushirou's spell,
it would be invisible until it meowed,
and then disappear again
when it meowed a second time.
So it's true, huh?
Where are those two?
I have to find them!
My...
writing...
There's no excitement to be had in your writing.
Every last word is utter tripe!
No beauty, no fragility, no impact to speak of.
It wasn't trash at all.
At the very least, not to that boy.
He saw value in my writing.
Rest in peace.
Both my Blood Art
and my drum playing
have been acknowledged.
Kiyoshi!
Teruko!
Tanjirou...
Why are you throwing stuff at me?
We're so sorry!
The drum disappeared, so we panicked.
I see.
Well, I'm glad you're safe.
You did a good job hanging in there.
You too, Kiyoshi.
Come on, let's head outside.
Hop onto my back.
Is your leg okay?
Yes!
You just have to keep it up a little longer.
I'm picking up Zenitsu and Shouichi's scent.
They must've gone outside already.
They're both safe n—
I smell blood!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. Let's hurry!
Take this!
Move it!
Draw your sword and fight me!
You spineless punk!
Tanjirou...
I protected it.
Since you said...
this was more important to you...
than your life.
I've...
always had really good hearing.
One time, I knew what people said while I was asleep.
Everyone was creeped out.
I don't hear any demons anymore.
Tanjirou, you defeated them, didn't you?
I can hear you guys, and also
these weird, loud footsteps.
...itsu! Zenitsu!
Zenitsu!
Thank goodness! Are you all right?
When the room spun around, we got thrown outside.
We fell from the second story window.
Did we now?
I'm fine since you were protecting me, but...
I'm glad to hear that.
So tell me, what's with all the tears?
Now I get it!
I fell right onto my head, didn't I?
Yes.
Am I gonna...
Am I gonna die?
My head is starting to spin.
What's this? What's this?
Chargin' through! Chargin' through!
There it is again!
The monster boar!
I can sense a demon!
It's him!
I can tell from his voice!
He's the fifth survivor!
During Final Selection,
he was the first to rush up the mountain
and come down again before anyone else!
It's Mr. Impatient!
Found it!
Stop!
Who the fuck're you?
Get out of the way!
I'm Agatsuma Zenitsu!
I'm with the Demon Slayers, just like you!
Demon Slayers?
Then I shouldn't have to tell you!
We've gotta get rid of that thing!
Now, get the hell out of my way!
I'm not moving!
This is Tanjirou's—
Stop talking back to me!
Fine, in that case I'll destroy both you and the box!
Now freakin' move it!
Why, you...
I won't let you...
I won't let you lay a finger on the thing inside this box!
It's important to Tanjirou!
Hey, c'mon now!
Are you bloody kiddin' me?
There's a demon in there!
Don't you get that?
I've known that from the very start!
I knew he was traveling with a demon.
The sounds demons make differ from those of humans.
But...
I can pick up a sound so gentle and kind
from him, it almost brings me to tears.
Never before had I heard such a kind sound.
All living creatures constantly give off sounds.
These sounds spill out into the world.
Breathing, heartbeats, the sound of blood circulating...
By listening closely,
I could even tell what someone was thinking.
But I've been deceived by others time and time again.
I've always believed in whomever I wanted to.
Despite being a Demon Slayer,
Tanjirou is travelling with a demon.
But I'm sure he has a reason for that.
And I trust it's a reason I can accept.
And I...
And I'll ask Tanjirou directly myself!
So, you...
had better back off!
Let go of me, dammit!
You're freakin' annoying!
I won't let you lay a finger on that box!
It's precious to Tanjirou!
You're not touching it until he gets back!
Damn you!
Take this!
Move it!
No!
Take this!
Move it!
Draw your sword and fight me!
You spineless punk!
Tanjirou...
I protected it.
Since you said...
this was more important to you...
than your life.
All that bravado and you won't even
draw your sword, dumbass?
If you're a fellow Demon Slayer,
then let's see you fight!
If you ain't gonna fight,
get the hell out of my way!
Move it!
I've had enough!
If you won't get out of my way,
I'll just skewer you along with that box!
Stop!
That sure was a crazy Blood Art. It let him spin
the room around while staying on the offence.
Maybe the closer a demon is to Kibutsuji,
the more potent and troublesome
their Blood Art becomes...
I wonder if I really have a chance of beating them.
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
Kyougai, the demon in that mansion,
is a big fan of "The Eight Dog Chronicles",
and I hear he was writing
a biographical novel of his own.
Right, this is no time to be hung up!
Next, Episode 14, "The House with
the Wisteria Family Crest"!
Your big brother's gonna kick some butt!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I forgot about my broken bones!