Wisteria
Episode_15
Mount_Natagumo
Wisteria
Demon Slayer
Sulking won't do you any good.
You have to go help your friends.
Demon Slayer
PREVIEW
l
First, let's calm down
and listen to the
sounds around us!
First, let's calm down
and listen to the
sounds around us!
PREVIEW
l
I told you
to calm down!
Now, it's time
for a Taisho secret!
My real name
is Ukogi.
That's because my
favourite food is
ukogi rice.
That's because my
favourite food is
ukogi rice.
But Zenitsu
hasn't noticed yet,
so all I get is beans.
But Zenitsu
hasn't noticed yet,
so all I get is beans.
PREVIEW
l
An ukogi rice ball!
He's seriously
worried...
I guess this is
why you just
can't hate the guy.
I guess this is
why you just
can't hate the guy.
To Be Continued