Tanjirou...
Listen here.
You don't become a Demon Slayer for shits 'n giggles!
Guys like you must be purged!
Pronto!
The Demon Slayers aren't to be taken lightly!
Nezuko!
Zenitsu! Quit following her already!
Ta-n-ji-ro-u!
Let's be friends, Tanjirou!
Zenitsu! Stop chasing us! I beg you!
Oh, don't be like that, Tanjirou!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Stop!
Zenitsu!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Man, I'm starving.
Pardon me, sir.
Those clothes of yours are quite dirty, I see.
Allow me to clean them for you.
Please wear these in the mean time.
They're pleasant to the touch and quite comfortable.
How does tempura for dinner sound?
It's food covered with batter and fried.
Hey, wait up!
Come back here, Nezuko!
Wh-What was that for?
Hold up! Hold up!
Stop chasing me, Inosuke!
Tanjirou!
Full recovery.
North-northeast! North-northeast!
Your next mission is north-northeast!
The three of you are to go to Mt. Natagumo!
Head to Mt. Natagumo!
We'll be heading out, then.
Thank you so much for everything.
Allow me to strike some sparks.
It'd be much appreciated!
The hell do you think you're doing, old hag?
What are you, stupid?
It's to give us good luck!
It's a purification ritual because
we're going on a dangerous mission!
Always live your lives with great pride.
I wish you much luck in battle!
"Great pride"?
"Luck in battle"?
What's that mean?
Geez, this guy sure is thick.
Well, yeah. Now that you mention it,
it's kind of difficult to understand.
"With great pride"...
I guess it means that you know your place
and that you behave properly
so as to never disgrace yourself.
And the old lady is also praying for our safety.
Where's "my place" supposed to be?
What do you mean by "never disgrace"?
Well, that's...
How do you "behave properly"?
Why the hell would that old hag
pray for our safety anyway?
She ain't got anything to do with us, so why?
She doesn't know her own place, does she?
He sped up!
I won't be beaten!
Wait for me!
Hold up!
May I have a quick moment?
Zenitsu? What's wrong?
I'm scared!
Now that we're nearing our destination,
I'm quaking in my boots!
What's his ass doing on the ground?
Absolutely disgusting.
You're the last person I wanna
hear that from, Pig Face!
There's no way I'm the only one
getting weird vibes from that mountain!
Even so, what good would it do to just sit there?
I told you, he's disgusting.
"Disgusting"? As if!
I'm normal! I'm the normal one!
You guys are the weirdos!
What? What's wrong?
Hey...
What is this smell?
Tanjirou!
Wait!
Come on! Don't leave me all alone!
Don't just run away!
H-Help...
He's got our uniform on!
He's a Demon Slayer!
Something must've happened!
Hold up!
Are you all right?
What happened?
They were attached to me, too!
Save me!
I'm going in.
I'll go on ahead first.
You can follow me, shivering in your boots.
This is making me hungry.
Inosuke...
This is challenging enough for you, right?
Let's go!
The hell's this?
Spider webs?
God, these webs are fucking everywhere!
Pisses me off!
Yeah.
Inosuke?
What you want?
Thanks.
I felt a lot more encouraged
since you said you'd come along.
That twisted, ominous scent I was
picking up from the mountain...
It made me freeze a little.
So thanks!
They're pleasant to the touch and quite comfortable.
Always live your lives with great pride.
I wish you much luck in battle!
Inosuke...
Let's go.
We've come for backup.
I'm Kamado Tanjirou, Rank Mizunoto.
Mizunoto...
Mizunoto?
Why didn't they send a Hashira?
It doesn't matter how many Mizunoto they send!
It won't make a difference!
Inosuke!
Shut it!
If we're talking differences,
we can start with your very existence!
Or better yet, tell us what's
going on, you spineless fool!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Did you forget that I outrank you?
Th-The crow gave us the order!
So ten Demon Slayers sortied.
But not long after we started hiking up the mountain,
the Slayers...
The Slayers started killing each other!
I...
You did well to return.
So most of my children have been slaughtered?
If that's the case, we might find the Blood Moons there.
It seems I'll have to dispatch the Hashira.
Giyuu.
Shinobu.
As you wish!
If only humans and demons could just get along.
Wouldn't you agree, Tomioka?
Impossible.
Not so long as they continue to eat humans.
I wonder if they hate me.
Would you really leave your friend by the roadside?
Wouldn't you try to convince them
if you were really friends?
If they both tried to talk me into going,
Zenitsu...
Zenitsu.
I would've gone, okay?
I really would.
But no, off they went on their merry way
up that scary mountain.
Poor me, left all alone...
Lucky you. You don't have a care in the world.
You don't understand a thing about humans, do you?
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're not cute at all! I mean it!
Not that side of you!
Seriously, you've got zero charm!
I mean, look at how cute Nezuko is!
And she's a demon!
But you're a sparrow, and you're so vicious!
He took Nezuko with him!
Why did he have to take
my precious Nezuko with him?
Damn you, Tanjirou!
Don't bring a young lass into danger!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Nezuko!
What's that sound?
There it is again.
It's that sound again!
I heard this sound before,
and the next thing I knew,
everyone started killing each other!
Where's it coming from?
These guys are all dumbasses!
They don't even know we're
not allowed to fight each other!
No, that's not it!
They're not moving normally!
Something is manipulating them!
All right.
I'm gonna go cut 'em up!
You can't do that!
They're alive!
Some of them are still alive!
Besides, we can't harm the corpses of our allies!
Quit bossin' me around at every turn!
There's this strange, sweet scent coming from his back!
Threads! They're being manipulated by threads!
Cut the threads!
I already knew before you caught on!
Where's the demon controlling them?
What's this?
What is this sudden, strong odour?
Spiders!
So these spiders are spinning the threads?
That means...
Now then, my sweet little marionettes...
Dance until your arms and legs fall off.
Cutting the threads won't be enough!
The spiders will just stick more onto them!
So we need to...
That acrid smell again!
What is it?
It's coming in on the wind!
All we gotta do is kill those damn spiders, huh?
That's impossible!
They're too small, and there's probably a ton of them!
We've gotta find the demon controlling them!
Don't bother, Inosuke!
Inosuke, if you have some kind of ability
that can pinpoint the demon's location,
then give me a helping hand!
This weird smell has been flowing in
and it's blocking my nose!
And also, um...
It's Murata!
Murata!
Murata and I will find a way to deal with
the people being controlled!
Inosuke, you have to...
Don't disturb my family's peaceful life.
He's floating!
Wait, no.
He's standing on the threads!
What does he mean by "family"?
Mother will kill you all right away.
Mother?
Motherfucker!
Where the fuck do you think you're going? Fight me!
Fight—
Inosuke!
What'd he come here for anyway?
That kid probably isn't the demon pulling the threads!
First, let's...
Okay, okay, okay!
Stop nagging already, 'kay?
You just need me to find that demon, yeah?
Shut up for once, Mr. Forehead!
Beast Breathing! Seventh Fang!
Spatial Awareness!
Found 'em!
There you are!
I won't let anyone disturb us.
The five of us will continue to live in bliss as a family.
No one can break our bond.
Whoopsie-daisy!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Where are you?
Nezuko's in danger!
Stop chirping and help me find her, Chuntarou!
What are you so mad about?
Here, eat this and calm down.
Help me look once you're done, okay?
I mean, Nezuko's in danger!
Nezuko!
Next, Episode 16, "Letting Someone Else Go First"!